i drive over here and i see the weirdest
fight i've ever seen
jim why are you sad
oh guys everyone's dying around me
i can't do anything about it i'm just an
aaa
boy please why
we've gone completely stupid tonight
yep yes yeah like we just we just gave
up on uh playing this game normally
and now it's just a free-for-all of
emotions
vehicle choices
decoration choices
life choices
i drink two dr peppers today i mean i'm
just off the off the reservation
i'm on my seventh year yeah that's
normal for you he's on a sugar high
the dr pepper dr pepper is getting to
them i'm sorry i'm running away but
there's a job to do we got to do what
they say can't be done
we got a long ways to go in a short time
to get there
i mean
watch that bandit run
what have you done i thought it'd be
really funny to bring this thing kind of
have a meme night but
i didn't expect our entire team to
completely collapse here into
chaos and social unrest
what do you want help i don't know
what's happening i'm they're they're
trying to make love to me and i'm not a
pre
gentleman no no no means no all right
all right welcome take me out to dinner
first
seafood dinner
you all need to simmer down
you may be jealous of my barrel the
scarf but you got the more longer that's
done you know what's this i just need to
get free
the bulldog is off of you yeah we got
him we got them sir
no no i'm the quartermaster i brought
everything from base that you might need
i got a bicycle
i brought it too i've got a vacuum that
that's a flamethrower
you have a flamethrower yeah look at the
back
you wait you're taking my job from me
no
wait i look how many people better be
careful don't fall down there now
look how many people we have in our
tanks i figured we need two of them you
know
we're the quarter jim you're the only
tank here that's
here to fight yeah the the
that's an actual tank yes
i have a barrel and tracks
did you bring any leisure activities
i brought a bicycle
i have a dart board so we're about
physical fitness and relaxation i
brought beer
that's a good idea i brought a
flamethrower that's that's relaxing and
recreational
how is this awesome william throws a
beer sounds like an amazing time
that sounds like you're gonna die that
sounds like a country song
flamethrowers and
bear love my deer
oh oh yeah see i could take this is
there something in front of us
oh yeah yeah i'm pretty sure there is
yeah okay artillery is standing by
just serenade him you are anti-tank i am
no it's right there right there
yep
let me go ahead and arrange that amount
of dirt in front of us
there's one over here as well
do not have a shot please let me back up
please let me back up
he's been deleted sir
very good shot
got the torches was a good idea
something in the smoke
yep sherman's down oh my god good shot
good i have to reload hide me stick we
have uh targets down on our back right
please hide me
don't let them take me
i killed a sherman today the power of
the purple protect you does this make me
a real tank
you're a real boy you're backing your
butt into my face why is this happening
like this
did i do something wrong
weirdness am i right thank good job brad
thank you for stick what's happening
here i'm pumping you away from the
contact same thing in front
uh i think it's on the right side of the
bridge there you go another sherman
stick
you got it hello
okay if you want there he goes good job
jim yep here you go good job isaac if
you don't mind should i uh get a parking
spot here for the show i just took a
shot
from where red
i'm not sure way up on the hill okay
that's not good for us
no no just don't back up we're fine
where's the hill to protect us when you
say don't back up it's fine that makes
me feel like it's not fine no it's fine
the planes are up
the planes the planes they have planes
they have planes we have the power of
you see a roof on this thing
you see the bombs
i appreciate that you want quality time
but it's not no not now i'm trying to
push you under the bridge because then
you have a room there's thanks on the
bridge i hear them to the high right
that's fine like you're the troll
i'm gonna kick up into the right see if
i can grab one but then you're not a
troll anymore and then you can't get the
toll how are you going to pay for your
troll food if you don't have the troll
toll trolls need troll food
yeah
what do trolls eat
troll food i was gonna say reddit comets
but
is there anything to the top right yeah
i hear it
i just need to climb hey it's someone to
be like in a boom or something else to
push me
have you looked up it's right there i
just need one more horsepower
it's so close
okay come on
it's right there is there sherman
i could literally read a serial number
from here
i'm hurt yeah there we go i'm good i'm
good stop
why did this work back down back down
back down
wait we're going down good shot i have
to reload
i just woke up let's push over the top
here well i went uh hey there's a tank
over here okay uh rotate left two tanks
two tanks
oh there's so many oh there's a lot
covering fire
here's the gun
oh jim torreira
what's what's happening
why'd you certainly jim okay well you
started preparing so we gotta go this
way well i'm just gonna leave i'm gonna
pack up my stuff
all these planes have bombs that are
coming so you might okay i'm gonna live
underneath the bridge now just help me
i'm perfect hi jim no stay hi jim thank
you abandoned him
the bridge was your home
but we can't live and die underneath the
bridge we have to live free
i could yeah we are the planes are
really unhappy
i don't know how far this is
sending it he's down i don't know how
far it is directly hits them kills them
in one shot and it was a complete guess
i promise
i have to drive off now kill more thanks
just fell down here something just fell
down here yeah there's something on the
outside of these trains too
something is falling down here that is a
half track
that's happening he doesn't see me he
doesn't see me
don't look at me
oh
what's looking at you i'm good i'm good
half reload i got it here in a second
he's down all right
thank you so much jim
yeah i do what i can two left behind the
train cars oh no i will protect you i
got prank train car in my way if they
push this way i got him i took his ammo
i took him first one's
i cannot believe this plan is working do
not get to live
uh said goodbye
the points
you came back yeah he's been uh he's
been looking for me for a while
i'm watching all my friends die
making the stuka sound jimmy got two
planes diving on you
stay in the bridge
no i was making the snooker sound uh the
planes have hit each other i repeat the
planes have hit each other
you just got a times two maneuver kill
sir
that's still there i know
oh you gotta target the hill here
i got his cannon i can't shoot you
anymore oh i'm doing bad duck things
stick you just need to take a breath
it'll be okay
i saved you jim i just saw your plane
play off of nobody that i shot at uh it
you know thought it was the enemy plane
because there's no name on it don't
worry about it
and then i realized it was a stuka
i'm going home
what do you guys need air support on i'm
going home watch out for the other plane
my engine just combusted into fire
i don't know that's cool yeah there's a
i'm going in
state boy one up here
no i'm going home oh okay where's home
that looks like a very angry sherman
down the bottom that hill yeah i think
he uh realized there's a few more of us
here than he thought fire in the hole
he's down
the tank buster's back in action
that's how we do it
i can't name myself tank buster
you know what you know what you you
i literally just busted a tank down
there you killed a lot of tank don't at
all there it is i mean like we can go up
that name don't lift just don't the
planes are still looking for me i need
to go hide again
yeah like we go home
no with the how about the nutcracker the
tank cracker
you can call yourself a ball breaker
okay
no no if he wants to call himself the
tank buster he has to have the cool
siren you know
you know
what i have to be from the
ghostbusters yeah yes that's it yeah and
you gotta have the you know the cute
girl no
thank you for calling tank busters how
may i help you you know with the
brooklyn accent i just got shot uh high
left
mark right there
i am broken down a cannon
if you want to nudge my nose left oh he
shot me i traded him good job i stick
i'm stuck like this
are you but my field of fire is
basically those two trees in front of me
i could do like a field goal thing
i could do this and really mess you up
no i can aim high
let me show you how high look at that
look at that elevation
are you jealous yet
look at that it just keeps going yo put
that down it just goes up and up and up
it's inappropriate put that down i can't
believe you're gonna do that in public i
look like an elephant
i can't
what is happening in front of me that's
it that's friendlies
no that's i gotta send you on that one i
don't know what that is stick take it
out i bounce i just got shot right close
right close right right no
plot twist
i'm shooting i will not die i will not
see more friends don't lost my
drivetrain
hey red it's all up to you right now you
won't get hurt
no pressure to make this shot
why is it getting closer
the 50 kill is not the 50 mil is not
working for me yeah he's just pushing
the road he's right behind you i've got
problems up here
promo's down why is there t-34 touching
you red
red's attractive red i'm just going to
push you
yeah that's not good this is not good
for morale
this is not high sir can i help you
go keep morel no the browser
there is a multiple tank
less tanks
everything's dead
there's a lot of tanks
hey thank you for knocking down that
wall
i appreciate that can you kill that
tournament please
oh which sherman
right in front i think the one we killed
he's gone yeah there's okay those guys
say is there two shermans
sorry i got it i gotta reload here
you got a target out there
where is he at red
right down there i just took his i i'm
the kool-aid man i'm swinging out i see
it give me a second
oh i get my barrel down aiming down and
slam
there we go that's two shermans
on this episode of sherman hunter
for the very dangerous 105 millimeter
how to let's drive on i don't think we
want oh hi jim yeah i don't want to be
here target at the corner
about where it was right there i can't
shoot through the wall oh see it's a
chappie is it over there now
critically it's still alive okay i'm
just gonna
yeah i see him
i'm trying i couldn't shoot through
tower i'm sorry
all right he's down hiding repairs
i'm
uh give me a half second
i do not see him
yeah no line of sight is that the corner
right there
okay don't scare me like that it's a lie
oh it is live
i hit him
i i do not see a sherman sir oh yeah
right there i see it
uh no good i think something that got in
the way of it like a fence
yeah i don't see yet i'm trying to
disease right on top of the friendly
tank right there i just couldn't get the
line of uh the clear angle
i'm gonna charge i'm gonna charge charge
on three chords loaded i have a shot
and sending it
there we go
nice shot
well done i do my part to kill the big
scary shermans that's
basically what i'm here for hey we
appreciate it with your big dirt gun
like i said this is episode two of
sherman hunter
we're hoping to get a whole season out
of it how about those other big guns
that they have
hey uh we're adding something in front
of you
okay uh i'll take the paper out of that
i shot the locus because i thought that
was more scary i contributed another one
behind him yeah that's another sherman
right there i tried to diversify my
skill set and messed up i got the little
guy
are they both german no they both died
nevermind
at the same time that was pretty cool
it's almost like we meant to do that
i thought there was more yeah we are a
uh well machine i just took a shot from
somewhere about direction okay i'll move
that way hey uh jim can we get a factory
tour
uh yes welcome to the uh mid factory
where they make uh uh
the letter b
you know i found it it's a charby one
yeah speaking of the letter b he's down
but something else shot me i'm being
shot from front right
all right everything's going to hell
here i'm being shot from my left hard
left all right playing truck something
something chase me
oh i just took hits uh jim right beside
you through the wall looking looking
looking it's a crusader
if i can knock this down i get him crack
there wall gone
tank goodbye
all right
do you know where i can get some more
ammo sir where's the gift shop uh
yeah you go you go to the the bee cap
and you get some more ammo you'll be
fine hitchhim something's shooting at
you in a violent rate of fire oh don't
worry about it honey i can deal with it
my own do i need a chaperone
no you'll be fine you're an adult
so do you come here often for all your
tank needs
uh yes welcome to uh the beat cap where
we make uh oil
if you look to uh our you know
your left do you actually work here no
because this doesn't seem like you know
anything about this place
yeah no i just wing it man he's like one
of the local oompa loompas hey jim do
not panic but there's a tank to her
immediate right
oh really because i i would like to
panic
it it's uh it's kind of big and i don't
have a shot let me push no don't go that
way if you go that way it's gonna be
it's getting closer it's getting closer
no don't panic
it's dead
okay i'm glad somebody else more
confident us got it yeah yeah we are we
just fell apart there we just
emotionally fell apart when hi mike
hey there
are you trying to like show off
i'm trying to drive this thing it's a
little bit difficult
we have eight wheels you better be
careful yeah all right
they know that's what the puma does i
don't want you to get turned around
i i have to revoke the daddy part of
baghdadi mike
that that sounded so strange when he
said it
yeah
yeah what revoked the daddy part if the
police don't ever say revoke the daddy
part i see the guy taking charlie
actually two of them
yeah the one has a one two for one yeah
oh the other one that's 20 mil i'm going
to hide behind this filler until someone
gets that is it on your mark yeah it's
right on that mark it's to the left of
it on the back side of the fountain
towards the west side
i'm just gonna nuzzle with this hi red
hey do some repairs direct front if you
can shoot him i might be very
appreciative i feel like you're you're
nuzzling
i'm just going to hide my face until the
war ends
yes bad news
the march of the shermans is back for a
sequel okay i can uh can help with that
definitely coming back
oh hi red right here stand by
aiming and lobbing
trimming down i'm going to back up to
reload again let's shove my face in the
pillar
i'll check and make sure if there's any
more actually the safest thing i can do
for the screws is keep them right there
three cores reloading
uh hi red i'm gonna swing out for it
i got driver gunner on that guy right
thank you so much i don't okay i got
stuck i got stuck
where am i aiming where am i aiming
harder right right there oh right there
that building
i can see i'm just gonna let it rip you
i'm bouncing up and downward for some
reason
on the other side of that building that
you're using as protection there's three
of them be careful i saw them on the map
a second ago
if he pushes out right i can get a shot
and otherwise no i'm gonna watch our six
i appreciate that actually let's turn
let's go that way anyway
flanky maneuver uh well we're two
awkward vehicles to flank but we're
gonna try
i mean i'm fast
be careful to your close right there's
gonna be something i'm surprised there's
gonna be at least one in there
how did that surprise go
oh no
what's oh no
front
looking
i'm no shot i have no shot there's also
planes draping us
okay i gotta run i wants my gunner he
couldn't run
he's uh he's right behind that pillar
right there
copy that i'm gonna see if i can angle
i if anybody wants to go like a machine
gun they want to aim it for that point
they're dropping already as well
oh no
this is not good we're all in very
lightly armored things yeah
tank close front
take him critical driver i got in there
there you go push it red here comes the
bomb 122. i'm diving
i hear a stuka
it's time to hide
something else to shoot me from my left
i guess
airplane
oh look airplanes
how you doing sir
watch out i gotta fire on him
get shot there's like two more up here
yes
there's two back here
okay you go with those three those guys
are very congested yeah i got a plane
behind me head towards stick
in the city it's actually on the b18 no
it's not i don't know what it's doing
it's uh it's on the 18 feet something
just shot me i got a aaa in their spawn
uh i'm gonna mark it right there
and that was so good
try that
again
oh
where'd that plane go i know one got
shot down but there should be another
one
okay sorry i'm coming back to get tanks
on charlie
uh there's an m24 headed on the our side
like our main road at sea
i'm looking i'll get something's on me
brett i got a plane up if you could fly
me flight jumpers like me there's a fire
on board my aircraft that's very toasty
i do believe i'm in trouble
that is uh minus a wing
10 10 out of 10 on the landing thank you
jim
[Music]
you