so stick when you do laundry and uh your
dirty sock fell out of your hamper and
they fall
why is that a conversation we're having
no no no i'm gonna kill that stew
oh there's thanks pushing me
i do not wanna know about stickboy's
dirty laundry no
no i'm gonna keep firing and ignore wait
you're just talking yeah i'm just
gonna yeah look at me ha ha german no
just push
i don't want to deal with this anymore
aim for the turret oh yeah i'm trying to
i can i guys barrel so feel free to take
better shots
no good i'm gonna take a track if i can
pinching his cheek didn't work
right track is gone he can't move
i'm gonna try and push a little bit
closer if i can
got him nice job i'm gonna check left
excellent shot
that was that was supposed to when he
disabled if you can cover right i'm
going to peek in here
yep i'm watching your right side yeah i
just don't trust that there's nobody in
here
i'm getting in the factory or whatnot
yeah they usually try to push on this
little road right here beside
us there's a gentleman on the
a point a gentleman on the eight point
what is this a what
element you say a gentleman not a tank
not the enemy a gentleman you know what
okay excuse me gentlemen
joey just talk about your laundry no no
no no
dirty laundry i'm pushing the point i'm
pushing the point
i'm looking for the lad that's on the
point
oh there's a thing down there oh it's a
locust there's a panzer
maybe four down there to the left yes
turned you good over there stick yeah
you're already
killing a locust i'm gonna push in here
and try to get back to stick we can
yep come on sherman you got the power
got something right here i think oh yeah
he's moving i see it i see it i can take
it for you if you need
i got a hit no damage he went behind
hill for me
uh-oh get what that's called i'm
attempting to turn around but the
sherman doesn't want to
not have some problems with this little
snow in the hills too
yeah okay tank right there gap he's
pushing towards us you got shots in
not a great one yet give me a moment
fired and missed
is he aware that you shot at him i don't
know he was pushing over there
that's not a pants before truck that's a
truck you're like completely no there's
another one behind him but that's not a
panzer four
the gaffney's back up towards you yeah
um the identification book i'm gonna
finish them off with that one right here
on the other side of the sperm
well i thought i saw something boxy
moving so i thought it was like a panzer
4 hole
that's a very interesting looking pins
are for you know what you can make fun
of me i'll make fun of myself
i should probably go to my doctor i'll
call it a tiger like
every other sherman did uh hey that's a
sherman
tiger no that's a sherman oh there's
also chaffee left to it when it's
building
or actually right there on the corner
you guys are finding all the fun
is this a race gym oh yeah i'm gonna get
him
i would recommend you guys don't go
bumper to bumper there's no plane yeah
we're
we're bumping and grinding over here wow
wow you just ran me off the road black
flag
hey hey you touch the hips you get the
lip
get the whip yep hey i don't know we
i have no whips no three m3 lead
to our left right nope that's left nope
wait hold on
right boy instructions are absolutely
amazing to listen to it
it's right so many points i think we
should turn around and help them because
oh hey hey there's an three elite right
there it's fine i had a there's another
one behind him
oh he's a small boy i don't see anything
myself
oh he's dead okay stick got him yeah
yeah where did
i'm to say hi to him oh no what's oh no
there's a there's a little one right
there watching help
standby okay okay
hi the rear jim i killed it
is that all of them got another one
another what now
uh hey guys never mind it's dead sorry
we're very close
yeah we need to uh finish off the kv2 if
we can yeah we do go live
i hear bombs when you get some space and
go under building
building to your right building to your
building to right copy a chappy
off-roading find you it's behind you
it's behind you oh thank you for killing
it yeah it's right beside us
i gotta show loaded give me a second all
right he's down
can we uh when we'll fall back towards
like charlie you're taking charlie
yeah i'll meet you guys along the way
yeah this is the wrong intersection of
sit-in
yeah there's a lot of tigers here i have
yeah we're gonna keep making that joke
gaff mentions that one reference and
then everything's a tiger
everything's a tiger i like reading the
books that call tiger ii
uh was it tiger royale it's like it's a
big mac oh yeah
like there i was facing the tiger royale
tiger battle royale no steak don't say
that too loud
yeah i just kind of died a little bit on
the inside trying to process all that
and that was right
my brain went to ten different places i
never wanted to go i will leave
thank you today for visiting the a
factory where we stamp and make
all forms of the letter a to our left is
our a
processing plant where we take the fresh
lower case a's and turn them into
uppercase a's
next falling to your right is where we
do the different parts we have times new
roman
comic sans bold italic and italicized
and then in the very front you see we
have our shipping department where the
various shapes and sizes of the letter a
get brought out to all wood processing
plants across the nation
i don't know how long he's going to go
with this
by the way there's a kv one down oh i
just got my transmission
i don't care about the a factory i want
it dead uh
if you see that down there uh not where
i'm at you've got two busted shermans
behind you
yep i see them now hey jim did they make
sherman parts here
no sir we just make the letter a here do
you have any a
parts a-shaped parts for your sherman
you require
i need a transmission that has a in the
name
uh let's see what way that was from my
right that was close right behind you
jim
sherman behind you that just drive past
me i saw the shadow of something in
there
them uh hey they just got murdered in
front of me
he's just outside your door yeah i'm
looking
i bounced i bounced i bounced i bounced
where is it where is it front front run
dead front
i don't think that's the thing that
killed them it's the sherman in front
it's the sherman
i'm looking i'm looking i just see kate
i see
he's he's hiding behind the kb
there's actually one closer right here
that's the one that murdered our boys
oh well there was one up here should we
push in before we die
i'm pushing i'll be right behind you
might be a bad idea to be honest bill i
like that stick boys being assertive
hi this is please please no very bad
factory grounds
there's literally a pile of sherman's
here jim what are you gonna do about
that
clean up aisle three think you see
anything left
no all right let's push hard right then
what about front of your friend
my goodness hard right of me heart right
at me oh he's about the sermon pushing
my point locust
wow stick is on fire we'll get this
paintings put down
he's a monster anything else we need to
worry about oh there's a plane up bank
over here
pain train he's not here lower back
where'd he go pain train is here
it's just the little one that oh gosh
dick is going all in
this is the t50 have mercy he took
oh my gunner he just okay well uh hi
hi oh i missed my shot do you need help
yes please yes please push
push you guys get up there i lost my
driver please don't die
yeah this would be quite embarrassing
thank you the t-50 almost killed all of
us
yeah they pack a main punch they're
little baby t-34s but they got teeth
i thought i could push the corner shoot
him before he shot me and i completely
missed my shoulder when you're done over
there
feed needs assistance b copy that we'll
head back the direction
hey j what do they make of the b point
factor the a factor is cooler
they make the letter a here well what's
made at the b point
b's like bumblebees or
the letter b the letter b it's it's a
it's a you know one's union one's not
you know
it gets pretty ugly where do you come up
with this
all inside my little mind you don't want
to know what's in there
no no no i don't thank you for visiting
the a factory the gift shops on the left
that's a bomb yes that's a gift factory
for sure
why it is we have an explosive t-shirt
sale today
why does the a factory have a gift shop
why because maybe some people like the
letter a and they want to wear it on a
shirt stick
don't argue with capitalism maybe you
need a gift
get it a gift i'm here all week
make sure the tip your waiter
what was that bravo it's not a million
dollar question
well there's nothing yet probably i
don't know but i was getting ripped
apart from there
i think we got here too late jim yeah
it's a little leveled over here it's
not how i remember i'm gonna try and
grab a crew member the only thing that
is happening
in this game is is uh
bad puns the a factory tour
and apparently the gift shop oh you're
about to roll yourself over
okay you better pump your brake stick
boy
that's why i'm here and i'm stopped hey
there's a tank behind us that's alive
what now what aim
i got a driver i have him i'm in trouble
i'm in trouble it's being funny
i got an angle angle commander gunner
engine but still not dead we hit
everything but the gunner
no it's a little baby t-34 you've got
two things
i'm gonna hit what's on the right f2 57b
is getting the bomb
unloading and it was good
fighters two fighters they can handle
the fighters for a second i'll
deliver the bomb for the guys i'll be
back in the air with you well that guy's
pushing that guy's pushing you very
i have a very bad plane yeah no
firecrest is a good plane believe in it
uh okay i'm loading jim
is out i'm alive i'm in fighter mode
plane going up for you i need you to do
a heartbreak up there
i'm just kind of stuck upside down i'm
sorry i don't have any ordinance
i have no more tail he doesn't have any
more
things either they are both on you okay
where are you
oh come on give me airspeed i have to
shoot a little
all that airplane's nimble
that's a bomb oh my goodness what the
heck
wait what deliver the bomb p40 i have no
idea
i'm sorry that might have been the one i
shot maybe
i'm on the ice16 know if that means
anything
i just um having problems hanging with a
hellcat
hi can you please pull over believe like
i'm gonna crash into the okay yeah i'm
gonna need
some type of new plane over here you
know what he's never gonna expect
i know what that is that's a bolo
mr gaff he is underneath you yep
i'm gonna climb no clue about the attack
willie
okay i'm gonna do moves i'm gonna get
him slow down for you and it's gonna be
your job to kill him
or is he going away swinging around
oh he's good he's doing something for
you he likes you now
he might try to ram you yeah
got him nice job thank you so much
ridiculous i had that much trouble for
night 16.
hi high five hi how's it going you just
want something
yeah i got plenty more i'm going for
that transmission
oh no no no okay we're all good well
maybe good
good there was a there was a stew about
to touch me and i did not like that so i
shot him in the face
normal tank reactions oh i've got
somebody peeking right there
good shot oh more danger there's a lot
behind him
you guys okay back there yeah for the
time being i'm gonna come to you though
i'm gonna go flank if you guys can hold
him there i'll drive around and we'll
hit them from the rear
that's wait there's something behind me
i'll hold them here this or something
i got the weight hole and there's
something in our team from over here
uh there's a chaffey somewhere but i
lost it
good shot good shot feels weird that i'm
in a british tank but it's american
it's a sherman a british sherman
shooting the american tanks i'm very
perplexed
uh left yeah it's a little bit advising
to shoot the sherman because it's like
i'm shooting one of them i am a sherman
if i
how's it going i'm still more wrestling
can't talk i don't think tanks are meant
to
do that that way all right i'm almost on
their rear that that sounds
bad phrasing just is it in your weight
class stick
or is he cheating all right well
actually i'm cheating
all right i'm on there six sherman
switch that's you that's your words
what were you fighting i don't know what
is why is that chasing you
i don't know what just killed what what
there's so many of them oh no hi sherman
oh wait
i'm not i'm not friendly sherman oh i
feel so bad
british sherman's just destroying him
with one shot
m10 got me the tank destroyer was like
enough of this games
i don't have a barrel so i'm gonna do my
best to help you here
yeah he shot me i think aiming throw
yours
problems all right i'll walk him up here
you just gotta
one second thank you five years for my
my mark down to our right we need to
push out of here
okay yeah hit the gas pedal and go i'm
going i'm going run if you can
run if you can we got to save jim i'm
going to say somebody
how many this is the fact you were to
make these things
i'm looking for a shot i shot way too
far to the left no good he didn't
i might have betrayed you here gaff with
my bad shooting
trying to break breach don't get on the
side there you go i got that one
something will be pushing up from my uh
my rear over here
you're over there got it but then maybe
yeah there it is never mind hi i'm gonna
repair you we're gonna have to fight for
our life are you ready
coming thank you and the words of
beastie boys you gotta fight for your
right to party
all right let's party okay it's gonna be
to your clothes right maybe something to
the left
all right don't worry watch it i'm
watching you're here
let's push your heart right still card
right stupid right there right in front
of you stick right go go step go
we distracted it there was two of them
stug panzer two and an fl-13
on the amex amex down get a friend
that is that's not the right to party oh
that's not
oh my gosh it's it's just this is
bananas over here
this is absolutely bananas hi i'm sorry
can you not point that oh that's big gun
okay um well how do i put your barrel in
the air
and i get my gunner back and i shoot you
how's that work for you
just tell him to go away hold on i got
him again nice
why is that here please please don't let
that see me
and that's you think seven just drove
past me like it's going to go pick up
his kids from school wait a minute
he says hiding over there the family i'm
i'm nearby
it's just it's just sitting behind that
wall now and where he is but i don't
know if i should go over and get him
um i'm gonna finish capping out c it's
being decapped
yeah i'm checking my right i think i'm
gonna go for it
on the other side of this wall here mr
gaff right here
i feel like it's a trap airplane
i got him we're good my job
oh good job good job nice i would like
to get a crew member possible
yeah i would like to not be here that's
hello jim
hello welcome to
the train here oh we don't we meet like
this all the time
so uh i'm gonna put this out there
there's three of us all in the
same building uh two of us are looking
each other face to face i don't think
this is good
this version of the bombs hit and
because saying there's an airplane
trapping us
no i don't i don't feel like it's gonna
be fine here in a second you know
usually it only there's the bombs
that's what i told you about jim oh see
we're fine no no we're fine
nope i don't think we are fine i'm gonna
drive off now make a new life at bravo
to quiet before the loud or something
like that hey that does not help me when
i'm driving towards my death here
why does it not help because i saw three
marks over a second ago i'm waiting for
them all oh there's one
fancy 4-h that's not well that is alive
there is a big swedish boy right there
okay that's two of them where's their
third mark third one was high right
oh and there's that one there's also
that one i didn't mean to cut you off
that came from my hard left behind the
berm
there's a mark on my left you're moving
i
see a driver it's the focus i got
them just hit me from the right i got a
mark on it
all right i see it nice job thank you
for the mark
second one right there you got the eyes
man i'm just going to shoot where you
mark
g34 on that corner i have no eyes on you
dropping smoke
i'm good to move another one yeah just a
heads up there's one in front of you on
the other side of the uh
fountain roger i'm going to push in
yep yeah it's fired again
you got one right there it's the very
top of him i can see him over the top
left side if you can get a shot into the
turret ring do so
is right one far back right here
it's a sherman it's a sherman p-34
engine radiator fire got him oh we got
another one across the way
well there's one more left i gotta deal
we have awakened the tornado get ready a
tornado yeah the guy pushing the corners
there
that is a big truck with a big gun i
assume
at the 29k looking at me i'm still
dealing with sherman over here too many
bushes in front of my face
right they're going to keep the cab
thank you sick
yep nice job all right
pushing out pushing out i would assume
they're going to come from that
direction next we might want to angle
and put some people out that way
where are we looking where where where
i'm gonna push off this way stick where
i'm facing
yep you just hold that line
yeah it's got shot right on me okay
anybody see where that was from uh i can
i only see the one that calf shooting in
this alleyway how's the dead husk i i
think that
or my left i just got hit left both left
kv-1
there we go fire extinguisher moving
that might have been it yep uh
g34 cruise down i could have sworn i got
a shot from over there
already but it might be wrong
see your mark over there all right t34
is down
that's still back over there that mark
good this amx is still alive over here
yep where is he i can't see him very
well look for my machine gun fire
uh like i'm just put over there oh i'd
see him shooting
there's a wall in the way right now so i
can't see him very well
i got him i got tracked there we go but
he can't he can't move oh we got a hit
no dice
i've killed his engine about three times
now okay i got his engine as well there
he is there we go
all right nice okay do we wanna
still push this direction and see if
anybody else is over here sure i'll
follow you
battle buddies uh b's being taken so
we can fall back to bravo i just feel
the second we turn around we're gonna
get like
swarmed from the river of course
we kind of just got swarmed now so
yeah if they come into waves don't they
all right let's be naive let's turn
around oh my gosh jim your eyes
hi they're so little yeah even in even
in waves you know there's that period
where the wave goes back out where you
know you could like run
you run at the water and you challenge
it before it comes back at you
they're already here the waves here i
lied oh no
you got one of them what do you got i
don't know it's a sherman i'm just gonna
move
i don't want sherman on sherman any
market for me
down the road to the left of my husk
understood i'm looking for it
don't see anything oh i see him he's
out
i missed i'm pushing for you
he's down nice thank you now should we
go to bravo
we avenged the sick boy um if you wanna
you're gonna be the one crossing that
path right there hey it's all good i got
confidence
i just brought some giant rockets i'm
hoping these work out for me
damn oh yeah they seem to be working
nice
that was a very bright light that just
hit him
if you see any tanks holler i've got
some presents you brought the light to
his life i'm the british santa claus up
here so you let me know where they're
needed
i thought santa didn't exist santa's
real your parents lied to you they
someone buy you presents
oh i just put that one a bit aside but
he's lost his tracks
all right looking i've got two more left
of these big bad boy what is that
i've got a couple on the nope that's
husks you shoot at me you get a present
oh come on there you go mozzie you got
it
don't be going down on us now i got the
barrel of him the rocket i'm pretty
proud of that
don't come this way don't come this way
oh no i want to come this way
no i want to go that way oh i'm three
leaves
stick boy present oh that's gonna give
you present
well the magic
[Music]