there's i've just ran into one in the
bush
oh oh oh
uh things are all right i promise things
are all right how are you doing
not good it's not good here there's two
of two of them there okay
i gotta go back around i blocked the
path for this one so stand by
i helped i got my problem okay i'm glad
to hear that
be sure to check bushes there might be
goodbye
no you're not you're not leaving me no
i'm good we're not leaving yet
bo i don't know how but they they
managed to not bomb the i'm trying to
become anti-air know if this is a good
idea or not
i got it don't worry about it put that
down okay that's all right i'll put
you tell me put my put that barrel down
okay sorry hold on if i locked it up
yeah there we go to just drive around my
snout is back in the ground where it
belongs i'm sorry
around the corner i think we're gonna do
this together okay
what corner that one you said there was
bmp around here
oh where where oh
assault mode is on let me can you do i
have no barrels i'll do my best here
it's your job
i have no barrels there's two of them
two of them one's down
i see you kill him working on it he's
down
excellent my transmission ate the shot
you are such a helpful
you say that but the evil things are
still here and we're not going to make
out this alive if we don't keep a
positive attitude okay positive attitude
you are such
a helpful tank that is the ultimate
wedge fighting machine that has no
downsides whatsoever
you you keep you keep you keep the good
words coming because
uh the the i think the darkness is
closing in
what darkness would you like some
preparing i got it um
do you have parts that'll fix this old
world war
ii tank i got it look i can back it up i
can put my thing down reverse it
look see down here for myself here we go
hi hi i can do almost anything you can
do
but i can do it better oh see now you
both need repairs aren't you glad i'm
here well you killed purple
but these fixed and you're fixed ta-da
thank you it's all for eventually
follow me does adventureland have a
like upgrade package do you like how
i've placed my armor all the way down
because i expect the worst thing it's
actually a little bit too angled down
why are you looking at us but why are
you oh good call out
you know what did you no fighting back
there or also pull
the strv over stop it the s tank is not
going to put up with us
what are you going to do like take them
to the top and rock them back really
hard till they get
sick you know what jim you're not
inviting our next field trip
well i i'm sorry nope you're not you're
not invited
no pizza party free think on the hard
right i just saw shelf life across me
sorry goodbye where is it from
oh one less of us now right
yeah something just threw a show across
the battlefield
right in front of me i shot the ground
he's right there
i lost my engine him he's running around
me
there's a lot damn it's on your close
right this is bad
this has gone every possible way wrong
they're now throwing airplanes into me
and is it working
no the mighty weapon i can't aim my
barrel up
what's behind me simmer down there folks
there's enough me to go around
i don't see oh there no they're just
they just roll past me
if i get this transmission fixed i can
shoot one of them
no no no no no big boy don't you aim
whether we don't
now you're going to get it is that
another bomb
aim up and he's done
well there's another one i know there's
one of my quotes right there
there's two there's two to your left yes
i don't know what you expect me to do
about it nothing i'm just
i'm just trying to to keep you informed
i'm in low rider mode right now
i helped just drop them right on me
i see him i see him thank you
okay i have a heart i'm not sure what's
going on anymore
i don't approve of it though
i would just like to compliment the
durability of that wedge
while only make my wedges on the finest
cheese
parmesan cheddar peas heart did you say
parmesan was the finest cheese
yeah i do like it on pizza
what parmesan pizza is great
you but then it gets all soggy you know
what grease it soaks it up it's like no
dry parmesan
you know what the superior pizza topping
is
i swear to god if you say pineapple he
will kiwi
what okay did he say kiwi or kiwis
get him out of here is he chopping up
kiwis on the pizza i am going to call
the police
get out out
i appreciate how he's in like when the
most armored vehicles and then it just
kind of gradually gets crappier
the more the line follows stick i'm just
going to
use stickboy as mobile cover i'm gonna
go uh
what are you why are you in the whoosh
is fun follow the ush
watch this these guys over here they
don't expect to use attack
ooh
there's so many things i crashed i
crashed my car oh i'll go i'll go help
out the minivan
he needs there's so many things i'm
sorry but i'm in safe hands there's so
many things over here
safe hands yeah like safe
safe hands like no no no no no
okay i got four of the missiles left and
running away operation uh plank is
still a go they're still very angry
why am i alive why why is this happening
oh don't put me down put me down
one
yeah i'll just do circles okay oh the
mud the mud
the mud thank you thank you okay nope
him ah
we headed under control sir oh what are
you doing
can you see my rope wheels they're kind
of becoming one what are you yeah
also there's a sister to give me a
proctology exam
oh this is uh oh what is what is
happening hi boys
don't get me come through i'm gonna i'm
gonna look at this see i'm like a little
rider
i i have hydra look see i can put it
down
and then i'm gonna bring it back up you
ready you gonna twerk that ass
i'm gonna bring it up i'm gonna bring it
up oh look
at your twerk look at that gun's in the
air
oh oh we're getting okay easy there
easy easier him what
yeah i know i know you you're jealous of
the pancake right now
hey hey the pancake yeah because i'm
flat and then i go to wedge
oh yeah now my cheese wedge
thanks for being my space no i'm not
your spaced armor
stick drive faster
hello gorgeous i didn't see anything
poke his head out
and boop loader track
oh don't you aim that at me oh yeah down
there i found mia
sm now it's time to attack charlie hey
so where are you guys gonna go
see we're oh i'm sorry i need to give
you 10
year uh advance i'm not that so oh my
gosh jim you
filming a commercial over there extreme
sports bro i live dangerously oh hello
and what'd you find this maneuver is
gonna cost me eight years leave it to
you
you may take high left yes please i'm
covering up i trust you
don't do that but hey jim can i have a
push no stick with bo
all right i'll stick with bo on the high
ground
is that alive that's alive isn't it oh
hi there is it bradley's down
good shot who else is up here
that's a friendly t-54 i don't see
anything on the right i'm gonna push
left
make sure nobody's up here hey jim we
have the high ground
oh but i can jump then we hold yes this
is perfect
you do extreme sports i do extreme
sports
parkour yeah dude hey wait you're
blocking my you're blocking my jam
my track i've lost my track
i need this i need this i need this
behind
okay i okay i can't aim right now oh god
no
above us to the right well what about
close bro what about quotes
don't worry about that nevermind don't
worry about that guy what about the
plane what about the bomb
hi jim i love stick missile oh i caught
up my face
right there right there mark also
something up there
i've broken on the wick okay i've fixed
the wiggling right there sorry what
okay you might not wear them can you
back up a minute your your tank is
making might take nervousness
i don't believe you there we go i got
better
nope okay hi here hold
if we work together i can finish this
off there we go
all right once to the high left of fire
missile right there
yeah he's poking out why is this
happening again there you go
stick please stop i can't aim like this
this is not the life
i'm not jim died and now it's just up to
us
and i'm trying to fix your wiggling all
aim faster
oh it's over there it's over there it's
over there it's over there
though i'm trying to fix the wiggle i'm
trying to scan for other things you just
shoot the thing
that is not going to help actually kind
of did
but then i can't aim right right i need
to go backwards
yes please tell me backwards show me
backwards
oh he killed the tow truck i saw that
this isn't going to go well for me
oh i exploded damn leader this is
bravo whoa
it's time to convince attack careful
there buckaroo
is the tank still staying up on the hill
launching the missiles
hey fire right here i got this
that was a lie you did not get that i
did nothing to him
good job good job oh helicopter near me
uh
i see it's shadow i'm working my way
back to i see him
oh this is a bad day he's got the
toe rotor issues
what it's a helicopter free-for-all down
here what
why helicopters as far as the eye can
see oh wow
a stick wants some motivation no i'm
good
well hemp that's not funny him
you know what happened last time let's
not talk about last time uh there's a
tank
way over there i had a building that
looks like a rock
did you see any other helicopters holler
[Music]
there's
there's something shooting at me going
to the right well something something's
shooting at me
you gotta kill that guy because he's
gonna threaten me
you know the uh the pressure's on
already
well you don't have to you don't have to
add to the weight that's on these
shoulders
i already did die he's gonna die again
there it is there it is right here
there go no
small problem with the uh
the exit egress
navigate communicate i think he didn't
do any of those you know what
shot you uh this brandon machine gun
around just kind of tapped off my head
yeah what what is oh where'd he go
he was right here is that you jim i'm
not crazy
to the right oh there's people there's
people yeah it's that one of you though
shooting me
oh my goodness stick this is what are we
doing
what are these white decisions
i can't that i'm stuck here this is so
well i'm going back downhill
earth tanks ball yeah i see this but
there's also not much room to shoot
right now
why are you focusing on the machine gun
when there's a tank
that's upstream the machine gun's
usually attached to a tank
the machine gun wasn't doing any damage
not yet
oh i see him trying to cross
uh does anybody have any words of
encouragement um
try your best okay he's moving in front
he's moving in front of me
all right there's one down there's one
down
one on my slight right i think still
there's one
right here that i can hear him over the
hill and shooting he's pushing up
he's pushing up standby
i got his cannon breech charge over the
top boys
don't charge over the top don't do it
you'll hurt yourself
over at the top i got his engine you're
mine
take every one of them you can with you
oh my god
he's a madman we can't take him anywhere
there's so many
over there wait here come on damn don't
make eye contact with him don't make it
awkward
he's down all right good shot can you
drag that roadblock out of the way he's
he's blocking my fatal funnel here
we got a we got a big boy on the other
side of the wall here he's looking in
window shopping no no
don't look at the windows he's coming in
he's coming in the back door
side ham you got that side we're
rotating
him okay no they're pushing him
yeah it's just uh you know this guy's
freaking me out here it's kind of you
know voyeuristic
hey stick when's that mouse arriving uh
i'm at in the factory
uh i'm moving past the pipes right now
damn your helpers down i can cover you
if you need to fall back
i don't need to pull it back but i need
someone to
i need some how to kill this guy okay
well i don't have a turret or height so
i'm not sure i can help you
gentlemen i am pushing he's backing up
ready to assist
me but i have words sir this is our
factory we make things here
and we have a patent and you're not
allowed to be here private property
please he's pushing he's not listening
to me he's not
i got him he shot uh
gentlemen get him good hands
where was that from vic are you good
back there this is not this is not good
i am so happy to see reinforcements
there's a tank right in front of me
behind this corpse
oh my god those reinforcements almost
he's right there he's aiming to the
right i'm stuck i'm stuck i'm stuck
don't get me back in this fight hitting
him
thank you so much tracks i just need to
push a little bit more
i gotta scan bro completely
come in here everything's gone absolute
hell
duck and cover duck and cover
where is the tank i don't know what are
you what do you do you don't know where
it is you're shooting it
movement in front of me oh that's that's
not the cookie i want to see
put that right through there there he
goes right he's the right
of the oil tanks copy that it's gonna
hold my little corner right here is
there another wave of reinforcements
because we're gonna need everything
i'm here okay there is something too
close right ham said
down by the tanks
it's a it's a centurion he's in the
middle of those tanks i'll mark him i'm
looking at the middle of the old tanks
excuse me oh you have three mouses here
to help you
something over here
but i don't see it right there it's
pushing
no we're at the end check out the engine
how did we lose a mouse i must admit him
oh you invented him that's good
hi hi bo can we go to bravo
you can come out i've been stuck in this
place yeah let's go to bravo for many of
years
let's go to bravo no let's go to bravo i
just don't want to be at the a factory
anymore
what what what what i see it
uh it appears dead the mouse killed it
oh but that one over there is not and he
took my barrel
i dare you he looks really mean
oh thank you so much i appreciate this
can you help me repair
one flick out to your right he's got a
side shot on you no
bearing 300 how dare you if you want an
angle i can take one in front of you
the other mouse got him we're good okay
let's move actually it works really well
now drive forward stick drive forward i
i don't i can't
oh he's hurt yesterday i'm i'm helping
the support repair oh no
we're going to bravo for ice cream
oh there's ice cream there is i figured
that motivate you
oh my god we're going no there we go i'm
going to move
your speed you ever see a mouse got shot
front
oh what do you see where that okay that
probably came from there
no you're driving too fast you said ice
cream
you said ice cream there's something in
the tunnel right here to the right i
think
my goodness you said
you were destroying the world right now
is there anybody in there no it's not
well that's strange does that mean that
we still get ice cream it means that
he's probably further down here
yes there's ice cream at charlie now
they moved it we were too late
what we have to drive the charlotte
something just popped smoke next to us
hello danger damn i feel like he's lying
to me
i i'm confused i'm checking to make sure
nothing's in the little
holes in the walls for us he keeps
saying there's ice cream places and then
he
changes where the ice cream is i just
need
him i just need to move a little faster
though
asking now you're calling me fat no i
just called you slow
he's trying i have the body of an
olympic swimmer okay
what i don't know how to respond to that
a whale okay well he said that
not me just remember that what it's true
he is so mean think in front of me
it's the truth uh gunner can't breach
oh i gotta get speed he's moving he's
moving is the centurion i'm trying him
i'm trying
wrecked oh balls wait that's a heavy
tank that can't be right
was it before it was a centurion i think
five
uh that's right one ah there you are
let's finish this properly yep he has a
kangaroo
can't confirm he has a kangaroo
i just got sean the right okay he's down
rotating
do you see what it was this is why you
don't need them
i got the wiggles i broke out into the
wiggles exactly you leave the mouse
behind and you and you get the wiggles
this is exactly what you deserve i just
break out into random wiggling
no that's what you deserve you left the
mouse behind i'm not excited i'm sorry
where's the disco music
i think it's because the uh the barrel
is touching a dead object or it's close
enough to it where it's trying to
computer stuff computer stuff that's my
explanation
computer stuff you require assistance
sir
uh standby one down you got two more
marks move towards you
oh i see that i've also broken out with
the wiggles again so uh
let me change positions hold on
my little meeting dance jello wiggle
doctor
no no no oh gosh okay hi i'll just move
positions
i'll just go here i promise if you stop
you will not have the wiggles
one russian day 100 000 please
what kind of medical bill is that
average medical bill
every time you get near me i get nervous
look at my poor tank
look i'm not wiggling now drive closer
to me park right where you were
i'm gonna get all nervous watch wait now
yeah see
why don't you two go rush up help him
i'm going to cover a make sure to push
back out
no stop making me wiggle stop the
wiggles
well then you stop being shy i'm not shy
uh jim there's gonna be some pushing
from over there
okay sorry i was distracted by your
willingness that don't you'd make this
weird
and i yes i start wiggling more listen
you got flustered
it's normal reaction
i don't know how i'm supposed to shoot
something right now do you see this
let's go help them yeah oh there's a
tank there
where's tank communicating imagine
bumping a person in their butt
what can i get a repeat of that last
transmission
imagine bumping a person in their butt
when they're trying to shoot somebody
i don't need to that's what i did stick
where is it
oh there's one here oh okay okay push
back push back that way jim
all right here go ahead excuse me
yeah they're pushing for me now
we're trying to get over there help
revenge time
this is the worst right in front of me
right in front of me
he's gonna come over the top of me
possibly all right this is wild
literally literally oh my gosh i'm
watching my doom
i didn't do anything yeah thank you okay
i'll push up
does he have a friend you think yes he
does okay i can't no he doesn't
ignore those carcasses that's not funny
i didn't mean it take no no there is a
friend there's a friend close right
close right okay
behind us behind us behind us
i can't spin fast enough oh no i fell
run away why did you do that
oh my gosh something bought me and i
went my booty in there
this is so bad this is so bad don't do
that
i don't know what else to do
i i'm shooting everywhere how's it going
down there bo
panic shooting right in front of you
another one yeah there's my barrel's
broken him i
they got me i am completely flustered
right now
they got the track this is no
no what is happening
wow they're rushed they're fighting to
get in the door
it's black friday
[Laughter]
it's bo it's a bow uh it's about monday
there's a tank director in front of me
he's down i shot you okay jim
uh just put my track back on well i have
to jump on a point we are triple capped
out here you worry about
everything is fine there's nothing to
worry about for the moment
you're just like screaming your head off
you're like no i was not screaming my
head i'll scream my head off earlier
when there was a
task force trying to breach the door on
me
fbi open up yeah basically but they
weren't the fbi
dbi tank bureau of investigation uh
something drop smoke over there
that was me okay thank you uh can
somebody reach
there you go somebody's almost today
yeah drop stick it was a long journey
we're proud of you i'm not gonna make it
before the game runs out
no you will you will no overdrive
uh how about that bomb
i don't know what i just watched in
front of me it was terrifying that was
cool to watch
the bomb exploded above you and then you
detonated getting shot there's a tank on
my sorry
yep we're on our way it's fine
he's pushing me now he's attempting to
push me
raise him what's race
i don't this is i don't know why this is
working you can't show me apparently
there you go
yeah you're doing great oh he's pushed
me off the point that's what he's done
no no no no no no can't let him do that
i can't even do that i can't do anything
you gotta stay oh no we're good
please don't put the game in my hands
please i i just had a horrible fun
fumble in the first quarter
uh well bud you better not butt bundle
again
uh no the butt fumble what fumble
please don't i don't want to be mark
sanchez please
all right here we go no
i gotta go through the door i gotta get
an a where is he
is he not here behind me
there we go fight me uh him
i'm sorry i'm dealing with some problems
here okay i'm just letting you know he's
right there
we're facing each other off they're on
beat commander gunner no you can't
do that zigzagging i have a
you just gotta keep b i i'm losing b
two bam you gotta keep b
you put all that pressure on stick now
you have to hold b
hold b i'm hearing a lot of high-pitched
excuses
i don't think we're doing it buddy
you're the one with mr sassy pants okay
it's official disrespectful did you just
read off the serial number
i read his name because that's what it
is
sexy blf is on the jets
you are mr sassypants
you are giving me impossible tasks
can we go around the room and say what
we like about each other
[Music]
you