there's something hiding in here
something hiding Sheridan oh wait you're
okay hold on I went over here to help
you
well I went over here to meet up with
you oh that's awkward we should uh plan
better yeah we should really coordinate
our movements
there's a lot of big tanks here I'd be
very careful
well I mean
hi oh my gosh your little eyes run for
your life it's it's not safe here it's
not safe here what about over there and
it's not safe anywhere over by that
thing
I can get I tried to warn you sir that
was from a different direction I said it
wasn't safe here like just in general
oh the general advisory to run away
that's a big tank
I'm looking for it
what's the name 103 you can't really
misplace those
you'd be surprised if I just stop while
I filled the ground move
um I found t-32 glass of water nice
c32's done where's the 103. I don't know
somewhere back there
see I told you you could lose it who's
over here
hi okay I can't reach on him I found him
I found him that's a big gun
okay sir can you just give up that'd be
really helpful
don't just drive away you're
embarrassing me you're making me look
bad in front of my friends please
those are bombs Landing no idea where
those went yeah shuttle next to me those
were
you gotta be more careful you please
I need assistance get over here
stop running you're making me look bad
you
there's no he's down he's down I was
wondering if he was going to the point
to repair himself yeah I think he just
wanted to make me look even worse that's
what he was doing foreign
make sure we're not being
you know that that make sure no my heat
didn't do anything
off the front armor and went up into the
turret and failed me twice it hit twice
on the front and failed me
that is a big scary tank right there
really loader turn drive on him he's got
a friend behind him
right behind him all right first one's
out I'm gonna try and jump up and get
him very good very good that's what I
think it is
driver loader on him got the radiator
he's transfer no don't turn don't turn
don't turn don't turn
no storms keep driving keep driving keep
driving don't worry he doesn't know what
I am no yeah
I'm trying to get through his roof here
murder oh my goodness okay let's spread
out shall we this is the scene of a
crime that was scattered crime the cops
are gonna come crime of failure I think
this is what that was
hey he ended up dead
yeah I just don't want that means
it's counted right there on the inside
of this building yep EDR I'm gonna see
if I get a shot hold on I'm being
playing regard I think I got something
right here on my mark he was fired again
I'm gonna see if I get a shot okay
I I know I don't have a shot fuel tank
he's still able to
he's burning he's burning push push push
for the transmission he's gone he's gone
good job oh it's too late you're left or
right right down the road
fan camera bad okay
eyeshadow yeah I do I don't want to be
here that's that's what I want to do
there's a t114 somewhere too the bombs
are here the bombs are here
I'm gonna drop my bombs right here on
this guy
works for me pull up pull up there we go
it was butter that's an SM
that's a big Target you got plain high
diving on you bow oh Shadow's trying to
flatter me alert okay I got one more
bomb
s no you're far away contact right
contact I don't see it I see it I see it
mom is up
I see it I'm sorry if that's too close
you good
you got him nice all right I'm bugging
out I got something on my six
trying to get on him it's all good I'm
gonna do a fancy meter for you okay
it's called pulling up I'm gonna drag
him for you that's bad I'm dragging him
for you you can catch him in the turn
catch him in the turn directly yeah see
that right in front that's all yours I
saw it like a half second too late okay
I didn't drop his bombs thankfully
two tanks two tanks here alert
air defense active
compromise soon be as compromised B is
compromised I found a helicopter
what I found helicopter
well um
should I make friends
you can try and make contact but they're
notoriously hostile
glasses mean that was mean I feel really
bad about that one oh my goodness it
just yeah he just looked at me like no
there's a tank crossing right
there driver track he can still shoot
another tank on him
okay
I can't see a second with this one
smoked I'm completely blind that's an
m103 that hit me another one to the left
of him
you guys still upping the gun yeah oh I
did not think the m103 is still alive
I'm gonna try to back out the flank if I
can floater
I got a fire
you should uh tell him that he's lit
well he's dead that was a bad joke
yeah there you go see yeah
oh sorry you're uh your back up your
flanker is um bad at driving it's gone
as well
is there any more over here
I don't know probably probably thanks
that's
let me stick my face out the hole and
see what happens
I stuck my face out the hole
we good on Charlie
uh I don't know probably possibly all
right let me take a look outside hello
you scared me puzzle flash right here
same thing oh no I I yeah I have no idea
okay you made me jump again
I was reacting whatever Jim was
dim's killed it let's move towards uh
the Bravo point if he's gonna wrap that
up yeah I think it's time for Sweet Air
I'll join you
all right I will cover the uh thin skin
Vehicles the enemy team does not expect
the Airborne brigaden
well they could here we go nope oh
uh sorry no that's fine I I expected you
to clear that I did too uh Jim just died
behind us by the way yeah there may be a
t-32 that maybe uh closing on your six
be careful we're fine he's nowhere here
I hope he does that sometimes you know
he just jokes around oh you think he's
making a joke about the t32 oh no
they're dying I don't see a t-32
that's because you know it's it's hidden
t-32 is the ultimate American stealth
tank
hey Jim right there yeah 103. where was
the t-32
he was he should be if you're going back
south you should be to your direct right
around that building if I'm looking at
the map correctly so he made the trolley
or is he still on their side
he may still be there be careful please
be careful no is that left he's full of
slapped he's exact left
hi you killed my friend prepare to die
no that was bad he learned that his
machine gun is my enemy
oh
I'm now down a power and he he has all
the power
no no no no don't worry don't do that
don't do that stop he stopped nope
I'm running away he's tracked it's gone
you got him magic is what that was that
was time delayed release his feet
slowly eat away at the tank that's what
that was slowly Burns its way through
I'm repairing my feelings oh yeah
certainly I just realized I just uh
Shadow I just realized I just drove
through the cap and like yeah yeah it's
it's a hurry it's it's right there
oh
I can maybe assist
I just have no visual
you might have to be there
all right can you get another mark on
them before
he's on fire okay uh Jim should have a
good flank on him maybe
burn down he burned down all right let's
wrap up this point move the Bravo boys
my ties
let me slide into your uh
you like it when I backed it up on you
please get your booty out of my face no
madam
you like it
I mean
you got a little that leopard's looking
as like you're a shame that that leopard
wants nothing to do with this it's like
I don't know those two that that leopard
is jealous that we're all like
zippity-doo-dah and the leopard's just
like yeah whatever all business no play
Zippity doodle was this Mary Poppins
right looks clear enough I'm pushing
full forward towards BNA okay
my feelings
where was that from
what I don't know
right there on that hit right there
there's a little one
Mark right there
he's down I still don't see him it's a
Char 25 nice
all right
hi my transmission engine ate all those
yeah just just care careful careful
there
careful before we become a Target yeah
of things like bombs look at a look at
look at the map and look at a right now
it's covered in red oh my goodness yeah
but it's all red that used to be there
oh well we should probably what
does it feels like an elephant sticking
your snout through the bushes shouldn't
stormling be in front because I was also
going to say that large
well you know if you guys wanted me to
be up front you could have positioned
yourselves as such here go ahead no I'm
gonna flank right and clear this
intersection for you okay you are good
to cross sir
I don't remember what he looked like
only that he was angry he's here and
he's angry
yeah I think that's his permanent
existence my Barrel exploded that's all
you I got his Gunner and his loader oh
he's got two he's got friends friends
they're they have friends he's social he
don't have friends back up back up back
up back out back out
now shot on my hot mess over here yeah I
see that
um if they push through the smoke maybe
I can help hey look Shadow I made a
blunderbuss
I'm a pirate
yeah like my new weapon Target on damage
done no Shadow has no life left in them
oh
that Amex terms of your front right over
there can you kill one you're right
you're close right you're close right on
the core of the building he's scouted
close right here I can't help you but
he's scouted
hate oh my goodness why do we even bring
tanks
I can be helpful except against that you
have a friend Paul your name War Daddy
on any trans shoot down planes now
you're just getting carried away with
that thing yeah now you're showing off
well it's not like I'm gonna hit
anything yeah you know that can't be
anti-air
hey I've accidentally hit a plane before
accidentally was it friendly
it was not friendly as a matter of fact
it was however trying to Ram me so uh
Charlie I guess or
I don't know let me see your face
Jim did you put a face on he's winning
the face competition today no no I'm in
try hard mode look at that
uh they're on Charlie yeah that's
adorable we should run
oh fine
okay I'm leaving goodbye it makes that
call out casually
I know he's angering it
well I mean it can't pause
right your front okay oh I'm gonna eat
this for you right here close
don't
say that I'm feeling miserably over here
oh my God I'm doing things to him
not good things
Charlie we're the big Winners it's
running around me it's an A8 we're
playing oh bring around the rosie we are
but I stopped and see if he's gonna
he's running he's running he's running
let's make a break for it never mind
he's gone he blew up
nice Justice was served
that's all I have I'll try to make
something cooler to happen but that's
all I got Justice was served oh oh oh
that that's okay okay I was expecting a
part two to that but that that's fine
that's all that's all I have
well I mean it's better than nothing
um
well uh I guess I'll head back towards
uh
gym
oh no we're fine I fixed myself don't
worry I'm a single independent tank that
doesn't need no uh light armored vehicle
to help it I thought you oh is this your
Gunner I didn't know you need any
repairs
he was complete I was assuming that he
was destroyed and then he got bombed so
I figured that he had it
don't worry I had it under control when
he says he had under control he opened a
bottle of whiskey and just started
drinking if you are garst on right I'm
gonna do it again and where's the court
there we go there's the tiger 2 in the
road pushing
uh Gunner on him if you want to watch a
missile or something
there you go nice job next to him the
thing next to him oh yeah okay got his
can of reach if he wants to missile him
I don't see him anymore
there he goes nice job got him
I'm now out of missile see with teamwork
I mutilate you finish
I think left is not clear
okay I know left is not clear left is
definitely not clear scouted right there
I didn't now guys breach I guess we want
to fire missile I don't have no missiles
no worries
I have magic missiles might be some to
your front right
wow so something there
there's a friendly tiger two people from
there there
oh direct front pushing front pushing
front
I don't see that heavy American heavy
there's two there's two yep
okay I don't know where that just went
storms I'm sorry easy to meet you I'm
gonna try to take his Barrel
okay I don't know where my shoes
T20 further back t29 it's okay right
next to you I know what's happening here
pushing up the other side it's all good
I'm just saying that because it's not
sir can you please put that bear away
it's huge you're making me feel bad
sir please no
no please he's got friends he's got
friends
how did you have friends there's another
one of him he's replicated
oh my gosh please don't look at me with
that big gun sir yeah that's what I feel
like saying but
yeah he's hurting he's all right I'm
hurting
no okay I'm going for it I'm going for
I'm going for it all in all in all in
got me
wow another t34 different t34 yeah
different countries t-34 yes we're gonna
Peak he stepped up to the plate and he's
out
all right I had a bump and threw off my
hand you two be careful over there
I will try no Shenanigans keep your
hands to yourselves
little tricksters I see that's I'm
trying to sneak up on some poor guy
who's being already no no no no no don't
do that don't look at me I'm not real
so there's another thing over to the
right I'm gonna go ahead and just say
hide it yep
okay uh Gunner on him
anybody's interested on a nice
T-Series Russian tank possibly t55
they're uh they're
they're behind me they're behind me oh
they're in the a factory I see it I see
it yep we're not gonna be taking over
we're financially sound
there's another one over here on this
one you know I'm good I'm just not even
gonna
Commander Gunner and him you see him
nice I'm about to go around the corner
go ahead I'll keep knocking on his head
I have I can't see it there's so many
you're fine you're fine I'm Gonna Keep
uh focusing front for now there's
another one
on the back or the front yeah back
okay hang on I'm putting my booty back
up in the air
yeah that's not a smart move I shouldn't
expose myself like that
hey Jim yeah so uh Russian medium tank
not happy
actually be careful on the uh on our
side right here because there's a couple
Angry American Tanks off Yonder okay
hole I'm calling artillery down on this
back side of this Factory we got oh
there's friendlies in there kind of
though yeah
I put the artillery there before they
got there
you can put that in the after action I'm
not gonna have blood on my hands
oh well
that weasel shrine
so uh Jim that he's not moving
from the other side oh yeah
thank you that is a big boy hold on
okay Commander radio or him scouting you
see that Jim
yep I got him okay I'm backing out for
now
nice
be good can we move out of this place
yet
I I don't trust it
hang up okay I mean there's a pile of
bodies behind me and also he's still not
happy he still wants to file grievance
with me let me let me breathe someone by
these concrete pipes is not happy like
right oh yeah he's uh right there I
missed oh hey Jim I found extra strategy
here oh look hi
I shouldn't do that too much because
he's gonna shoot from there you can pull
me through there though if I need to get
out here right yeah but you know you're
also like inviting them to smack you on
the butt maybe but maybe they like that
well hi all right
we need to get rid of this guy if it's
all possible hey big uh m103 m103
understood switching to heat
directing the hill okay somebody hit my
T-Series
dead
I'm gonna push the teeth back I can't
see you
I'm making a run for it smoke is out
charge charge charge charge oh boy
charging I gotta get rid of this t54
that's just making
come here no he's okay he's pushing
towards you guys
oh wait right here right here right here
running around no that's not happy
track right there
go weasel go
tank right there tank right there in the
corner got it done hit this guy hit this
guy reload reload reload I can't see him
I just drove front either shot Jim
corner there
bombs here
we're like I need tiny bomb Think Tank
there transmission's out I have to
repair
I'm stuck in the open Hillary
cabin forever wants it
he's dead I'm even left
sir right there shadow
where when I I'm alive
never mind go you're dead wait no
Jim help me
I don't leave your brothers behind
I'm dead we're back no I see you over
there
you're gonna leopard one
running fast that's not good
oh no that's really bad for us
oh defined really bad that's the
emotional damage alarm
we're all gonna need counseling I can uh
permission to hug you yeah let's just
hold each other it's when they find our
scarred remains this is two two tanks
nestling together
weasel no I'll head Pat you
where he maybe will save us
we're being nuked by the British how
could they
where is he didn't we tell them that
we're he's over there we have time
wait where is it uh it's a bearing it's
behind you
it's friendly right behind you go to
your right I see I see they can't nuke
us they're still friendlies on the field
they don't care we're you got quite a
little damage pushing uh from there
Jim let's go dive our boots on
fair enough
you know in 20 years they're gonna be
saying let's start for skinny jeans on
that's gonna be the new thing
one of them
thank you I'm dropping already on that
all right Jim I'd rather die to the
enemy than some friendlies
I'm gonna
walk bait right there right there driver
loader
this guy no then what
yeah literally he has a nuke symbol next
to him yeah I know I know no there's
another tank over here honestly see uh
he's up there is it out
he's overhead he's overhead
please no
have mercy oh dear
bo uh I just want to let you know uh
I've always loved you Jim hold me I
don't know where it is I don't know
where it is
oh
hey best Squad
[Music]