attack of the pumas
it's one down the last thing you
expected was a giant american armor car
to stare him down like i own these
streets
basically the american imitation of him
i'm not backing away because i don't
have arm or anything i'm just doing it
because i plain yeah bombs that's why
i'm doing it
wow that was pretty lucky my drivetrain
broke again
of course this uh
can i make a red bull joke
is that too soon
i i don't know you're gonna have to
inform me what what kind of uh
there's two of them actually there's a
light tank to the boat
you got him
it's terms do you like this
not really oh look at that big beast
i got the gun around that's yours take
them
guys work we're teamwork here
yeah see my front tires wave at you
oh so seductively
yeah they're they're doing the the
wiggles i shouldn't let the look and see
that he's too young
his eyes he's seen he's seen so much i
don't know which way to face like i feel
like yeah face the way the look is fired
he's trying to shoot through the bus
oh poor little guy here let me help him
oh no and there he goes
how did he shoot your bus
what was he shooting at
nothing okay he was trying to get
through bus no he's trying to get
through stairs should we just leave him
be probably i think he needs to go on
this adventure on his own this is like a
walkabout for locusts getting already by
the way yeah we need to drive fast watch
the right i don't see anything
me reversing is about your speed yeah
are you making fun of how slow i am no
yes you are
i would never do such a thing yeah
something just fired at the sherman
do i need to spin around
no it's too late for him
you just caught on fire and exploded
yeah
the um
a kv-1 is now on the outskirts of the a
point to the south of it
okay i can push that i i am on the
outskirts of the airport to the south of
it
no eyes no eyes this melee could do the
fire and smoke but i'll find them soon
oh there something that's a panther
three
no another one on my mark scouted
i can't pin him very well inside the
building to the north of that panther
three was the last one location for the
kv one mark right there oh no he's right
there he's right there staring at me
okay i don't know which one you're gonna
kill but you gotta kill one of them
can you hold him there
yeah yeah
do what you got to do um
let's go i just counted something else i
don't know what to do here
hi buddy
i killed the kv-1 now it's my time to
die
no i killed bo
what
why why did i win the engagement against
the panther 3m and
congratulations you used up a year's
worth of luck
we got things crossing
first one's down tank's not crossing i
am not
fast and nimble enough to go forward and
backwards and take shots like that
i am
we'll go out there a little stuart and
see what we can find
no thank you
i'll do it again
i look like a boulder anyway
oh crap
uh there's one right there sc-96
that was the t-20 that has killed you
i just missed my shot we're falling
apart here it's coming around the corner
heads up i just shot a pole
hi how are you doing you want to drop
this
yeah i got your nose come back here
i'll be here all week
don't you machine gun me
i think he's angry that's who's saying
six is uh still there fighting got the
driver here we go
you are doing work up there big hits
no more
sadness can't move come on car
yeah i got one behind here scouted
stay alive is that alive sure yeah it
was alive
okay movement here moving here
just i i hope that we have anti-air
coming in soon
wait what this is fell over
sc 122 on that mark
is that a thing i'm hearing lots of
calls
oh that's a big boy what's the big boy
oh teach wait you are still here yep
over here on that marker no you drive on
my life
yeah uh little one pushing in front of
me little one push in front of me okay i
swear jim you're right
oh my goodness i got the engine oh no he
smited you yeah i did i was afraid of
this he had some friends he also has a
they beat the stewart meta by bringing
their own stewards
i got the driver gunner too thank you
i'll work on it he's down thank you
teach weight is still to my hard right i
cannot get him out of that uh i am
loaded i believe her shot there may be
more behind there keep in mind i don't
like that idea i don't like that i can't
see very well from my spot can i just
say no
hold on t28 you home hold on be careful
it's fine it's fine this is my spot i
own the spot
you own something t28 come on play a
timeshare maybe he's he's not here him i
shot him i didn't do it i can't do
anything sorry he is upsetting spaghetti
you have a sherman
uh-huh where'd you find a sherman at
this time of the day i i
i have some good friends behind me
behind me behind me they're rushing
barnacles uh commander machine gunner
one scouted another one running right
i'll take him he's leaving
get the other one get the other one i
can't he's leaving he's just driving off
him uh
uh he's gonna shoot somebody just left
us
somehow the c20 hasn't pushed us i will
hold the right side you hold the left
side you sure about that i'll take a
change of scenery
oh hello stewart
that bounced okay that's the sad
oh party strike me okay great on him
oh good to hear he says he says okay
this is embarrassing i'm having problems
with stuart
um
he said he said okay hi okay good uh hey
jim
yeah hi so if i was to put some off-road
parts on this vehicle what would you do
first i would recommend a high clearance
off-road bumper a winch
um a high lift jack oh yeah some better
tires i would say three inch lift uh
depending on kind of what you see you
know you don't want like you don't want
to aggravate like some of the angles on
your drivetrain
um i highly recommend a uh aftermarket
off-road fridge a rooftop tent
he's just you think we have the budget
for an off-road tent
uh yeah i mean you know i i mean i won
mine in a raft for 60 bucks you know i
don't know what's stopping you from
doing the same but um
rng yeah
pretty much here
ham it's really quiet i think we can
push today
uh
negative
be advised there are some bt sevens that
are just you know they're they're uh
they're sitting on some grassy knolls
cam you have a front slope i have a
front curve
get that slope in there
careful there's no till it's no it's
fine it's just a matilda
hi is he in that tent where is he at
he's got start
okay i shot him
what's that range by the way uh
too far for you
aiming left
hold on there he is he's down oh my god
it's a very flat shooting gun they're on
a roger here let me push first i have
the armor the slope
curves are better in slopes
that is
i mean there's this there i got those
stuart where's the other one
i don't know
okay hold on something else is over here
though
i want something just fire from behind
here i got target there rank uh
i'm busy
shoot it please kill it please kill it
you just got shot from front it's behind
us
no
where
i don't know i don't know either that's
why i'm backing up right now right in
front of me but i don't see it
it's uh get away from me okay nice shot
he's got fire from the right
i lost the track one scouting there
behind that body please kill it please
kill it sc-122 yep he's down oh my god
you're welcome why are we still alive i
magic
oh god there's russian bomber inbound do
you believe in miracles cause i hope you
do can you repair my uh something you
think i can okay i can repair you hold
on
i don't know where to look though
what do you mean you have the 50 cal
no i don't my commander's dead okay get
a new commander
but
i have not three crew members is jim now
like shopping online catalogs looking at
parts of this thing yeah i am actually
hey i'm wondering hey what kind of tires
are running without lifting that thing
uh the rubber ones uh okay but like what
size i think they're round deep dish
chicago style lord my good lord yeah
okay you know what i'm gonna just say
three
two inch left oh my gosh
too much action
there's contact over there somewhere
roger i'm pushing to engage
i think there's something still over
there i'm gonna drop party behind it
hold on that shit's friendly
uh no there's just there's something
back there yeah right the panther two
seats fighting i think this guy's gonna
be able to heard it i'll be honest i
dropped already further back so i don't
actually smack him there's something is
further back it's moving left yeah i see
it moving left yep
i'm gonna try to grow those rocks
he just died to it no wait he killed
something he got it that's the same six
down there is still something else
though i'm driving into my own arty
crap
italians are here i see the mark i can't
see there he is
it's armored car av something
there's a 41. yeah there can only be one
true off road on this map i knew i was
gonna say 43 and it wasn't a 43.
it's one of the two
i have 50 chance of guessing right now
we've gotten wrong 50 50 or good odds
i think she's a very
lovable vehicle
she uh
she's tall
and she's
i'm on fire
yeah better than that it's a great it's
a great car let me expect her for this
thing
yeah
um look now i'm even going faster yeah i
i really think you should put that fire
out i should right i think
thrust also disclaimer if anyone likes
to off-road i highly recommend you put a
fire extinguisher in your off-road
vehicle
i got a plane on me him that's friendly
there's a dauntless apparently that was
about to
he had to say planning to worry about
him he's good
and what do you got running up there
get it
i got the engine on that's yours i got a
loader radiator it's still it's still
got gunner
okay i uh use the bigger cannon that's
on my vehicle
to finish him
we have the same side gun no we don't
don't you dare say that what does your
fans get
57 mil oh boy they're going to break out
the rulers and the two men's bathrooms
that's 20 whole millimeters bigger son
for 37 57 potato potato are we going to
shoot down to a we're going to clear up
here first then push day i think
here let me save you from that thing
driver loader you didn't
why it's all right you're in my way
right now
i'm going to murder you that's what i'm
going to do
why did you do that i'm trying to stay
live here
first of all
i got his periscope it's fine
you better murder him
like that there you go good job i think
we're clear
you think we're clear
yeah
yeah now you now you've done it that's
your thesis i'm being so blind you
brought embarrassment to the family
he was straight in front of me i don't
know what to do no shame for shame
oh gosh armored car life sark in the
forehound in it together
it's gonna sit right here i hope i can
fire over this there's a hitbox
there's an s57 who may be trying to
flank you guys yeah there's a sark all
over it he's doing great work he's a
good job
i'm gonna trust him while i watch the
front
i'm running towards a
is there anything else happening
there's things on the other side i think
also what driving is hard
bo uh danger rain is happening i don't
like it overnight danger rain is right
yeah something's gone to your lower
right oh no i don't want to die there's
there's a star
i got you
mr stark i apologize that sark is a hero
yeah he is give him one of our finest
but what are you what are you doing yeah
you have trouble neutral steer
i am
i can't do that
you always seem to run into me in the
weirdest times oh it's not weird i
thought we were going to a now you're
going over here you're picking fights
there's something in front of you no
stop look forward
what in the world
now he's gonna shoot me look what you've
done him forward and left there's
i got his gunner okay uh scout is
something to your right
thank you for killing him good shot good
shot through the wall right there i'll
break it down for you so you can see it
whoa god do not do that
well now you can see him
well now he's gonna see up he doesn't
see me i'll shoot him shoot him shoot
him i don't want to go knock down that
wall too
oh my goodness
him
you have to kill him you ready what i
like how you knock on the wall like five
goes the wall
that's all yours
that didn't work well did it i got it i
got shot front
wait wait that was
no it starts saying hello oh i see it oh
wait no that's alright no that's the
start that's friendliness i'm sorry
that got me earlier this is a revenge
good ham oh hello i'm just in there okay
can we collapse town this is a terrible
place to be i don't i don't
i don't like the a factory today i want
to get out of here someone dropped the
smoke what's actually a refinery today
they closed down for uh
it's the it's the egg crying factory
that's what it is
we'll be fine over here i promise we get
some speed there's a plane coming in
there might go faster
ham that's that's uh you drove into
something there
oh yeah you're driving too good either
you know what
that's just because four wheels you
can't seem to drive straight oh my god
eight wheels i have eight
oh my goodness
potato
i mean we got artillery dropping i'm not
gonna stop for anything yeah there's a
reason why they called the slow but
deadly that yeah they just crashed i'm
just gonna keep moving
target uh marked over here on this side
i'm not worried about the duck from be
honest no there's two things marked over
here
it's got it one kv one i gotta give you
one here
get it get away
we can slay him what the heck this gun's
really good i promise oh my gosh i'm
sorry back into the m3 i am i'm sorry i
really hit me in the back here in front
of me i can't move anywhere i i love how
we're all just kidding i'm driving here
shoot it
this is how we lose
my engine how many hits is he gonna take
help you get to center what a monster
don't worry about it i am worried about
it maybe target to the front right
because there's a smoke stack all right
hang on three two yeah i can't wait
until you do
i i'm out i'm out
okay let's get out of here this event i
got shot from right
target scouted all right gunner and
cannon breach on him uh what is this
what is it that's the t-50
and this round goes through like butter
as i drove into a wall because i
get moving you big point every minute
it's a big vehicle look at my tires this
is much look this is me turning this way
this is full turning oh we're good
bye friends i'm good
hey all right now that we're alive hey
boy my drive train went out
i got a question about that vehicle real
quick uh what what what size tires can
you run without a lift on that thing
eleventy billion eleventy billion okay
uh bf goodrich or uh you know uh
goodyear
uh always goodyear okay i'm gonna i'm
gonna go find an extra uh excuse me i'm
gonna go find a uh 4x4 group on that on
facebook and i'm gonna ask that question
i'm gonna see what they say they're
gonna uh please don't post my address
because i'll get
i'll get attacked
you'll get centered i'm leaving
goodbye where do you think they are
besides uh fighting for their lives in
that top spawn
pick your question
fighting for their lives
yeah you see that like blue embargo
happening i do i do and that's kind of
glad we're kind of doing like an about
face to kind of get more back in the
center of the map
we're in patrol we're security
don't worry about it okay all right all
right you know ham every time you say
don't worry about it we worry about it
well why
because like things go bad you don't
trust me that i can't handle whatever
the situation damn it's not that i don't
trust you it's just that like you say
like it's the opposite thing of what you
should say also like oh i like how we
all hit all these
ham like we gotta we gotta
that's what i'm doing hold on why don't
you trust me i'm driving off the sunset
no it's because like some of the like
some of the matches we've had you've
said
trust me and then we end up like crying
and like you know licking our wounds
sometimes spooning i i open up another
beer wait horsefull spooning
i i need some clarification on that
danger cuddles we somehow end up
spooning or spooning
yeah when you put one plane on top
another plane i'm going to call that
force spooning from now on
you know you know you guys may be
spooning but you know i'm the one
getting forked
here can open
as you can over
there's a whole family of them up there
what i probably should have shot the one
behind first because now he's
yeah they're alerted
uh puma might scott mark right there
horde can you drop already on that mark
there's there's things there
yes i did
i do not have a lot of mobility in the
fresh powder
i'm closed in the distance i'm moving a
amazing six month that he shot me
oh i got shot twice
nothing to see here boys
just pass it on through i joined your
little
they're chasing me they're chasing me
they're chasing me
oh mark right there mark right there
i'm really far away that's fine
i'll survive
i'm just anchoring the other team that's
all yeah uh ro roll roll to seduce roll
to seduce i'm just rolling down the hill
now
what does that mean uh dungeon master
dnd
okay i'm gonna crash here start
repairing
40 seconds ish um
to my right i'm gonna give another scout
mark you ready hold on i'm clearing this
hill i'll be able to get some over
target scouting
you go to here ham or i'm going to go
i'm going to go rescue bro
yes go i don't think there's any
rescuing me from this hell i've put
myself into
there's three marks on top
they're all around me there's there's a
dicker max right there oh i see his
barrel
i'm just so no no you don't see me no no
no i'm not here got my gunner oh i got
my gunner they have they have
reinforcements
[Music]
you