due to recent changes in the a factory
structure we are closing down facilities
for today today we will take you on a
guided tour of our extra section the bee
Factory
do not worry because B comes after a it
is not second to the quality of the a
factory the B Factory is the toughest of
qualities compared to the a factory I
think top tier broken stick
we may have to reboot Jim
is that an option
sometimes you have to make decisions in
life to decide if you're a monster or
not and I I I'm struggling with this one
he's so small and adorable
but if he shoots at me
I'm gonna have to do it
no no don't come over here I'm not your
mama
please the team's gonna see you and
they're gonna hurt you
just go back in the corner go back in
the corner you're not harping it you'll
be my secret no I'm not harboring
anything just go over here sit behind
the boxes and be safe little one damn it
sounds like he's harboring an enemy
doesn't it I'm not harboring anything he
and he might be a wait a minute excuse
me uh sir is a uh tips it
there's nothing to see here
you probably call security and report
that there is a Lost Child on the
battlefield
Mama's here
I need a shot
got him
no don't he turned on me he turned on me
that is a Rowdy child simmer
please I don't want to do this
don't hear just sit you have to do it
but I'll sit behind me like that
I almost crushed him you have to do it
or I'll do it oh my gosh Jim do not
judge what's happening here no either
you do it you are as small as child as
he is either you do it or I do it
I will not have his blood in my hands
you are a monster now you go in the
corner
there you're in timeout no
I said like kill me boom time out let go
of me let go anytime out right now you
can't do this to me yes I can you can't
do this to me yes you're going in the
corner no stick boy is the reason why
you don't give High br's children there
just sit there and think about what you
did
I'll be back for you in five minutes
if something happens to me I'm sorry
I love how he's just there he's accepted
it
princess I have come to save you from
the evil enemy
where are you Jim are we really an
improvement
I guess
also look out for t80s oh
where is it is it your right or is it to
your left I don't know right there right
there I'm having a rookie moment well
that was a little cleric
do you have a TV friend
I don't know you're not sure
get back to me when you figure that out
I'll help you damn I'm gonna be honest
right now you're really not looking to
live up to your night status right now
now see here you
peasant well now you're a peasant
peasant
I am one of the most Brad Knights of the
army
I'm not saving anything
named after a twig
sticky got that side we'll push back to
gym yep I got this do we have to save we
have friendlies on there I just want to
make sure that we have nobody else
Consulting my family name
if we die in his castle there's no more
family
Forest
I'm throwing the white glove at you the
white glove you slap him with it oh you
challenge me to a duel
I'd like to see you try
snap you like the name you are
Mia boy who is a twig wow this is
getting personal stick it boy stick up
boy I will
break you
child
I will not take this I will not take
this from somebody who can't even just
turn their left from the right now see
here
I'm gonna push through this just make
sure that there's no enemies in it by uh
Parish I perish
uh we have a couple dead friendlies over
here hang on to the sides of the rock so
I'm concerned what happened to them
again I need assistance
come back to you
keep your head down oh I'm leaking fire
where's it coming from
right here
[Music]
unsure of the second one oh my gosh what
in the world
I'm gonna be honest it's behind us
location compromise oh gosh
I needed you to help me and you didn't
help me on top of Jim it's on top of Jim
he cannot penetrate myself
this is a quite the Sprint to try and
not save you because you just perished
we just both took each other's tracks
I I hope to reload I'm gonna take your
yeah we're gonna take that first
and then I'm gonna come down here and
I'm gonna hurt you
it's nothing personal you're just a t80
it's my job
damn
yes
I think an important lesson has been
learned here today the t80s are slowly
getting to me we're on the way back
no no worries I'm just slowly
psychologically breaking because of them
we um we shouldn't fight Jim no I think
the the biggest lesson here is that you
are a terrible Knight you are not
capable of saving the princess because
you cannot save me
the princess is grander than I am
you are not worthy
actually I want to make a height to your
T-shirt call it hurts so good it hurts
so good yeah 11-7 Hurts So Good
we don't even have time to have a
personality we're just like take left
direct directions
left upside down up down mayonnaise I
repeat mayonnaise on the bread Commander
we have T-Series
merging onto the battlefield requesting
direct support you know how hard it's
gonna be to be verbally the whirlpool
win at top tier I don't think uh this is
verbally's neighborhood there's a
contact close he's down nice there's
gonna be probably more to either left or
right okay I'm looking let's go for a
little journey shall we yes I would love
that very much
uh danger should be over the structure
uh I got shot in the back but I got one
in front I am on fire and I need a new
engine to track I'm getting shot front
things are not looking well for me
I'll come back to you never mind do not
do not Advance there is uh I've got a
big problem over here someone has The
High Ground over them on the south side
of uh see oh same with this situation
over here by me
oh never mind Abrams thank you Abrams
always trust in Abrams they're always
there to save the day
poke out a little bit right there you
can machine gun them yep
okay I'm gonna break back up
they are on Charlie so keep eyes up
there I understood
and also close right there
all right uh transmission on him if you
want to flank him
I will do that let me cut in front of
you he drops smoke you can't move he did
um
uh Jim watch your high left though too
I'll try to cover you
where is he let me out in the smoke
right there next to you
yeah let me let me get my feeling stick
out here you're feeling stuck out no
oh there you like that Jim you got him I
got his loader hang on I'm pushing on
the other side what is this thing oh
hello sir you got another one coming in
oh oh goodness we're gonna finish them
and move
I I got hurt
I know there's one right here he's down
Jim I would love to help I can't keep
losing teammates like this where's the
next one
I don't know I got stuck in a rock in my
blade stuck on the hill I Austin Powered
myself
I need your tow rope hold on Jim I have
got a leopard to stop five seconds
three two one that was so embarrassing I
want to help you so badly what's wrong
I'm an idiot that's what's wrong
what'd you do I got stuck oh well you
appear to be unstuck yeah I just wiggled
a lot okay I was having my own mini
freak out so I'm glad I'm glad you got
over your hurdles
I actually have a good show for this
I hit him never mind him with the dart
I knocked on a tree
hi Jim hello
hello oh I'm sorry the tree was in my
way no no worries are you okay you're on
fire no I'm not okay I'm not okay I
should probably fix you I just I'm just
destroying the ecology and ruining my
friends do you have toilet paper you do
I do you always have to be perfect you
never know
oh you see that on the map
no I do not actually we just lost a
friendly in front of us oh there was
there was a runner he's moving he's
moving that away left or right okay left
right here right here you got him
there's two there two there I uh
critical hit fuel tank all right moving
for you
back up or push
t-72 pushing someone t72 pushing someone
well I didn't do anything to him
two on me
I got my gutter I got one I got my
breach I'll hold them for me
just buy yourself time buy yourself time
nope
that's not good oh I was gonna call a
couple targets at 245 but wait a minute
look at the kill field what did I do
what did I do I'll be burned him out Jim
yeah he burned down what I think front
240. thick left right I I do see you and
I will help you I I don't feel Parts I
can't okay I'm failing you twice you see
that thing charging us six gone two
Targets front we're in danger he's
charging us he's Jim nope what hey
you're gone I was taken from there your
body is gone
hello now I'm over here
uh sick just drove off the cliff stick
boy oh is that gonna be an issue
let's join them did you flip over pull
you did not flip over did you our Dozer
blade make us makes us very front heavy
on my way to save you
did you see how smooth that was that was
very smooth could you help me please I
can if there's no tanks pushing down
that hill I'll I'll watch the hill while
you two uh have your uh
just so moment leopard two
yes leopard two moments what is PSA
amiibo
hold on a second you're actually pretty
tall when you're upside down and I can't
grab the top of your track
oh but just use the Dozer blade and like
push me from the side that would work
right
it does it just made it sound a little
weird and it you could you could really
hey they're here leave me there and
don't use me as cover I'm trying to drag
you out the line of fire
oh I'm not in fire
did you not see that disable the t-80 uh
Jim is in the process of trying to get
why are you so heavy we're the same
vehicle
you just got me
I'm going to gym I'm trying to make sure
you guys don't die I've been shot from
the right
oh well that's an issue I'm gonna push
him Jimmy got the other one
okay the other one just hang out
okay stick up stay there and look pretty
I can activate my toes are playable
upside down
can that get you unstuck because I'd be
oh he's pushing my side
he's trying to get angle on somebody
reload
they take out your weapon system he's
down Jim's been shot and on fire
hey similar shoe over here
Jim Jim
it all hurts
what did we learn about diving off a
plate so if I would uh checking what's
underneath them
don't do it with a giant Dozer blade in
front of me I have a robbery to report
he took my blades I can't see anything
Jim can't I had to Ink I'm exposed I
need a new engine I need two new tracks
is he up on the is there two of them or
just one
I think there's tracers coming from here
I think there's two what was that that's
an atgm what one sounded like it was on
there right here
you're too far away you're too far away
I can't do anything Jim I don't have a
hatchet underneath me you two go to your
separate Corners
I'm gonna burn it down some water I
don't know how many hatches on the
bottom of me you need to get closer
while I'm upside down give me closer to
him I'm trying to push him to him
let me give him a fire extinguisher I
got it
I'm trying to help people
okay it burns really bad I only have one
thing of ammo left because everything
burned out that the blast why don't you
put together your shattered turbine
blades and I'll help him first what is
that
they're friendly laughing at us that's a
friendly laughing at me because I am a
birthday cake because I'm a special boy
why can't I fix myself I don't know I
was waiting on you to do that here we go
okay I'm leaving at the friendly
we're gonna die here hold it
wow
[Music]
maneuver kill
good
I can't claim that I'm calling that some
mirror kill no let him know that we
can't claim that
are you upside down it's right here
right here oh my gosh that was epic
double decker mbts oh my gosh can you
get them before he shoots me can you get
him before he shoots me
I'm trying just keep moving me I like
this this is nice right right there you
go we distracted him this was a top tier
strategy
he has no idea what to do right now I
got him you are clutch any chance you
can put me over I'll help you repair uh
let me fix you no worries he did not
expect that
he was like why is there a tank upside
down and then another tank Falls
it broke his brain it was all a part of
our elaborate plan it is
get this to West Point right now the
next group of uh Cadets need to learn
this we are gonna be General you and I
oh gosh Man Down artillery
your help's here Jim
you see any other targets
not yet
don't worry there will be I can promise
you that oh I'm sure I'm sure that I
think they're all coming from a
gonna push that direction
one two but we need to we also lost
speed so they're coming from this
direction as well
things I don't want to do but I have to
do it for the good first Target is right
there
brick light on him his uh Drive trains
out look at us being adults Jim
it should help the same room so we can I
got his track Abrams is on fire I'm
pushing up to him
I don't see anything directly on top of
him can you repair this front right
front right can you cover my left
or something too
there's two down there looking left
Abrams is down he's down I'm pushing up
I'll take the hits right behind you
actually no let's smoke and Retreat I
mean all right retrograde retrograde
fall back fall back reposition falling
back falling back please redeploy please
please
we're having some like US Army
miscommunication that's not a time for
this I'm gonna flank right
we gotta get around them
if at all possible R4 LED right there
it's just like watching this guy
paranoid
can you look watch him
I will just make sure they don't push um
oh God they're pushing they're pushing
they're pushing they're pressing barking
I'm on their side
oh they were pushing me I thought
they're pushing you holy crap oh hello
Russia's here I am panicking under
there's a t80 around every corner that I
try and live by found one right here if
you want to help me all right I'm headed
that way he's aiming towards me
a little faster he's down the work there
is a second one somewhere
there's always a second t80
wait does that mean that there's a
second t80 to the second t80 I'm not see
anything over here yet that would be
the fourth p80 e80 squared how sure are
you
that there's another one like percentage
um
no definitely a passing rate
all right I'm behind you
if you want to cancel B I'm going to
push left and just make sure we're not
being uh flanked yep
I get the feeling we got trouble right
next to us
see those marks of our teammates going
down
I do and oh uh you're left I didn't even
see him he's on the far left corner
there's one pushing Charlie
uh never mind
I'm so glad that worked out as well as
it did every direction I look I just see
tanks
affirmative on B yeah okay see the mark
on the hill
yeah I just got glazed by an atg from
some nerd behind you yeah it's not good
another time oh it's fired at me from
here at all
they're collapsing down to me at Bravo I
I may have to be selfish here and fight
for myself I don't know so please defend
yourself
one zone
good I am not alone here
I hear at gyms as well or a
I'm canceling B
good I need to uh make a little Peaks
noodles here and make sure that that
Batman isn't here to smack me again
there is one that's gonna push from over
here in front of you
understood
I look back and I saw something yeah you
see that
you see the Mark I do not see the target
hold on yeah I just got hit oh gosh
I'm on fire hold on I also got hit
I see your target that one's down all
right there's one here how you write I
think too yeah I think you're right
I'm still Captain Point there's one
behind me towards a
just remember we're surrounded
and you don't have The High Ground every
direction there's a threat
right there you got him thank you
man those things are terrifying even
when you're in neighborhood I just got
shot again
there's no cover in here
I'm just gonna move over here now I hope
it doesn't see me you're trailing fuel
look at that I'm being shot from
my track can you see him no I don't I
cannot I dead there's two of them that's
why I was confused
oh gosh she had The High Ground the
other clerk one was coming from our side
one from their side
that's why no matter wherever I went
there was no cover makes sense now
I was actually like more impressed with
your uh like what just happened to him
future like time traveling centauro just
got the guy next to us right there's a
horrible there's a centauro to the close
right there is a second centauro to the
close left and there are two Abrams on
the other that's that's taro
got I got black sharks
I can't do much about that
I see those targets over there I'm just
gonna push
this is not a good plan
I got k-15 as well but I was able to put
one into the dardo
I really appreciate the diversity of
things I'm being murdered by in the past
five minutes it's a good time right oh
yeah it's the 80s calendar Twos
for a common goal of ruining don't you
love that I message you Jim hey hi tier
be fun yeah yeah see you there totally I
just got in the face my nc25 I deserve
that for that joke
there is no safety anywhere no I see the
Frog foot I must kill frog foot
[Music]