control your flying saucer do you think
I have a CDL does it look like I know
how to drive a truck I mean have you
seen your backside it's round literally
you need a CDL to carry around that dump
truck there's a paner 4 I'm for that
where's the paner 4 around the corner
around the
corner can you lure him in here right
there I bounced good luck with that what
he
bounced oh that's alive right
there wait there oh not anymore I was
looking at those two bodies I realized
that one had tan and green paint and
didn't match the others uh one low I
think sitting right there in there he on
the point
still oh I can see it I can see it
there's two two right there can you hit
him I can I'm looking your direction I
see one firing hit
one oh that was not one that I saw
you're are we good up here
down theill is not good uh we got coming
up here also one I'm taking the one
close slow if I get bar depression get
him get him get him
and you doing all right there's a lot of
exchange fire there no no no it's just
AA it's just AA open face is ridiculous
really at time like this what are you
doing birthday
parties what did you do birthday parties
we do uh sck Dead We
meetings can you do my shot in the face
hold on I need to kill some I don't want
assist this my cab is like
sming I was counting on
you the planes are here well I don't
know if I the plan
boss on this episode of Bose's Big Game
Hunter we sneak up on an M10 in the Wild
Woods of I forgot where we
are thank you 50s I'm a good host of the
show I haven't been drinking at all
anyway we're back on the hunt for more
exotic tank what am I doing I become a
monster this
thing David B I don't think that should
get much funding you see that thing in
front of
you did he meant to shoot me
or probably did he miss you and hit me
I'm not sure what happened there does
doesn't matter he's dead now I think he
saw a truck and and got fixated on the
truck and then I am quite stylish he's
too he's blinded by your right you see
anything else down there I'm seeing
nothing I think you're clear all the way
no you're not clear not clear paner oh
my gosh I I pushed too
far oh hey can you guys handle that I
have a small issue building over here
can you thank you oh no I have to go see
you
later I'm on the ice I got a stick give
me one second oh that's he's dead I am
I'm having new issues
now thanks hold on no no worry about the
Tanks i the situation are deal with no
fate don't go join him he has tracks I
going to tow rope you and drag you along
the edge of the
canal uh I need to move out of the way I
need to move out of the way as long as I
drive on the snow I have some
control you can see the ice is a little
slippery you don't have any control just
what are you talking about this is
perfect what wait this actually might be
a good strategy you could just shoot
over the
ledge uh maybe nobody expect nobody
expect Gunner machine gunner I'm trying
to hit the brakes but this is fine hold
on I'll I'll be back in a second your
tur you might as well just turn around
fully this is so hard to
aim I'm like a cat trying to run on ice
this is terrible tank where I'm going to
die soon to being out of Balan me give
me the tank give me the give me the tow
rope I need tet first oh no I'm good I'm
good I can't hit bounc I'm reloading
give me the oh okay we're fighting down
here now he's just sitting right there
he's smoked I I'm at a bad angle for
him uh I can still see him he's disabled
there he goes he's down give me your to
hard left hard left shoot tanks I'm
trying to get it I'm trying to see it
he's down give me give me your to give
me your to no I need to repair just help
me repair I'm going to drag you focus on
winning the fight first
over can you help drag me up this I was
going to drag you back out the other one
don't or maybe I can make the Hop oh
look at this
thing W you didn't even need me it's
amazing right at times did anybody get
that um Panzer four that we no it's
still wounded and then okay well watch
your right when you poke out that way
copy yeah nobody nobody moveing the
flank oh he's looking at me what where
oh he's down Jesus it's all good well
you know that works out uh stay cool my
babies what is it stick is dead fine
traded there's another one next to
there's another one on the flank well uh
he's right there he took moving around
I'm moving around took everything I hope
he doesn't notice me he just took my
Barrel can still focused on me I just
can't get a shot he's around that corner
right he's right there yes okay I have
to continue the flight around he's dead
thank you you want to take
Charlie sure I'll go over to Charlie
than marked on it near our friendlies I
I only have two crew members left so
might as well I have four also white
pole never mind think on the road Mar
three there's a mar three down the aim
there we go down there one
down h p look at your map there was a
mar coming loation
I'm going to take you next he's
down oh my God you're on a roll why why
are you the most deadly truck ever cuz
I'm
stylish I told you this okay okay it's
that
performance okay that Italian is that
this one doesn't have rally car Heritage
does it it's that pedigree I tell you uh
there's something close to
me what pedigree you don't have a pedig
it's a of excellence in winning might be
might be the Martyr think it's close to
me or is it going around me uh he was on
that side wait I can hide the cabin
here are you there we go he just got da
even sneak here hello I am here to help
with this uh martyr
problem oh my God what's
up what's the
matter oh T just drove past you
distracted me dick what
uh right there loader can you finish
that one yeah rotating there's another
one behind him okay which one you we
take whichever one you can hit copy I'm
about to enter The Fray taking the back
one close one's yours close one's yours
okay where's the other one uh on Mark
right there we got one close left push
in the corner Nice kill
stick danger close on top of me God
you're like a
spider what do you mean I'm like a
spider shot that supposed to me they
hide they they hide their heads and only
like show the rear section which is like
painted colors to like
attract what they want to
eat I'm not a black
widow oh no no your cab like that it's
happening Puma behind me Puma behind
mea rotating rotating drive this way I
am just drive drive finish drive hold
hold hold hold hold hold up don't back
up you push me you I was going to handle
T right there tank on the corner tank on
the corner is another one yep Mar no
Canon
breach punching him he's
down think it's very hard to stay play
to get this thing on
Target and I know you want to help
that's why I said I was going to do it
but just remember no means
no I'm being shot in the back stick oh
up bye okay you're on your own
now sad
truck tank on me oh uh two tanks on me
one's over here here to the left another
one to the right pushed uh towards the
other entrance I got a small boy that
probably the one I
saw you know what is exactly Bo okay
Sherman to your front right Sherman to
the front the sh front you doing the
most Soviet thing I've ever seen you do
no one on it's failed me it's failed me
um hey on that Mark if you taken fate oh
I'm
dead P dead how you doing not good
pushing for Sherman good news Sherman's
absolutely distracted Sherman's gone
that's terrifying okay I'm now having
nightmares tonight and I'm going to go
find a new place to attack or live or
just start a new life I don't
know can you see that Panther 3 down
there I cannot he is right there I see
him I see him I see him I see him yep
okay I got two bombs for him if you
can't finish
them don't fly in there don't my
goodness we almost all just died
hey good kill uh no worries uh stick I'm
sorry but your body and plane are not
recoverable it's okay I didn't have an
engine so it was um that way or the
highway we got a puma watching the point
over here stick committed uh there's
also a little Swedish AA thing pbv oh
nice you know where uh it's shooting at
you now I
believe yeah it's shooting at you now I
have my awkward til turret I can use
you're going to try to gun him with the
rear is he on our side or their side
he's on their side oh that thing has the
butt gun oh there I see him is that him
no that's not I was wondering why
something just went out
trim I got the paner 30 off the point uh
shot yeah I can't help you I'm being
shot I'm kind of in trouble here I'm
going to try to use my turret if I can
yep it lines up in
time or the Gunner was uh not home
anymore think on the corner
D3 I got you thank you I'm your truck
OverWatch Your Guardian truck angel that
was that was excellent I'm here to H
away your problem I'll stop I'm sorry
are you a moving truck now I move 90 mm
shells at a high velocity towards their
target I was waiting to see how long
until you ran out of ideas at rock
bottom
prices he's call me the Koolaid
man I got there he goes oh wait that
actually worked why did that can shoot
over the wall can't you I told you I
haul away your problems that's amazing
that perfect they have B by the way the
a factory is the great is a great place
hey Bo there's another problem where
okay hold on second RSE a little
slow but I'm here never mind I'm gone
Here Comes one of the weirdest
deliveries you're ever going to
see that was his pain it was a T14 T14
well done that is scary
he machine gun allow my
crew help I should be good I got 28
second
repair something else I think was near
Charlie heit you just like hip checked
me as you went past sorry I have these
little anchors that stick out the side
be careful okay stick that was that was
on
purpose maybe Corner what okay so sound
like you have food in your mouth for a
second you good I do oh okay
you sound like a chip you're not
supposed to distracting tanking don't
eat in tank that's how you get crumbs in
your keyboard there's another there's a
Sherman back there you want me shoot
through the building I I don't know I
okay he maybe thought that was you so
get ready you made him mad yeah I'm
trying to bait for
you if you can put down the cookies long
enough you might be able to kill
himun what what was that noise can I get
a can I get a repeat on the last
transmission there's multiple there's
multiplexes there's multiple M Sexes
okay scary guns I got one I got one
scary guns Doc and I are doing our best
to
distract are you almost
loaded they took my breach it's your
dinner still on the plate do I need help
okay it's I'm actually eating uh Milanos
so uh yeah well that sounds
fancy what was
that sorry trying to talk while I'm
eating it's not a gooda I understand
yeah no just don't choke I don't want to
have St boy give you the maneuver
the stick's dead so I don't know how
he's going to help well that would be
really bad for you
then I don't see anything else in that
corner so I don't know where the other
M6 is yeah he backed off I don't either
he lost something or couldn't get
through you want to go follow
him he's going right he's going right I
hear him me I hear him going right do be
careful in the Gap he might be there
already I'm going to get the Decap going
he not that oh my God be coming in here
hi sir oh no bye no that was a 105
Sherman yeah that was a 105 can you
break that door right
there no or that that works too I
guess something behind me what
what okay that's
enough okay nobody can talk on this
squad that's what got me good luck the
the PO it's the PO I heard behind
me oh I have bad news it got worse for
me I'm your only for no I don't machine
gun me that proceed you that did not
kill
him got big machine guns loed up here
I'm trying to help you I got to go he's
he's to your hard right right there Ram
him Ram him I was counting on you I took
his machine gunner I'm trying I'm trying
it looks like you're line dancing with
him doy do grab your
partner I've done line dancing before
that's why I know this I'm sorry I'm
glad you're in the grave uh flank left
if you want to get him blank left you
just shot me sck you on him right there
if you're happy and you know it kill a
chaffie I missed kind of song is you're
not happier he's still looking at me
still looking at
me stick did you just I'm really not
happy he's right corner at the corner I
finished him another one left uh Left
Right another chappie your wizard hat is
right in the way okay I just fired the
top of your hat oh thank you for not
wait you got him okay thank you do the
planes are here I'm
reloading anti-air problems you never
have ammo when you need
it yep is true we have multiple friendly
air up so we should be fine ah he says
that look at the catastrophe that
happened over here I know there's so
much death it's just death on both sides
of the road German CR the hill right
there yep oh nice kill time to re
position Giant Truck of
Doom yep it's just like discount black
bus 2 second rep he's pushing back in
the window he's down hey I know you
don't have a machine gun but hey look z
boy got replaced by TBL
Wilbert Wilbert uh stick is wber
shooting your AI bot is attacking me why
did you crash your game your Bot is
attacking doing Wilbert has turned
against me what is he doing probably
wrong him in some way did you really get
replaced by you did get replaced by
Wilbert what say like that okay he wil
is a bully Wilber is Ping he is still me
in spirit he's shooting that kv1s in the
back and pushing me around what's he
doing he just shot where did he shoot at
he's just shooting that
potty plane plane plane oh run okay
there's no bombs that there's a tank out
there though but the plane knows you're
here probably how am I going to hide
this thing I don't know
um try really hard and believe that
plane isn't real well you're With
Wilbert good luck what I'm driving home
going why are we saying it like that why
are you leaving me with Wilbert I don't
want Wilbert's now pushing me well yeah
he's a boy Wilbert what are you oh he
hit somebody uh W's still shooting
things I don't know where they are he's
just shooting through walls you know
maybe maybe if we just if we just let
Wilbert sort
of you know if we if we take some
pressure off what happened in between
you from Hangar to ing game that you got
replaced by a bot named Wilbur what
what's going on my gun we don't talk
about that Weill and a black bu over
there that's talk about that yeah sh
firefight from left I pushed up too far
that's not great I got the Church Hill
Nice kill on the Church Hill that's
actually really good
um but my flacky 88 Brethren is out
there hunting me
now another tank right there my goodness
the
fire back in a kv1 there's a bunch of
guys on I don't know if you can see my
mark on the map but there's a bunch of
guys over there unfortunately right here
though they're pushing across I'm trying
to come down all right well as long as
you got a good sight line through there
you can at least work on some of those
guys they're going to push was that a
bomb no that was a shell I got to go see
you later which one's the most dangerous
one to you uh the one that's right there
there's two right there's two there's a
hiding with them oh God are those good
there's one the pur thank you that's a
and I'm sure you disabled the other guy
I'm cirle back for the
plane keep going do you're
good he will be double in a
second okay that's where I have to
actually kill him but you're good Mr a
wing tip will go down
thank you
maybe he's getting lower there's a a on
me he's down down is that off on
me looks like it no oh that's Firefly oh
that's Firefly is that what was firing
at me
uh this is a bad move but I'm going to
drive for
it I got the turret ring if you want to
go for the rest of it I am two people
dead in the
turret got some the 50 he's also got
meding
eyes something else is hitting me
another AA sitting right there I think
that's a um what's it called the South
African R3 Cannon oh the
uh or whatever yeah thank you sorry nice
I couldn't remember which one was what
yeah they've all got weird names well
there just two different ones there's
one with the zsu and there's one with
the um oh yeah Park and then the other
one bit you doing okay over there
hey paner P are where behind me
backwards now my reverse is not very
quick you're on your own for a minute
can help
youan low right Panzer is watching is he
Cloud watching what is he doing he's I'm
watching your helpful teammates up there
I'm not sure what they're doing either
where is he low right it's fine I got it
I got it I got it we don't talk about
that handle I'm sorry okay nope nope he
was he was covered by a rock or
something we don't talk about how it was
just in the open and I'm blind come on
daa the water's fine yep waiting for
there to R take him out yeah there he
goes I have no idea if anything's on be
or not well we'll find out together
right you best let Stick Boy go first
that' probably be a smart plan why you
have more armor what what I I okay that
was at me not at you you yeah yeah it
was saying you to clarify I looked at
the front of my truck like do I not know
something I know armor best armor
clearly oh I meant fate feel free to
shove me up the hill if you need to uh
you know if I could catch you that would
be a great option you're slightly faster
than me we're all different struggle
buses today yeah we are if you see
planes be taller cuz I want to be out of
here I am not at all plane that's a tank
that's that's not a plane what is that
guy doing
he's dead does he have a
friend I don't know let me Po my head
out and see if anything shoots me I'm
going to try and reverse behind you but
it's very very slow hey daa you might
push in the front of my cab so I can go
faster and reverse um yes and then I can
properly
help what
where on the
bridge I see it I see it he just roll on
the bridge that's right
no
I shot I have plenty of depression right
now because I'm machine gun by 30 50
Cals I can't hit him I can hit
him I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying I'm
trying I'm trying this is an American
Gladiators I also Austin Powered myself
thoroughly well in here in the Panic
here you turn on your to to toe rope I
don't know what you just said to me I
can't even I can't even what was what'
you say first I don't know I think he
said to ro there is one C up so be
careful please drag me out
here I can't back up that quickly go go
go quick this is me at full speed I I
will push you okay you promise yeah I
promise thanks Dad we go this way now uh
tank right there there something
shooting at
you be machine gun oh god oh you were
dead
anyway that's not what I want to
hear
[Music]
a