why are you guys inside of each other
what the hell happened hey stick don't
ask questions you don't want the answer
to okay
Jim and I had a very unfortunate
accident and now we're merged together
no no why is it the Abrams that does
this it is always the Abrams that likes
to get bad never connect
Ed
uses like instead go to your room just
go go to your room
do you not watch what's happening in
front of you right now oh look at us
this is
very traumatizing for for poor stick boy
oh my
I'm sorry on my end
I just get so excited when we play
Abrams I can't help myself man buy me
dinner first good Lord we are live on
the ground here oh my God
if things have not gone well
I turned the corner I see a t-80 driving
through a massive dead Abram's bodies
and you guys screaming I'm gonna back up
now and hide and re-evaluate everything
no no situations under control we swear
to you are you sure I I you just had a
burglar in the midst of your home
no no no that was just stick boy letting
in you know a funny guy hey stick we
need to have a talk
I don't want to talk I want I want
therapy the 80s I want a baseball bat
don't let them indoors they're outdoor
tanks okay
I can just imagine like the news reel
now like has your child been exposed to
a t-80 here are the warning signs
yeah Jim you just got spoke to a t80
I did I think I'm pushing left
but but the t80 was left I was gonna go
right so that I can get behind I'll hold
here noise right there
right there right there pushing me
facing me okay coming around coming
around I'm coming around coming around
let me know when you have it dealt with
Hey Big Boy
nice job
it was a good plan 50 50.
we enveloped the enemy that's a tactical
word
I think you'd use engulfed surrounded
it almost sounds like you're hugging
them
I embrace the enemy oh
well I'm just not gonna go that
direction and I'm gonna go seek years of
therapy for watching stick boy just be
plucked off the planet in front of me
like he was a toy in a crane game he got
raptured he did I heard Sonic Boom
missile Stick Boy gone
you can just go check this side of the
street maybe this is nice over here
hello any Soviet era things
when to kill me
well there's one uh tank right there on
that Mark on Joe party
yep
Mi 28
I repeat am I doing stop taking all my
friends angry Sky God
in the city there it is oh in memory of
stick boy that's what we have to say as
he gets killed by a leopard 2a5 in
memory of Stick Boy
yes
what a great team at your gym
oh and memory of Stick Boy
they're gonna make a park bench for me
soon
I'm sorry I'm getting what I deserve
what's happening to you back there Karma
can you explain where it is he is on
this Mark
he is also having a stare down with a
friendly Abrams
I'm gonna try and save you
thank you I'd say try because I hear
something flying overhead
I could save you
thanks bud Jeremy just backed us up like
that oh man oh look at you guys butt to
butt hey okay he made it weird so
yes and memory of stick boy was the
correct reaction to what happened back
there
hello and welcome to the reopening of
the famous a factory known for making
all forms of the letter A except this
time is we're no longer is making the
forms of the letter A we're making
Abrams because a a for Abrams remember
your ABCs no now go back to school
forget about it welcome to the a factory
I I have a question
no questions oh oh okay I have many
questions hey why are they making Abrams
in Russia
too I have a question what was that
accent
I I'm going this way now
you're doing the Hokey Pokey and you
turn yourself around I just didn't want
to hit the poor Latin that's what a is
about
all right so uh you leave the premises
go go to the Schmucks at the Beef
Factory this would be the most confusing
intelligence briefing ever I didn't know
we were having a factory tour today I
don't know what's happening at all
except there must be like a BNP in front
of stick oh my
machine gun
wants some cannons
right right there right close right wall
wall everything just shoot just don't
back up I mean I'm gonna casually back
up first just keep backing your room
you're good
hey Jim
yeah that's the tour guide is there
another entrance we can take uh well I'd
just like to let you know that the a
factory is not responsible for any
injuries and or deaths things this way
okay that was pretty cool stick
I'm gonna go home think close right I
can see his Barrel poking around the
corner I shot his Barrel you can't hurt
you no more
I killed him please
there's more in there I guarantee it
this is not the Men's Warehouse for
record
no this is the a factory come on boy we
just had this whole Factor we have this
whole tour about this
I'm gonna push into the factory
I want some walls and a slight roof over
my head if I can
oh my God it is not safe it is not safe
at all
I got a leopard too I got a t80
I got
I don't know anything hey Jim yes
me and that man traded shells I got the
better deal but there's a lot of me
missing right now no no I'll put you
back together you know what's funny
because we have Dave you know we make
use here the a factory Abrams hey
what I'm laughing internally because I
know it was made of this Factory
historically
which is like the furthest thing from an
Abrams you know could possibly get what
he is some kind of Ned and you read
books you know what there's a tank
sitting right out here I'd like to talk
to you Jim
yeah no ow my turret ring you know the
Soviets would like to have a word
about their a factor Gunners out on him
I would like to apologize to anything
negative I've ever said in the past 10
minutes he's done
okay I take that apology back through
him I'm gonna repair you we're gonna get
through this okay
thanks I must say this this tour guide
has some very strong opinions you know
we make it through this I can get you a
job here it pays well this is one of the
most strange rounds of War Thunder I've
ever had I do not know what's going on
anymore
uh stick there's one behind you there's
tanks in that pile bodies right there
Jim
he's at the other he's at the bee
Factory well we'll uh the Beef Factory I
hate those guys they're killing me they
stink Jim's lost his mind
they killed me
the bee Factory boys got stick I can't
we gotta break the kneecaps oh we gotta
go let's go get the tire from the truck
I got my crowbar right here
okay let's check this first
take it slow
there could be right there
no something just fired from that angle
right there see the mark yeah yep
you see where it is right just blind
yeah I see it
no there's a mark on there and I saw
left close after me oh gosh
right there I'm putting my fire out
if you just hold narrow up here
yep nope he is very close
yes
I think I'm about to meet him
they overran the a factory no he's so
pushed sir
if any of you make it up here there's an
ifb on the other side I'm sorry Bo I
can't
never mind he got strafed the B Factory
boys have overran the a factory
boys there's a tank beside me
it's Jim's worst nightmare
tank there
ain't happy one
also leopard behind me pushing into the
small Factory between us
he's gonna push up on your right jump on
your right I do I'm being shot no they
overran the a-factor get out of there
I'm surrounded I am totally surrounded
right now we gotta burn it down can you
call somebody hey I can call Tommy
tentos Tommy tent
what if he has tintos how's that unique
how's that a nickname he actually has
nine oh yeah
trying to get in here it's trying to get
in here
I bet it snows off
why would you bite its nose off that's
the only thing I could do it's time to
fight dirty
yeah I'm uh I'm being circled right now
like sharks
I'm gonna go
they're dropping everything on you
something just landed in here with me
please let there be room
there's one out there oh there is
I am totally surrounded
behind me
I gotta hit no damage they swarmed that
factory was so much hatred
but the second one got me bad ideas
take three all the other Abrams did a
little drifty thing too oh I should
probably pay attention
more happening yeah there is a war I'm
sorry I got distracted by Abram's drift
I think Abram's drifts are more uh
important they are really cool though
yeah like when Abrams gets sliding
just watch out
I just saw a friendly are you good over
there stick I shot the stick shot I saw
the friendly thinking it was an enemy
because you weren't paying attention
it's like that was my friend
also I'm over here very nervously
looking behind me because I expect a
herd of t80s to just rush this
intersection at me well would you like a
thought to make you uh stop thinking
about that what's that
you bake cookies
but you uh cook bacon
no why why did you have to start that so
he's bacon cookies you can grow up first
and then find if there's any new tanks
that push the street okay no worries
I'll go with your friend
sir I'm sorry you can't park there
all right parking tickets now stick see
you're a murder maid are you okay
no he shot me before you uh I'm sorry I
typed on your face to repair you this is
very awkward why
you climbed on my face to fix me
I want to make sure that you know it's
gonna be okay
okay now we have a party watching us so
I don't know if I like this I I don't
want to look at that actually let's just
let's just cap the a point there I'm
gonna look at the leg this
I'm gonna push your direction
if you want to turn around somewhere
okay
you're a drone
that's where we're gonna push this way
away from the cluster of Abrams
leave it with you in a second we just
have to gather ourselves here I got
something right uh yep fast one fast one
I got this driver an engine I took his
track damn you should be able to finish
him I got him he's dead he's dead
the steaks might have been made
I'll let you know in a second
great places right there
dear Mark yep driver engine on him he
can't move yep nice got him thank you
I want some fire coming from my left
over here Cannon breach on that thing
Jim that's an oil drinker but I I think
I see what you're talking about yes that
one right there his third drives out
I got another one
hey you gun okay we all have targets we
all are getting in line
I'm looking right there he's down
thank you jumped into my front lap for
sure
took my leg if we keep this going boys
let's give them all numbers and process
this like the DMV so we'll never
finish helicopter out bearing 176
careful
bmp2 dead that's the thing making all
the pew pew happen
I could use repairs that's what's my
right track all right push it up to you
for support oh thank you emotional
and physical oh thanks well
well I just need mechanical support I
know about physical support I mean it's
technically physical I mean I have to
add the tool in my hand and then I work
it around and then your track's on hey
Jim yeah I think you can need emotional
support after that never come up to me
again and say work it around please what
that's how wrenches work
fair enough what's wrong but you don't
like Jim working around the top yeah
that's exact exactly why right there to
the left also I just did the stupidest
thing ever I deserve to die I deserve
Jimmy yeah
this is horrible please please help me
out this before I die hey Jimbo needs
physical help again yes I need you to
let me just work it around physically
help me
with Chuck repairs oh yeah it would be
lovely you're laughing at me but I'm
gonna repair you because that's what
teammates do
there you go oh thank you very much go
get him tiger you know I I I love on
this map just absolutely spending my
time and surveying the beautiful scenery
of the B point
absolutely the honestly Bo
sometimes I wake up at six o'clock in
the morning before my work shift and I
load into this map and I just I just sit
and just admire the beautiful map design
and beauty
it is it's wonderful state if you can't
tell Thor he doesn't have good
experiences on this map I mean this map
is just wonderful I agree with him it's
a great beautiful map I do the same
before work you should feel like you're
home it's got snow
and there's a lake
it's a bad plan but it's a plan
nice work now he's gonna have a bad day
at the beach because he's burned
how long you've been sitting on that one
long enough that it's dude
oh
odd
he's laughing at his own jokes now he's
completely lost I might just run out to
that ice in a second here
uh there's one right there I'm sorry
there's also one further back
he's down give me the old one too
I'm sorry I thought that was just a
truck there I didn't know there's
something behind it I thought it was a
truck as well
I just saw a missile fire from their
spawn also tank pushing right there
get to see the machine on top
oh yeah I can see it poking over the
ridge yes be careful of him
otherwise we can just get this point we
get out of here
I'm gonna back up and hide a little bit
more
oh no I'm sorry I'm sorry
hide behind what I just ko'd up for
Abrams
how dare you though
I backed up full speed to a friendly
you know you keep that up and and he's
not gonna go camping with you do you see
the mark next to you on the map what
there's a mark on the map circling oh
yeah I trust him he's got that
can you can you help him
not really not when I'm backwards the
hstville just lost his head wow yeah I
just thought that was from your right
all's fair and loving yeah
but he's down no we gotta kill the thing
that's killing people
looking
right there
it's all on you bow
I wish it wasn't
I'm on my way wish it wasn't Arctic
Explorer test with the mission of
fighting I just blew my own breach
because I'm panicking because I'm
sitting down yeah I think that was
coming very quickly
where's that t80 oh it's down there just
right ahead she's waiting for you I'm
I'm gonna go tell the teacher that you
have a fart you stuck I'm stuck on the
wrong brain
you're gonna Abram sir move
there you go what's going on up here it
takes two Abrams to get through a hole
don't ask
that's all the details you're getting
yep
uh there's multiple times oh there's
that t80
I was being half sarcastic about the t80
it's gone bad up here
it's gone real bad
see that oh just off to your left okay
third don't mind this but your body is
now a meat you said how you want to
uh gentlemen there's take just got shot
in the face he's getting some help no
we'll trade I'm just gonna there is a
lot of them down there drop already drop
anything you got
you got it friend
right there that's the closest one yep
trying to hit it
Jim you may want to back up further yeah
I keep hitting this Commander he's
pushing he's pushing popped up one
popped out
oh hello oh hi sorry sorry didn't mean
to rub on him trying to get shot
I'm just gonna show his body will
forward like that
I just see all the touches going on
he's getting closer he's getting closer
right side yep yep he can't fire he
can't fire he's got to repair that
Cannon breach get a new Gunner okay I'm
gonna try to slip out and kill him then
no shot if you step out make sure you go
right because if you go left you're
gonna end you're gonna enter the firing
hole of death
yeah but I come and play some offense
here so I'm gonna see if I get closer
one right there hit him no good
you see him pushing nope
did you lose your engine
gone I'm gone no no no no
you keep finding repair
10 seconds that's all you got to survive
is 10 seconds
D you're doing good they resettle of it
though so
cause they shot me
I'm just gonna curl up in a ball nope
okay I can't Crump a ball there
only here where are they at same place
that they shot you from nothing much has
changed but the amount of bodies oh okay
and we're losing a lot of Abrams it
looks warm and toasty over here this is
a very expensive fight
I'm gonna try and move forward
let's do it with caution
there's no caution here
only zul
your pit crew is here
let's just push this what they can't go
any worse scarge
no you're also adorable
a little air assault tank
we'll find you an airplane later
oh
I'm pushing straight across
while he's fighting that
oh good job
what's down here that's a question I
want to ask
but is this better please don't ask that
question the terrible game show I've
entered
oh right there
guys can't breach if you want to finish
him you got a shot I can't I don't have
a shot
I'm trying but there's a window I can
shoot through that
if you just want to watch I mean watch
up for the Target it's not like
oh oh God
just drove up where right on the border
behind you that's creepy he looks creepy
he's looking at me like hey for a minute
anybody close that can assist with the
creepy deity on the corner I will be
there in about one and a half business
days he just chased me down
War Thunder is a horror game sometimes
like a psychological horror not just
jump scare right
there's one thank you one's dead there's
a second one behind pushing further back
and right get back to him keep backing
up keep packing up keep backing up he's
right there let's push left
you see him
he's going towards the lumber Nice kill
thank you so much you guys got one uh
good job on your side of B near the rock
as well
I have to repair my Barrel
those missiles
are making me very nervous as I've seen
them fly past all right they're not
coming at you nope I'm just watching
play right to left in front of me
you see that Mark right there in front
yeah but you know that doesn't matter as
long as they're not at you he gets two
kills also he's Mr chill
water under the bridge well listen Bo
he's when you got a cool
you can finish them if you want you can
get collected
one right there
yep
you good nice kill yeah yeah you see
cool calm
collected individual
then the battlefield just comes like
putty in your hands pink in front of me
right here behind this building one left
of him okay watch your left hard left
watch the uh the hill to your left yeah
I see it
this guy that was my concern
he's fired he went low
I can't get back skills right now you
see this one right here
yep
you're just my madman this match
it's a uh I lost him
he's switching pushing low right yeah he
just shot at me
if you want to charge them I'll keep
engaged with me I don't have a breach
and it'll take 60 seconds for repair oh
that's quite a bit of time
it is
how about I just hold back a second and
let this happen
also is your left clear
as far as the stick eyes can see
it's tick ice
yeah guys
he is just sitting there I'm gonna drop
Artie
he's pushing
do you see him
oh my God yes yes I'm sorry I didn't
think I got it with already
we got somebody else
one stuck up behind me
you gotta Drop Smoke and leave now
I don't know if I'm gonna get out here
in time
I will not be his litter came back
good job sick no let's go kill Street by
you
[Music]