wind up for the pitch
oh it's a strike I'm being shot in the
pack is that you nice kill nope that was
me that was me sorry thanks for the
minor heart attack I was trying to shoot
at a plane
would you rather have gotten bombed I
just I got flanked for a second I'm
sitting here getting a crew member and
an enemy tank just drove up next to me
oh god well it is going I didn't do
anything distract him okay wiggle be
friendly
I am not a friendly tank
really mad
don't you shoot there do not shoot there
stop stop on my side of my side on my
side no I'm in full panic I can't turn
faster I lift I lived
he broke my other track
I'm gonna hurt you trying to get to you
there's a teammate nearby he's right now
he's getting straight
we could be friends I'm sorry for the
mean things I said
I'm alive and his head is over there
this is stressful
I'm gonna need a pamphlet and therapy
and a hobby
I do not know who I'm alive thank you so
much Wayne run little ones
the plane candy killed him this is so
terrible
look at that one
what in the world I don't know what's
happening but it's not gonna be good
Airline oh no that's a big bomb coming
this way that's what that is that's a
big bomb
just fire at him fire everything fire
everything throw things at him
what is it the plank another Point
coming in
we just gotta fight for our lives now
another plane coming in
I gotta hit him right on Fire Sun
I gotta repair again
oh well I killed that guy left left it's
a plane why why do we summon so many
places another plane faring 80 where is
the airplane
right we're coming down from straight
down straight down what I have to reload
straight down I can't aim it
oh
I'm broken again I'm broken again too
I'm never meant to have these tracks
ever where is he where is he I think he
has more ordinance This Town Plaza it's
just their oh no bearing two five five
two planes five five on those marks
right there and another Point coming in
right there yep I see that one
oh it's like a zero or something
okay so I'm repaired and uh no offense
I'm gonna go drive towards a I'm gonna
go leave because as a tank destroyer
I would like to go see other tanks again
I came over here to help you guys all I
got was bombs I said it was awful
we did say that on the pamphlet yeah
it's gonna be awful
well you know I didn't think that it was
uh no playing big plane it's coming back
like where you mean the big plane from
earlier Josh is playing right at me
watch
how did I miss that oh my God oh my boy
you missed the airliner World somebody
please shoot that don't make Cannon
somebody please one of his Pilots please
took one of his Pilots please it was all
in there
goodbye
I just saw a tank Crest around the
building in front of me he's down oh
nice shot he has a tank no more that was
a big boy I have to put a new Barrel on
oh do you get your wait what happened
you shot each other the same time
oh you could say we exchange another one
another one
so if you look at my Barrel I'm unable
to really do anything about it so I'm
just kind of stuck here watching yeah no
I know I know I'm just letting you know
by screaming it loudly no worries
I'm reloading now it's like a Sherman or
something it's yeah
if you say M51 I'm gonna push you out
there first they're also over there
they're also over there I mean it might
be shot came from left on the field oh
my God he just exploded
yep make sure the left your left is
covered yep watching that way oh my God
there's a heavy tank in front of us
there's a heavy tank in front of us you
want to push
I I think I'm gonna I'll I'll push if
you want to push all right beside you
they're also two are right over there
that's not good
Nice Shot stick anything else I got one
right there there's one back where where
fate marks okay I trust you guys got
right and pushing left German oh he took
my gut wait what I'm going forward
right
I'm looking right for worship hello Mr
Sherman I am so sorry for the overkill
ah don't be sorry the the T20 right fade
right you see that
no I'm just gonna tuck in here and
reload the last second uh you guys got
that shoot the machine gun no is is it
tanks down the road coming in they got
reinforcements
oh that's a D30 I'm half reloaded I'm
trusting you to have my back right now
please load please load please load
please
didn't load there is a small Squad of
Tanks pushing down Main Road come on
please be a little faster please reload
faster I need the show no it's missed oh
my god well uh it's been an honor
serving of you bait no I need you
nope you are you are surrounded I just
lost my track
the t-32 as now is aware of your
location I can't aim part up to shoot
the guy to the right you pushing come on
keep pushing
I'm an example of the Sherman for the
others that's all I could do
well uh you have some friendlies pushing
up so yeah
um the t-32 is still over there and
there's a t-34 further down like
around uh they're they're I don't know
there ish I'm surprised I'm still alive
actually I thought they were gonna swore
me why did you say that
don't do that please I beg of you
please don't do that t26 pushed into my
front left somewhere
or direct front Maybe
uh yeah no there he is there he is I see
you
don't have t-32 that's not the t26
that's a t34 t29
well his engine's out and he's talking
about the road he's very unhappy oh well
that's unfortunate for him
well all he has to do is wait for your
reload and then you can finish him it's
a very long reload
the 20 second or so reload I've lost a
few crew members too he's looking my way
oh and that's going to be significantly
longer I'm gonna go for it
maybe not what is happening to my high
Bearcat maneuver kill I suppose
I got the radiator on the big American
heavy tank so that's uh more victory
what is shooting to my close right
oh I'm sure it's nothing don't worry
about it
um
oh no I'm sticking my head back out here
coming right there so there's some
marked
220 65 down I took him coming up to help
him good work
I like to move from this position
someday but I don't know where to go t34
is down what's what's machine getting
you bro we may have over
uh they're on the right plane so just be
careful I just got your machine gunner
okay come here this is embarrassing you
got the AAS machine gunner yes I don't
that's it
don't don't question this okay
ah you know that's the hundred you know
always killing me oh he's killing me I
have a machine guns on it oh that was a
lie don't get sir you're embarrassing me
please stop
oh yeah sir sir
no what you survived
this is looking really bad please stop
oh no he said he's done I got it first
shot
on your right
copyright
no eyes yeah there is there's just just
head towards B and you'll find them
eventually I'm almost to be
I see one on that building right there
I assume that's what you're talking
about
yep should be a t29 slash like p34 over
there I'm gonna guess there's other
things here too I think the t-34 was a
bit a bit more south
if you see that Mark on the map the one
that's like out there they're out God
for example I've got a tank right to my
left I hear him butcher me
um good luck I have no eyes
but I'll wish you well you know but you
just have to push them real good then
okay you know what I'm gonna
I can't do anything to him but no you
can't do anything to him right now
later though yeah later maybe
they're all pushing
family of t26s have just arrived a
family how many is this like a family
combo meal or something of p26s well
yeah how many does a family two there's
two oh oh so it's a couple
I'm watching American Heavy tanks
everywhere and I don't know which one to
fight first
which everyone can kill you the most
now all of them can kill him
I hear you beside me
but he's not pushing hi I'm I'm almost
here where is he there's one behind me
to my left
behind like which which car let me give
you Mark I hear noise back back over
here
okay
um
I don't I don't see anything yet though
it's there there's something there I
promise you
behind that building somewhere yeah okay
I'm not crazy I believe you I'm not
crazy
leave you
okay I'm gonna try and push B
look at a lava itchy shell over there
and just see if I hit anything
back out didn't get anything
there he is right there
the second I pulled back he fired at me
he took a shot at me I'm gonna try to
get around him
yep I got a shell loaded come on they
rotate he's down
nice deal so I knew I heard him over
there
yes you sure did
all right let's go get Bravo Now
my poor object 268 is just absolutely
covered
and hits on the right side that's crazy
do you see that one where the shell is
actually just still embedded in your
tank I do the tiger two just want to add
another one to the collection I think
that's crazy you've got so many shell
pock marks everywhere I can add one here
let me add a few I love this thing
having a T10 chassis at this battle
rating is crazy you are not welcome in
here
Mr M51 with your fancy heat shell I know
what you want to do to me oh no another
M51
oh God I am surrounded
it is fancy heat gel they brought in the
vehicle to kill me it's like the perfect
meta to finish me off
thank you so much
I just worked through fate Point clicked
and he disappeared it's a stressful day
at day Factory it is a stressful day
there's also a guy over there you know
I'm just gonna see if I can lob an AP
show more of a lowercase a I have to say
uh more tanks pushed in the other door
I'm gonna cover that is it is the ah
Factory or is it the a factory it might
be an at symbol type of day over here
but I mean though they're still there
streaming but not screaming M51
on that Mark
oh I shot over sorry I'm trying to
engage guys because you're right he's
done okay there's uh m41 in there yeah
I'm noticing a lot of things dying in
front of me another thing over there
I don't know how to help I got that I
got a lot of Panther right there right
thing pushing up there to that door
up got him bye bye nice work
I'm gonna push on try to cut him off
okay 41 right over there here comes the
bombs yep might have been in a Rado
there was something over here
I got it uh yep I said I see the fun in
the building m41 right there
got him oh good job is that building
clear now
yep building is clear I've killed two
guys in there a lot of them both over
the wall okay let's try a cafe
yep
I got it the captain
there's a whole Gathering of them out
here whole family no
leper one down to the left of that Mark
there's gonna be two more shot you oh
thank you gay yeah
there's friendlies behind us I think was
that friendly that's friendly no yeah
yeah that was not friendly not friendly
that was from the right I remember
remember the danger of the m51s yeah
there was it there's like four of them
all coming out coming out of their spawn
oh my God there's a there's a herd of
them
I may have angered the M51 family there
was a herd of them there's like leopards
Tigers everything everything is coming
out of there
I'm gonna have to come up with a plan
here I see like a whole group of them
just sitting right there on that Mark
yeah that that's the herd and then
there's things on by the factory where
stick died yep yep
yeah there's something like on the
corner over there yeah I'm trying to see
if I can mark them up a little bit there
he is it is another M51
oh my God again yeah there's one down
there I see him
Nice kill I'm very happy with that
that's the guy who got me it was me or
him
um her to the right is still there
yeah the guy near you just died I just
lost my friendly next to me
yeah I'm pushing up to you Laura on the
way bro
I'll dig it as long as I can
I'm more worried about down there
somebody's taking a shot from over there
that's a lot of bombs Rockets thank
corner
tiger two down Nice kill
okay it's gonna be okay I have to tell
myself that
things will get I can see the hole
through him blowing underneath his front
plate that's awesome
wait the whole from where you shot I put
the show through there's fire that's
pretty cool the herd is still pushing
hurt is still pushing
uh that is not good then
I'm not gonna peek and let them keep
coming
okay
hello fate
I it's kind of awful here if you want to
take a wide corner
apparently Mark on the map for the
Centurion they're over there
wait what right there
there's a body in the way there's an M51
block there's a lot of M51 bodies
I think that's what the factory makes
something left
you got left
okay gentlemen don't worry I got shot
and I'm in a bad way now I am that's the
Tiger
okay you want me to turn you facing him
uh either yeah yes please yes please
keep pushing and help my repairing I can
watch watch droids be watch straight out
honestly can help you repair
16 more eyes and put them all around you
guys because they're all coming
all right I'm gonna turn towards B yeah
I'm gonna open the Centurion heels nice
enough to cover me okay
hello tiger two are you still in here
he dropped smoke over here to my right
that's the canister so I don't know
where exactly he is
uh M51 is down
next to us
friendly bombs I hope so
yes they were it just killed a Waffen
breaker
I didn't even see him over here
yeah he was
he was he was right over there I think
about him right there something else
right that's the tiger too thank you
I'm so glad we got rid of him
yeah that's the guy we were looking at
um I'm kind of exposed here sorry yeah
run run back to us I think he sent Bush
Bravo what's this break Tank's right
Tank's right shooting right yep on the
way on the way reloaded I'm not I'm
stuck out being a friendly repair so
I'll be with you momentarily I took his
tracks we can't move out yep
hi okay he's down he's down he's down
yes who wants to go to Bravo
it'll be great I promise uh sure I'll go
are you sure
I I shouldn't make any promises
I just want to leave the a factory
let's transfer to the B
The Beef Factory
three factors not as cool
I hear something but I know what they're
shooting at
I'm gonna try to help these guys
yeah there's still a lot of the enemy
team left what's that from was that left
uh there's enemies around the corner
right over there
is it through here
yeah yeah it's in there no no no yes oh
my gosh thank you
for 151 yep
I knew I heard him in there and 51s were
out in force today man I'm now
recognizing the exact like noise of the
M51
you've had you've seen that many
you just got shot I'm gonna close my
eyes tonight and see m51s zsu-57 to your
right oh my God no rotating around
no no it's it's in front of you
in front what start right right right
right right right rear shot
he's down left in the gap
left there yep there's something in
there yep copy
push number towards you yeah I'm Gonna
Keep reloading yep let me know when
you're loaded
I'm gonna just make sure there's nothing
like else
hiding in those bushes there
all right taking a peek
one of them died I don't know if there's
anybody else in there
I I didn't see any more only that this
young gonna make a crossing here
he wasn't sure if it was one or two so I
didn't want to make a bad call up there
I figure it's safer say something's in
there than you know yeah then to you
know I'm not gonna say something in
there yeah because you know there's one
or two or three or four things hiding in
there yeah or a whole bunch of m51s yeah
and then 51 that's yep you almost have
little eyes in your tank from where
everybody shot you I have shells
everywhere we'll get the top I got shot
on top of my yeah you got shot on top of
your tank
got like why is everything like but it's
a take me oh my God look at look at the
face of that little a that little a
oh my goodness that's hilarious
that's great I love that
you never want to come back here again
you don't want to go to the a factory
again come on Stick it'll be great just
like last time
that is a very satisfying
nice Bill Cannon when you fire it
uh yeah follow the milk trucks lead get
him is this 12 oh my God this is
supposed to rain out in front of the
King Tiger oh my God he just ran out in
front of them I looked away for one
millisecond and he was gone
we have to we have to be I got the King
Tiger
Walker Bulldog is down Nice kill that's
all the targets I saw over there okay
I'm gonna back up three Loop for a
minute yep
hey stick you wanna take your uh fancy
turreted tank and look left yeah just
make sure
thank you
look at that little this look at that
he's got a turret who's this 12 truck
it's our hero right there we'll have to
build a monument and his heroism for his
Brave right now in honor of this is Bob
he was
great little milk truck his leadership
was undeniable he should he is what all
milk products should aspire to be gone
too soon our hero is
where
where is the bad guys that Bravo is the
question now
um
he spoiled their advances
he really curdled their cheese
we can go places with us if you want God
please
oh come on fate
Tanked
yep uh I'm gonna watch our back don't
let our jokes spoil your fun oh all
right well God was gonna watch her back
I think I'm just gonna leave it exposed
now
um
for the cream of the crop
I'm jaying out okay I'm sorry I'll stop
it's somewhere back here Lefty still
firing
or well he died is there another one
you're not getting the points there's
definitely someone over there
oh we're taking it now
you must have just he must what was that
that was from White behind behind behind
the hill
I'll give you mark in a second it's at a
way back during the corner over here
I have the church in my way yeah
somewhere back there there's one hiding
no eyes
I'm not crazy he is there are you sure
they need
he's back there he's hiding
I think Paul might have got enough I am
not I'm not crazy
here just push it with me we haven't
surrounded he can't go anywhere I hear
the enemy pushing my side I I don't
really
I'll be honest here Nick I promise you
there's a tank back here
just gotta take his word for its thing
just tell him yes and that'll make him
feel better just do that
okay where is he hiding I hear him
he's behind this rock I think
can you get behind that rock
hold on I'll let you know are you
calling him fat
okay some yeah there see he is real he's
right there I knew it he took my Barrel
like I'm in trouble he's real if you
look at that
when I'm in a second it's actually 30
because I have to repair my Barrel I
hope he's he's gonna push his knee hey
hey Bo I see him machine gun sorry I I
had a milk he's so fast no no please
please be gentle no please don't
I thought we were gonna win that
engagement
one delivery of close Air Support I'm oh
hey I'm sorry if this goes wrong but I
will do my best oh my God he's budging
bomb is out hope that's good for you hit
him
that hit him he's down that hit his face
that landed right on him thank you for
that anything else on fire I got two
more bombs you got any Targets I I don't
know there's something scouted coming
out
um over towards C but I am just so
elated with how good that plus air
support was the thing that scouted is uh
the thing that's killing me so I'm gonna
go ahead and drop my bombs on him yeah
go ahead and get rid of him
who bombs for him
yeah this is Revenge or something on
fire
Nice kill the fire is getting worse
uh yeah there's also a plane up
themes I found the desert
you found the desert found you again
[Music]