honestly the con St there's a mouse to
your mouse is
down I'm really surprised that shot took
from the weird angle I put it over you
into
him I just saw nothing but fire at my
face all right well that was that was
interesting to come around the corner
too I thought it was an EBR for a half
second and then realized no that's way
too big and then all of a sudden you and
it has a really cool like Grill on its
roof I didn't get to see that but yeah
it does back corner that back corner I
see a lot of marks over there
too ow a turret just flopped onto me I
think that was
mine do you want to go right I do want
to go right let's good let's do that
especially after having Zoot head hit me
he was just giving you a heads up well
there's two right there I'm going to
take the left
one I just got the track on the other
one okay what was the thing you saw
otherwise machine gun it yeah I machine
gun it it was a
t114 I'm going to watch behind us Mark
right there
pushing I can take him in a second I'm
waiting to reload there one there's one
in Smoke by the way no that's bad
[Music]
bombs imagine that the year is 1989
you're a young Russian man and you just
work very hard to graduate from Soviet
tank
school and you think you might go to a
fancy t72 unit but instead they gave you
the t10m the dinosaur of the Soviet tank
force what is your reaction you know at
least I'm not likely to get sent to the
front lines anytime soon it's crazy that
these things were in reserve until like
what 1995
1996 yeah it was the early ' 90s
basically up to the end of the Soviet
Union that's absolutely
crazy because these things are
essentially what the last is variant
that was created in effect yes I mean
for its period it was incredibly
Advanced it was about as far as you
could realistically take the heavy
breakthrough
concept I mean it's really not a bad
second lane
think no not not for its intended role
it's just that the MBT concept just
supersedes it yeah the Abrams and the
leopard have something to say about that
Leopard 2 in
particular
yes I mean would you want to be driving
t1m against those things the Leever to
no I'm I'm good I'm you know we're
talking about a retirement date in the
'90s that that would be the kind of
thing you'd be up against hi stms I'm
following I guess you now cuz I don't
know where where the enemy is so you're
telling me that it's been leaked that
this map is up for a revamp they were
upset that not enough people were going
to the Sea
Depot um well nobody likes the sea Depot
well you know that now now we have too
many
se's everybody's going to the a factory
and it's not got enough output and we've
got we've got 300,000 tons of unused C's
so they're closing down the a factory
because it's too profitable and too
popular to focus on a product that
nobody wants correct because they have a
surplus on it I mean look at see right
now like there's one of our friendlies
down there and he's leaving it this
sounds like a Disney executive decision
you got to get I I would I would CR up
as many A's as you can before it's too
light so I can make a a sorry that was
terrible that was a horrible joke I know
that was pain I won out of here now I'm
I'm not actually going to go to a now
I'm going to go to the other letters but
a is awesome and you can have an
adventure there good luck with your uh
clearance sale at a you could be really
ambitious at the a factory I want to go
to the C Depot now I just want to use
words that start with a see myself out
of
here the Rell and this are having a
battle yeah and it took my engine I
heard about five battles happening
couple tanks marked on this
side it's a reton again it's the 19th
usof happening over there you always
talked about opening a restaurant on the
sea point in
Vietnam what does it serve there
Seafood no it serves um clam chowder
smoked
brisket stop trying to get a reaction
out of me I know what you're doing I'm
trying trying to ignore
you thms I love how you just took that
to the face and never let off the
accelerator well I just I'm going to
protect you until you're
ready he's down thank goodness we have
zo the destroyer of worlds I totally
Panic fired dead center of him because I
didn't know what he was and I was a
stair fight from your your screen I
can't
talk honestly I'm surprised it didn't do
more that was a really big explosion
I'll push first this time I will
probably left the accelerator I'm not
dedicated as you are to the
cause I mean I was either going to die
or he was going to die fair enough the
rules on these Mean Streets of wherever
we are that's them rules yeah that's
them rules there was a bunch of marks
over here a minute
ago so I prepare either close right or
straight in front of us affirmative but
good news our lack of bar impression is
going to make this much harder yeah I
just apprciate the challeng cops is
there there is I'm going to attempt to
peek right if I
can way I just see scrap
metal it's an S tank I see the Str
strv i' been shot from front I got the
transmission on the strv Jes
I see him I got the Gunner it's just
nothing but pain term you want smoke
Thor you want
smoke does your body want smoke I died
there's a crappy fridge
helicopter yes the body wants smoke I to
repair smoke is out that's I would keep
reversing if I were you he took my
engine well here's the
ttmm attempting to save the fancy
is7 wow I'm pretty sure there's probably
footage of that out there somewhere
you're fancier out of a ditch or
something you're an is7 you are much
fancier I that necessarily mean it's
fancier I don't know it's pretty fancy
does anybody have a bearing on the
helicopter or last known all right uh it
probably crashed of its own accord it
was an h34 you really do not like the
helicopter it's a h35 there nothing to
like you're just saying it because
you're British and it's anything French
you immediately start attacking so you
stay have that conversation
wait he's still up he's still up I
repeat I see him thank youf 105 down
that's terrifying he's behind you he's
behind you he's SL behind you what okay
rotating rear your yelling does not make
me play any better it just makes me play
more
frantic can you get it pring the hill
it's right on top of us right on top of
us I do not have a shot I I do not have
there got him any more
bullets oh actually he broke the gun
that's why what happened I will come
repair oh no no I don't need uh fancy
technicians like you do for your thing
oh my bad
wow techicians either he just needs 16
Gunners to help reload those machine
guns can you imagine that you have to
out of the that was uh quite
spectacular I if I went up I was going
to get shot I went down I was getting
shot I went down
anywhere pushing back to the path of
despair tears did we ever kill the S by
the way uh no CL yes uh something shoot
me front I lost the track oh no that's
the Str strv right
there no that's the different one yeah
he took my
breach I do not have an angle fire that
body I took out one of his barrels serms
he wanted adamant so I think you're
going to get your challenge on this one
ow yeah no I got it I I
I good
I'm proud of you thank you I've been
practicing can I get that repair team
again I'm going to start charging you
now you can make another tank
another I'm very concerned about the
amount of fire happening in front of me
also
playe Thor this is your fault it
is that would be your last words Thor
this is your fault he called me back to
repair him and the second I started
repairing him couldn't move a bomb
landed on me so my last words will be
very spiteful that's just how I roll I'm
sorry right leopard one I'm trying to
push for
it I'm almost there get anything got I
got nothing he's running he's down all
right let me help you repair if I can
thank you I'm going to look directly
behind
us actually let me spin all the way
around just in case yeah y cuz I have
this fear that everything from a is
going to be marching down this direction
a second I think you could be right all
right there you go um I hear them to my
left your left is our right
correct I hear a lot of engines uh Tom I
did nothing to it let's get out of here
I'm pushing
them okay I'll push
around let's go this way term's over
here left
okay there's one Gunner on him he's
down thank you I'm I double back
I'm half reloaded I think there's
more the nerve-racking thing about the
T10 is your loader is frantically trying
to put another shell in knowing that
death is ENT because a heat shell or uh
missile are inbound any second so STM
the more reason she gets upset is
because I buy them right before
Christmas or my birthday and then she
doesn't know what to give me are we
talking about cookies or magic
cards magic cards SL
Miniatures and and
cookies yeah cookies make great
Christmas presents they
do especially for people who have stuff
it's always fun to mention magic cards
or models when she's nearby because he
immediately gets very very scared and um
fearful defensive yes wor that she'll
see the he purchases next to his
desk listen she hasn't spotted them yet
I'm I'm you actually have you actually
hiding models under your desk right now
not
they are still there from when I sent
you that photo can you hear the tone
of's voice getting
defensive
yes she she's not even like privie to
our conversation and he's already he
already has Max fear they are they're in
plain sight no
[Music]
hidden mhm I think the TV5 is calling
for help on the North
side oh yeah I see why I I see why
oh the hold up on a small Convoy right
there my tracers are I see
it also there appears to be a plane or
helicopter yeah I ricocheted off of him
I got you okay I tried to say I got you
and didn't didn't have you I I got his
bre if you want to try to finish yours
in the field deal with this guy you got
him he's behind the building I can't
move I need the one on the right take
him down before he
and on the right's dealt with left is
down the plane is down was the vdar
dealt with at any point in the chaos of
the moment I thought this was a tank for
a split second had to process it because
I don't remember anything saying there
it was the turret of the guy from
before just didn't remember anything
being in that
spot also it's way too quiet now well
yeah cuz you just killed everyone you me
take it or you work on your adant take
him take him take him I'm going to take
the left one good that one's SE her
still I'm going to try and break his
tracks he's tracked how many more hits
do you need we're going to help you get
this challenge I'm still reloading so I
can't help you anyway almost there what
is close right I took his Barrel okay
I'm going to push it's a VOR it's a VOR
it's aor do not push I got the driver
transmission on him let's get rid of
that one he got my track he's going to
reload I'm also
tracked I am trying to get him a worse
angle he's just sitting right there he
has both my tracks in the building just
collapsed one to his
right target right there that one's dead
H I got to get around you I got to get
around you no worries close right there
what is
it I don't know I'm getting ttis in my
right ear hio you're a very noisy man
I'm suppressing him want you he wants
people to know that he's here Mark right
there I'm going to up your Pa thank you
uh you you may need to flank around
little PT 76s and get
him good job D how is uh the left
looking I don't know I haven't been
paying attention at all I've got R and
lost the track
again uh left is not good and right
there's stuff coming back from their
spawn I'm sorry I've been shot
right okay Mark right there through the
building through the building yeah
unfortunately I still can't move that is
a tiger I just hit I think it's a porch
tiger too it is I'm out of ammo in the
auto reversing okay I'm pushing I'm
pushing all right well we are just uh
having a party in here God I thought
that Lorraine or the S was an enemy is
everything dead in there no probably oh
God directly in front of me can you help
him z uh yeah it's the it's the uh the
the non slow one I found a
mouse uh I'm
gone that's not good you're all gone
yeah I just got hit by a tiger 2
H okay I don't know what to do here I
don't have a plan for
this well I'd say escape and we will
meet you H's going to Stand My Ground
okay yeah that was yeah he's close in
front of me that's close enough to my
advice oh there's your tiger to friend
and my shell just detonated on a porch I
think so that was very disappointing and
sad that poor person post I've ever seen
on a
porch actually it's probably just uh you
had an overly sensitive fuse I'm sorry
oh it's you're talking about the Soviet
quality was not good enough uh it's what
I'm suggesting a fox has charged into
the battle is it a friendly Fox yes yes
the fox is gone all
well he died like he lived what did the
fox say nothing but terrified screams as
they drove into that battle terms on
sorry I didn't see that until it was way
too late tank pushing right there he's
going have a shot on
me yeah heavy tank is I think it's
another t32 in the
water I guess I'll swim after
him
startd oh if you want to sit up there
zoit I have no choice in the matter if
something's uh is something shooting you
oh yeah it's right there at the M48 okay
I'll be back in a second
if you can hang on that
long uh me and the t32 are going to play
slap fight I'm going to push him around
to you if you have a shot please will
free take if you can okay just what
threatening make threatening gestures at
him threaten attacks them or something I
don't know steal his Museum things put
your arms up make yourself look
bigger me steal his
culture
dang he's pushing
I'm so glad there's a dock there that is
preventing a firefight from
happening uh Thor that's all yours he's
reloading I'm looking for other targets
they going to creep up on us his track
is
taken I've got one back here
scouted oh there's one high hello m103
on the Rocks I repeat m103 on the Rocks
M 103 on the Rock that's not a drink
either th I hope you're winning that
fight the t32 I'm I'm winning the fight
it's just taking a lot of rounds to win
Sterling did not win his
fight
gravity I'm also going to uh admit
something I scouted that t32 before you
killed it because I I wanted the credit
for scouting
it there's no shame in there not because
there's any reason for Intel or helping
the team our friend is still there uh
something just hit me and ricocheted off
no clue where you're in a PT 76 was it a
BB
gun it might have been did a child throw
a rock at you wouldn't surprise me did a
bird fly over and crap on your tank what
what doesn't pin a
bt76 whatever a shot fall
apparently a particularly tall wave oh
tall
wave a strong dust of wind I'm afraid to
pushed him now I hear it to my right
it's in the building yep
I'll try and help you if I can it's an
M48 I shot
over I wanted to make sure it was dead
so I shot it twice it ricocheted off me
twice oh how your PT managed to Ricochet
two things Russian
bias yeah is in full effect no his
little splash guard is open that's what
it was no they're on the
turret have an AA here the hit box of
the splash guard saved him oh
bombs NOP
by you know it's a shame that there's
not two vehicles roaming around with
anti-aircraft barrels that could have
stopped that oh there's three Sterlings
back in spawn I was repairing a truck
thank you very much uh behind
me oh by an M18 no less plane the
plane's maneuver kill I'm calling that
maneuver
kill well you can uh draw that on your
Barrel in the afterlife there's about to
be a fight over here
I took the a first there's going to be a
tank behind
this somebody wants to try and flank it
that might be the best idea flank it why
flank when we can just drive directly in
front of it well there's also things to
the right I haven't told you about
yet okay that would have been handy to
know wait you're withholding information
he just fired that would be the I didn't
know about
left left is down uh there's a little
something coming behind I got shot from
front front yeah he's pushing
me I'm just pushing we're going all in's
down one on me right here close another
yeah another light tank in there hey
right there I'm getting a
massage I'm I'm reloading still oh no
worries no worries I will sit here and
do what I can for
you I'm actually going talk
repair there is one more back there
behind
this I think just be aware of it i s I
thought I saw it on the map I don't see
anything two or three I don't know how
many that was kind of a blur what just
happened the whole action is just sort
of you know 3 seconds of chaos the other
one Charlie's
down but there's still a df15 out there
somewhere I think sturms there basically
is a Hut of bodies over here yeah you
can be like one of those uh bugs that
covers themselves in ant horses oh what
yeah what f
I don't remember the name I think it
might be a type of assassin bug assassin
bugs
yes is this like a weird sequel to bugs
life I don't know about um it would be
the dark gritty
reboot also where was that thing that
just took you I see it uh he's heading 2
about to be he's down I got him thank
you I thought he was further on the
right
side no I was still heading to you you
guys and he just I wor that was a bad
angle for you you have those
Powers we're sick boy I'm going to say
the terms of agreement just
changed I regret coming over here to
help you I wish p and I had to say it
even though he's not here can we
terminate him now well look at Tor just
did you see that it's catching on
[Music]