what does the a factory make people
asbestos I was going to say aspirations
but I guess that works too well why
would they make aspirations in a
factory because the Soviet people are
counting on the factory no they have to
learn to live without those kind of
things aestus will keep them warm we
we'll we'll save meso for another time
you heard that History Channel ad so
many times as a child well you
have burn ads
that like random disease is I swear the
most televised disease
ever I can close my eyes and see the
text crawl next to
lupus wait you had lupus
ads no he saw it in house no my family
kept watching house on repeat that makes
more sense and they talk about lupus
like every other episode and how it
isn't lupus I swear it was every episode
to be honest terms
so the a factory doesn't make people
happy and hopeful no there are very few
factories that I think actually have the
byproduct of making people happy what
about the Lego factory that's not true
stms the Lego factory the McDonald's
chicken nugget Factory nobody's happy at
the McDonald's chicken nugget
Factory imagine Happy
Meal so who votes for a sick to keep
going
first I'm going to help this uh
t55 wait there wasn't there was a vote
for me to go first yeah I thought that
was just assumed yeah everybody voted on
it Target moving right
there this cannot be undone t55 is okay
for now but Situation's kind of
dynamic I'm glad I fear for
him got one STM I'm going to use my
reload to
repair I could try and push up and help
you guys or you think you're good over
there uh where more or less good serms
is really the only one to get shot
you've got one in that building right
there CMS you keep getting shot you
might want to back up he is mighty
is4 I'm dying he was mighty
is all right s how can help you uh
there's one behind this BM cop looking
for
himms looks like an AMX
30 coax 20 STS t54 hard left down the
wall of the other uh Factory building
yep yep I see where he is now it's in my
kill feed from where he killed me
oh I love the Sass that you got after he
died and it wasn't aimed at me for once
and I'm truly smiling plenty the Knight
is still young my information came from
the kill cam as
well I'm going to harm this M18 I was
fight now I was just slow I was so
tunnel visioned on trying to push up and
help you guys so you both
[Music]
died you know I like the is4 but if I
could change one thing uhhuh I know what
it would be strv right
there all right there'll be two things I
change okay it sounds like you found a
new one yeah
me oh no that one's the easiest to
change uh there is a little guy causing
Havoc right there okay
actually I have a plan if it'll
work he's just sitting right in that
corner he just bled our
t55 thms hard left in the
corner hard left in the corner yeah in
the yard by the
pipes you know what I'm talking about
does he have the pipes to sing
though can we drop him off
somewhere and just not tell him
why do you sound like a parent who's
tired of their kid and wants to drop
them off his daycare ter what is
happening in there well I'm getting shot
um there's a zsu 572 yep I see him he's
gone he exploded violently never to be
seen again I'm going to repair this Ste
I've lost everything that I held
dear you haven't lost
me okay awkward silence I understand
starting to feel bad about myself thms
I'm Target right there on the yep I see
it I see it I see it I got to get on St
side so I get
shot wow that's I'm not I'm not fast I'm
sorry I'm pushing it it's like the
moment you said shot the the round flew
through the air it's like he saw the
future but was delayed in it I'm in is4
everything's
delayed I'm over on this corner
now okay stick away I will now attempt
to fix you they're on this wall Hing
around just it's just a track if you
want to go help him watch right there
watch right there he sounds like he's in
a very I'm trying to warn you to so you
stay alive we're both looking at
it I don't trust you who you can't save
me I you're death I know you don't trust
me B that is perfectly fair and very
good on the track targ but you can trust
thurling no I can't Target right there
and Target two Targets there I tried to
push on help they're swarming over here
and I'm sucking a very bad spot
am I getting bombed I think somebody
else got bombed it's an army of small
things over
here yes there is t92 and something else
with him that's not so small I'm just
going to try and push left yeah there
appears to be a heavy tank and like
three
light just be like the daycare worker
Wrangle all the small
ones yeah I think I make a terrible
daycare worker you would but in this
case they don't need to survive their
day thank you so much for the that bomb
teammate big guy back here is Cannon
barreless okay or without Cannon
Barrel I am almost to you I'm going to
push and finish him because I don't want
that thing to have a chance yeah yeah do
it do it uh can somebody finish c b yeah
I'll get on to
B hi there I am slightly sorry for this
but I'm going to go through your machine
gun
Port all right he's done excellent
anything else over here there was a lot
there was a t26 but he got taken care of
and then there was a couple others
pushing from the a side that might still
be
active okay hi I am uh going to join you
here I'm repairing my machine gun well
do the infamous L-shaped defense
maneuver
yes and I'll help fix you I'm good thank
you
okay do we want to push back towards a
um but do we can we really get a the
question maybe we want to try and push
to
C I think Stick Boy calls the shots all
right you you hear the Pan's voice
immediately he's like oh no
responsibility I I didn't think about
this I why would you give me responsib
where are we going you have to choose
now because B technically already choose
to
you I'm taking the new one one close
right right there small one thank you so
much I was more scared of that 109
pushing
yeah I was too I was about to blast
him be fair I didn't see the t92 I just
saw the 109's
barrel okay around the corner you look
like a lost person at a grocery store
looking for their
parents in a way he is why are we going
towards a because you never said
anything protect the verbal
wind
oh I didn't want to go to a but B keeps
driving to a well we don't have a there
now I'm out never have a hard
left shot no good stick it's on you
verbal in head just popped on top of you
yeah and it was right it my shot made it
vibrate it did not go well I
bounced okay I'm going to push to the
left if you want to hold him there okay
I will attempt to hold him here I just
want to make sure they don't go around
us you got that t26
right yes 100 he has a friend he has a
friend he has a friend
do you need me to flank
around uh you won't be able to flank his
friend so maybe just hold on for a
second see if his friend keeps pushing
I've got one over
here the t26 just got bombed Ser you got
bombs I have a bomb can you drop your
bomb right
there onto pushing me this is the worst
thing I you know how far away I am right
I do but he has no transmission so he'll
be stuck there for a bit I got multiple
things pushing over here stick I'm back
with you I'm back with you the off a
little bit let him push okay onos right
there one back my God yeah don't show
yourself to the
onos where's the target you want a dead
mark it again he is sitting right
there well there's something driving I
see the machine guns I'll handle onos
I'm trusting you oh I take your shot
I okay I took that one you take the onos
okay that
works I think that went too early bom
okay thank you so much ter no that's
perfect bad news he is so angry at you
does he have any shots left the the
right side the right side barrels are
shot out you should be able to get them
I'm still reloading I'm just trying to
push him
back he's down good work I figured
aggression was the right call
there okay I am looping around I don't
even know what happened between you two
uh mostly name calling it's a lover
squirrel the sheriff and the stick
boy there's a scorpion I just hit him
I've injured him grievously thank you
I'm
looking I think sck also another small
one stick Bo is bringing something to
get his revenge from me scorpion died no
I to do something and instead it bounced
and just H the right side of all of his
barrels well I mean that that did
something I'm going to mark it on map
for team I see it that's a big American
Heavy I want him to push
that was loud was that your shot to hit
me first uh I did not hit you but I hit
him something came from the sky and I
think I jumped a little that's what I'm
going to say that's fine that's fine
just realize that the thing in the sky
helped you I appreciate it thank you
very
much thms if something never mind thank
you I got shot from front uh
stick okay I'm getting the plane that's
on sur's tail off him quick oh it just
bombed you I should have been
quicker I do not have a barrel or tracks
now and I'm
stuck sick I was uh very sad to see your
name in The Kill feed just now I'll tell
you that that's behind
you uh that's unfortunate I I'll try and
do something about that no worries I
just need to get the one all the way
down there off me for
now B is going to be contested here
shortly
sticky s us behind me towards a it's on
the main road um I see it headed towards
B so that be right where I
am never mind I was firing at another
scorpion there is another scorpion I'm
attempting to get him Bo but I'm just
giving you a head on the behind you
behind you where that uh heavy tank that
I hit was there's a scorpion turning
around you oh I am angry now
got the Gunner on him good
work there's one right on me I can hear
it Canon Barrel out on it stick I need
your help with this I'm oh my good okay
he's a big boy he's a big boy up to
you that is not what you said it was I
that's cuz I don't think that is what I
was trying to imply I think that's
something different Stick Boy Called
died to something else the thing that I
called out phoned me
again oh it's on the point oh cool he
turns highways and I broke his track so
now we're just both stuck
here machine gun each other uh bo he
might have a friend
soon we all have I wish I had a friend
here soon I'm sorry it's unfortunate but
there will be no friends coming to your
position in the near future what if I
had a friendship token he just Jed out
which I'm very thankful for but also not
because now he di sideways get out it's
going to take some t92 across the way at
a
okay well this is going to take some
problem
solving turn you this
Direction come on keep keep com this
direction this didn't go as well as I
thought it would no no you got this just
be aware there's a to the right of his
body
past good I guess I wouldn't expect
anything to be stuck behind this either
the t92 was last seen there
copy so he does not have a current shot
on your position but he is still active
and angry at existing I have the world's
biggest meat Shield many moons later the
is-4 was able to get free from his
slumbering
hole yes all is4s have very extensive
Slumber
holes it's a historic fact yeah that's
actually where all the current is4s are
except for the one that was pilled out
of its Slumber hole to be in the museum
I'm going to push a with
you okay that's risky but uh it is but
we need to get a cap Point that's a
closest one it is it is that was my
thought
too I'm dropping smoke and
going if they shoot me you'll have a
clue where they are I won't cuz I can't
see
you I will tell you where they are okay
with my last yell over my little bitty
radio I'll tell you where they are
uh we just lost the guy Bravo do you me
turn around and go back
yes s can you use your ghost to like
hunt B attempt to find something no no
just like yell scary spoopy sounds at
the at Bravo yeah oh make them think
you're a
ghost
woo okay I wow he's a really lame ghost
he is I didn't want to say anything but
I don't
know I got have you never have you never
wanted to be a ghost before sck boy no
being ghost would be so cool when I was
a kid I just want to be a
Ghostbuster no no the real money is
being a ghost there's no money in ghost
busting no that's sad to hear nobody
believes in
ghosts that need busting that's why they
all laughed at me when I said I want
anyway uh but if you're a ghost you can
charge people to like scare bad renters
out and
stuff all right there's a couple things
over here that one's very dangerous I
can't get the pt6 off the point he's
down okay good so now it's uh equal caps
here I'm very close to
a as I said that I knew I was about to
lose
it no no you got this you still got this
you got this I'm
reping uh I I don't really trust leaving
a
I would either I'll try to get Bravo but
there is a ban right here just waiting
to rip my face off gotcha gotcha I'm
also very close to a nuke so if we can
hold two cap points I can probably drop
it okay our pbv uh or I mean our friend
on B just got killed
copy I don't believe that the enemy is
on the point yet over here another one
came
in affirmative this end of me I'm
sorry maybe I get enough negative angle
here I can disappear
okay uh they hurting me immensely
so our teammate back there or you might
have to do this okay it just rolled on
to B I'm going to try and drive across I
have a very big repair and two Targets
over here I'm also being Saed think he
just charged me straight up he's on my
body that's so far from
me there's one
serms got that one
still out there though nice job
canceling that cap that just saved it
for
now good job over there3 down died don't
die to Bard now
yep I am rushing back in AA with a lot
of
ammo and I have Google's friend good
good I'm glad you have friends um as
soon as B's taken I'm going to try and
get back across to a because that is
probably where they're going to push
next
if we get on Charlie that'd be our best
bet too but that's a long it's just so
far away
yeah we don't really have the tickets to
spare right now correct I mean if we
lose two people two deaths is
enough I'm driving a giant
bomb we just lost one guy to the left
yeah to another bang
Cannon we just lost two teammates right
there at the end
yeah I mean that's the risk of low of
letting the tickets Get Low like that I
mean they did a good job pushing both
caps the entire time so it wasn't like
we could just easily run onto either one
of them no no and then me getting stuck
behind t95 for a good amount of time
probably wasn't also super
helpful no no but there wasn't a lot you
could do about
that don't get kidnapped by t95
kids yeah it's not
recommended I feel like stick took off
to do his laundry or
something oh no he might be broken down
in like Purgatory or something
Purgatory yeah it's a he goes there a
lot I think his computer actually just
crashed oh great uh do you see yeah so
we need to somehow plane coming
in those are bombs don't worry it's
bombing somebody else ax50 no it's
gone there's only so much we can do I'm
going to push up and protect stick if
got Le one never mind I'll leer one's
good though
I don't think anybody's good the
Centurion is behind one of the buildings
just tucked in in the shadows I'm still
reloading s is getting shot I have to
try to save him you don't have to no I
have to I mean he's effectively bright
his tank is now brain dead there is no
one
home I can still defend and there will
never be anyone home I don't know what
to do for him let him die use him as a
shield I took a shot for him lost my
Barrel
parking him I died so he could live
longer
okay Bo I just need you to understand
that I would never do that for you I
felt bad for trying to push up and take
shots and find the thing earlier for you
but I at least one to try to be a good
team was alive I understand I was just
trying to do the nice thing okay he's
still alive down there there's still
hope no no there is don't give out F
Stick
Boy heam May fix this computer
yes he might get it online get
everything back up and then manage to
rejoin the match before he dies you know
he's making a snack right
now I mean he is probably using the
opportunity for it to boot back up to do
that you see that Mark to close to him
two Targets yes multiple actually one's
down they are dying I mean there is a
chance that he survives the match it's
slim but uh operation protects stick
boys a go
I mean that's your operation that's my
operation okay okay I need a purpose
that's my
purpose cuz that's my purpose right now
tun on airplanes going to
try something's marked in between those
buildings but I can't quite see it
yet okay over
there but also something Mark closer to
stick tank destroyer looks of it
yeah there's also a light tank
approaching his position pretty quickly
XM 800t I'm trying to get
there there's I3 kind of we're watching
him I was hoping he um all right he's
launched Warth Hunter so there's a sign
of
life I'm totally not spying on him oh
wow he's connected Hello Stick hello you
are still alive can you get into the
game quickly how am I still alive
Bo decided to sacrifice his life for
your brainless tank other tanks are down
here protecting
you why now when you come back please
don't complain that you've driven into a
house the house has kept you
alive here I'm I'm moving you in fully
now mostly because the enemy team
believes that you are dead how many
people have sacrificed themselves saving
me uh don't ask you really don't want
that answer
but you're Al why have people sacrificed
to save me cuz in a war you need a cause
also you're quite jiggly maybe that's
why oh my God and your tank likes to oh
should probably Focus On Target on
Range st's one right
there I think it might take it it's a um
MBT of some sort light one 1960s or
70s that's that's what I got for you
position
went into that hole over there I do not
have no no visual welcome back oh my God
I am hello how many repairs do you have
uh only my breach is
gone convenient at that oh hi I'm being
shot again for you hi I think i' I've
backed up into a wrong position Sho or
is your breach still I'm rotating my
turret I'm got 30 seconds on my breach
thank you
I'm repairing as well don't
worry Target right there Ser you can hit
it when I say you can hit me you can
kill
it nice work that one died so did my
friend that I came over here another
shot coming in I'm trying to Pi stick I
why your drive okay okay I'm repaired
let me go help go ahead Stick Boy drive
out there please don't die let me help
two Targets pushing up I took the first
one behind him on my mark
you might want to angle slightly more to
the
right all right I knew that was going to
happen I I knew as I saw it I just I
even motioned with my hand like I was
trying to direct your tank to
turmo that's a
Bigg I just I don't know what to fight
for anymore he
Tred uh storms one right there you
probably never mind you're gone too I
didn't just notice no I I uh was trying
to roll out I don't know if I want to
continue if I can
continue no no I'm on the way back on
the way back sadness you can well we're
too far into this match you can't give
up now I'm in is4 I'm on the way you're
you're a very strong Dependable tank
that's
questionable your centurion's
down
EXC I just like the other teams to
staring at me just waiting for me to
reload
two more targets marked to my front
right I'm coming to try and uh bomb and
strafe them yep I'd appreciate
that I don't know what just landed my
lap hopefully not a
bomb well there's a plane incoming I
think it has
bombs what is doing
that oh what if it's one of those little
rocket tanks and it's just like
something exploding it's so loud next to
me
I'm going to meander off over
here well that is the speed at which you
move yes
Meandering look at the is4 Meander to
the battlefield aimlessly
lost wondering where its friends
went I found it it is
a right there Sur that Mark I don't know
what it is okay I'm rolling back around
M48 so it's firing Heat at me that's
what that s was it's very loud it just
sounded like cannonballs exploding
around me I'm I'm back with you Bo I'm
here hi
hello there's things up to the front
right also things on Bravo if we want to
push that direction as soon as I'm
repaired oh we can put that I got the
tracks on the looks like an M48 they're
still please angle a bit more to the
right just a little more angle to the
right please
no I watch again
hey wow it was an M48
again I feel like I'm living in the
what's the movie called with Tom Cruz em
blunt the edge of tomorrow or the day
after tomorrow or the something tomorrow
tomorrow
yeah feel like that's what I'm stuck
in I mean what are they going to do take
a b29 and bomb us please don't say
things like that why would you speak
that into existence also stms I really
appreciate how he just peeed me and then
soow backed up into you yeah but I've
already shot
so I got the other one well I mean that
works all right so there was two
different tanks because I saw that one
look at me backed up I thought that was
I didn't know there was two I'm pretty
sure I hear a third yeah yeah no I I
killed the one behind him which I think
is why he backed up I'm reloading for a
bit so I'm going to sit here I knew I
heard a
third I will play I took his Barrel nice
work I'll cut off any Retreat you may
have he's he's just sitting
there he's accepted it I think
so okay well
um before the STS are
rightward would you like me to finish
this one then yes
please there you
go I got the one on our right stms we're
good okay rotating back I hope I did a
good job for you sir you did the tiger
dude just walked in going what did I
just went tiger 2 is not saying anything
anymore he's just he's gone Sil so you
should be able to kill it when you
reload I'm going to keep on you guys
though that's fine we're both reloaded
now I was finishing my reload gotcha do
we want to push a or just keep circling
and killing things well the goal is to
eventually end up at a behind me
affirmative rotating rotating rotating
it is a small thing they're
mine mine rotating I just SP the machine
gun around killed him demon spin the
turret all the
way he was covering bushes I didn't know
what it was I thought it was am90 or
something first fre out about a z I
didn't know what it was I'm
sorry feels like it was a little bit of
a it was not unnecessary Panic if that's
what you're going to say you saw
something in the night and it turned out
to be a squirrel a small bushy thing
sneaking up on ice4 is a very serious
threat uh-huh and some rattling in
off without us so I'm circling for the
thing killed the tiger to if he's still
over here I think he just
died uh he did yes I'm doing security
guard work that's fine that's fine I
just wanted to let you know that you're
alone I always knew you'd end up as a m
cop also you just described a trash
Panda to me and I'm not scared of trash
pandas I don't know you were pretty
scared about something covered in bushes
that were making I knew it had a
chemical round or an atgm or something
sick boy do you need tracks I do need
tracks do you have tracks I how did you
walk away with not having cuz I backed
up when I heard
him yeah see somebody was harassing me
and couldn't hear the plane coming in uh
there's one right
here oh yeah I see him yep he's looking
over at me he's looking over the top
right now thms you were short yeah but
he didn't hit me and apparently you
didn't I connected but it wasn't very
good you that sounds like my dating
life he took my
Barrel gun you took his machine gun I
did well it's uh really going to dampen
his
day I dented the glass on the
commander that work for at least
startled there's a smudge on the glass
now he has no
Barrel I'm going to cycle back over the
side okay going to try and grou back up
with you yeah let's go into this into
the town serms I'm going to be honest I
don't feel comfortable shooting at
distance things I don't have the skill
for it that's fine you just aim a little
more
up I put a little more mustard on that
hot dog before you send it I don't like
mustard on hot dogs
what do you like mustard at all buy
mustard that's the worst
mustard uh no I mean it's a pretty good
uh dipping sauce mustard
I don't like this conversation where's
the nearest off
ramp I mean I would not put it on a
sandwich or anything that's what like
real mustards are for yeah you put
mustard on sandwiches that's what they
go on like hot dogs yeah you can do that
I feel like that statement is ay is
really like fried chicken dips
yeah he just called a hot dog a sandwich
no I said sandwiches
I guess I did say like a hot
dog well Pizza is just an open face
Taco you're making a the hot dog bun is
still conjoined so it is only one piece
and therefore is not qualified to sand
[Music]
w