I just saw something horrible over
here I may need some assist thank you so
much there's probably more things I'm
going to smoke and fall back is it still
horrible don't go around that corner
it's awful you need repairs I just
watched the murder no I'm fine is
someone just fired at you again okay I'm
not so
fine hey
B I just got killed by a Rollin three
anti-air missile in my 2s3
8 and I thought I was having a bad
night did you just hit the pillar and
flip
over you got to come up with a better
story uh I don't have a better story he
was dodging missiles I oh okay there you
go drive along the wall here and you're
flipped oh that actually worked okay
well I don't recommend that because
that's kind of kind of cringe man
no all I said is I want to make a
professional intro to this video said
you wanted be cool like a real YouTuber
look all I want to do was talk about the
2s 38 and the upcoming the anniversary
cell right the one that happens every
year and whether people should uh spend
their hard-earned money on a 2s 38 or
not even the t72 terms or the tud I
assume all these are going to be
probably on Deep Discount um yes because
they are all going to be within that
period so if they do the high tier stuff
pretty much all of that's going to be
50% off right and we've never done a 2s
38 video it's been featured in other
videos but we've never done a 2s 38
video um the reason why I didn't do one
when it first came out was because I
felt it was extremely overpowered and I
tend to shy away from doing videos on
things I feel are just super op you're
broken stuff like that this was I think
this was very broken was first added and
that's why it kind of has
the reputation of just being dominant
since then and storms can go through the
changes on 2s 38 it is no longer the
dominant Beast that it once was when it
for Saturn it still has the potential to
be very good um and incredibly annoying
to enemies that face it but it's just
not as domineering as it was most people
have figured out how to deal with them
since you know it's been in the game for
what two years now um it it's definitely
been a tiger that has been declawed yes
it's still a great well it it's still a
great vehicle it's just it's not
blatantly overpowered any longer it's a
fantastic antire the hvt round is
phenomenal great at smacking helicopters
I have a quick clip I'll put in here of
that I mean oh God more expensive but
only because they come with a container
helicopter going to say isn't that your
job Mr it is it is it is sorry I had to
get rid of the shell I can't see him
through
smoke you mean the smoke of that down
plane I got a hit this thing's insane oh
sorry is my plane body causing an issue
I got a hit on him backing up this thing
is absolutely bananas the capabilities
of it helicopter's down it's really good
taking out mgs's ifes and tanks if you
get on their side the main problem I
think that happened to it besides the
changes they made to it in terms of um
it got more modules right they adjusted
the armor and the model they increased
the size of the ammunition to a more
realistic so there's just much more
stuff in it instead of it just being
empty space now other countries that
sping got a lot better the Germans have
premium leopard twos now the there's a
Swedish you know premium Leopard 2 out
there the Christian 2 and then there is
the um Boxer that was just add in the
event and that makes the 2s 38 life a
lot harder if you want the 2s 38 we
recommend getting it after you get a t72
AV terms or a tud or just unlocking
other Russian tin three things and then
adding this as a second or third or
fourth spawn to that lineup yeah it it's
not really first spawn material but it's
a very strong addition to any line line
up that you have in that BR
range 103 is very good because for for
the Soviets because they have a nearly
complete lineup to be made
there they have the Su
25k um and the t72 AV and the T8
UD which basically gives you all you'd
need but last thing I'll say say is
we're not going to do a premium buying
guide this year I don't feel like enough
things have changed from last year's
guide to Warrant a new one what we're
going to try and do between now and the
anniversary cell is put out videos on
some of the big Heavy Hitters that will
be including that cell so if there's
something that we haven't done a video
on in a while that you'd like to see
played I know we're pretty much planning
on doing a video on the vdar right and
then there is the the wyvern we're going
to feature again and any others you like
to see we'll try to put out a video in
between now and then so just let us know
in the comments what you'd like to see
and uh we'll do our best to try to help
you guys out and figure out what is
worth picking up if you're going to buy
anything in the sell well I actually put
in a request that we get more Bandon
Factory yeah that sounds like something
you would do B Factory is a place where
your heart goes and just
blossoms yeah it's where our dreams go
to die you craft things with your hands
that you can export to other nations
called
tanks no it makes
A's well the A's go on the tanks but
t72a where do you think they get the a
from no they do get it from here but
it's not specifically for tanks it's all
A's all of them that's a lot of pressure
yeah how do you think the ABS gets it it
has two wait so you're saying that the
Americans Outsource the a the two A's
and abrs to foreign sources Russia even
just like they do tungsten this is a
huge huge conspiracy you're unraveling
yeah there's a three agency outside to
your window right now I like to talk to
you my gosh the
ABC sure stms the ABC gang yeah the men
in black suits the alcohol beverage
center I take back what I said about the
a factory it is not as kind and happy as
I thought it
was is not not very much
not I even know what I'm fighing right
now it's a picture of a tank I just want
dead a picture of a tank
uh SI you just ran to a tank that was
the one that killed me I was looking at
the other side of the wall at a
different
tank yeah I regret saying all those nice
things about this
place isn't it your favorite you love it
here I do love it
here but I do regret it here as
well a I'm going to follow bp2
him what if he just died right now
please don't say
that it's okay he's probably
Immortal sometimes being P
are I don't think sometimes sometimes
they can
be thr that leopard two is down he
wasn't Immortal no I actually waiting
for him to push across there I have a
very bad plan here in a second if it
works the eny child is watching that
guy's flank yeah if you wait if if you
can wait a second
I don't know how many seconds are left
cuz there's one behind
me
scouted doing what I can oh it's pushing
you pushing you pushing you it's pushing
you the weasel VI use bullet on me get
back in there child I need some repairs
now that one's backing up scouting
again he is curious about what to do
with
me he is he's trying to figure out what
he can hit if he fires I'm going
unless he has teammates me I got to
watch look look more to your right
there's more interest no yes yeah don't
wiggle no at me yes this has to happen
You and I One V
one unless I can muster a teammate to
attack
you
the oh wait wait try and Scout him again
so that our yep people are firing him
he's still
scouted he's looking that way now
there we go pressure's being put on
him Barrel's gone Barrel out his
Barrel's out his Barrel's out and we're
going to take all the underneath
parts thank you team is that how you
describe when you're T underneath Parts
the L hold taking the underneath Parts
imagine if we get you hired on though at
the a factory stick all the benefits and
memories you can make
here
blown are you saying that these
buildings aren't good enough for you
well no I'm just saying that if I get
hired here it means they're trying to
reopen this plant which means I have to
rebuild these buildings oh somebody else
does
that yes but I would be in charge of the
networking
thms you think this place has
networking not yet it's suit can and
string yeah close lines it's actually
just one man yelling really loud from
one building to another yeah but who you
going keep that man's like throat filled
with water so he can keep yelling stms
that's a weird thing to say I was going
to say like keep the batteries and the
bullhorn but I didn't expect you to baby
bird another human being
didn't oh you're a bottle of water that
makes more sense I can understand why
you're hesitant to take the job did you
not know that that's one of the uh key
adaptations that the syrians did to that
model thms I am not amphibious I know
that for a fact no I not this will be
fun I am not
amphibious join us you cannot trick me
into believing this thing is amphibious
oh can we actually fit under that bridge
I didn't think this through if I could
be honest that's pretty
low yeah it it's really really low do
you want to turn back or oh Target down
the
road I'm glad our team has
it GL we have our amp72 here with us
don't I'm thms I'm trying to keep you
alive do you have your floaties on I did
not keep you alive also he did not have
his floaties on otherwise he would have
survived that if you're down here with
us you would have
lived I would have sunk no you float
those blocks on top of you they're not
ra they're
floaties
they're terms yeah this is a problem
isn't it okay so how's that bridge this
is my bad
a little awkward it's just a little bit
just uh just a
little I at least could do anti-air from
here yeah I don't know what you're going
to do be sad
mostly thms if you come back where you
jumped in do you have enough horsepower
to get out or would you need a
pull it's just kind of a sad thing to
turn around something is amphibious
we're not very fast I just have my
little splash
card yeah I have a splash card to it's
not quite as fancy as yours I hope the
viewers are enjoying this quality 2s3
gameplay they're experiencing right now
yeah I mean this is pretty much I have a
feeling we're going to get up to the top
of this and die we just won the true
experience of the military where we got
lost and then had the double back to
find the correct way to get to the fight
yep don't worry we'll be participating
soon no you won't I got the horizontal
tet drive on the Chinese MBT at the end
of the road I'm pushing up right now
temp to get
shot on
him he behind the burning corpse yeah
it's hard for me to see sorry yeah yeah
super limited
angles Dr back there though do you like
yeah if he Fires at me I'm going back in
the
river that's
fair you are so quick in that thing with
another 2
s38 uh M1 kvt is backing up from
something to your
right on some mark down there I see it
yep y y yep y I got a
gunner I'm going to go to left for
cover why would you
anger well stms has an actual like
proper Cannon I have an auto cannon that
guy just died I'm watching right
there or would you let me watch right
I'm going to watch forward still yeah
watch right I'm watching M1 kvt he's
pushing up again so hopefully he can
take that out
Guys across the river firing at the
enemies too
yep all right let's push up all right
there's a BM right
there or debris
pile I am not watch you guys they
modified these Bridges didn't they these
are these all feel than they used to be
okay but serm did they get much lower or
did the
water I'm sorry try to J I should
looking for
I didn't make it I was going to dive in
the river and leave
you I think the game uh frowned upon
that I was about to say like how unfun
is it to lower all the bridges where we
can't float down the river I know right
who made that
decision are we the same guy that blew
all the bridges for low tier I'm now
just going to go to random Eastern
European towns and measure Bridges oh to
see if this is the correct historically
accurate height I'm going to find the
average height of a bridge in Eastern
Europe and divide and we'll figure out
what it should be okay
okay but would wouldn't we also have to
account for the average water levels uh
year over-ear true it's going to get
complicated did raise a good point there
that it could be that the water level is
also raising I was about to say what if
it's flood
season I am flooding in pain did you
hear that besides the one that killed
him oh no I just turned his uh life get
snuffed out before my eyes yeah I killed
something
hey time
delayed we're getting we are can we go
first no I'll go
first I see a lot of smoke down the road
I'm going to tr I have some semblance of
armor I have autoc Cannon though you do
but I should oh right front I so glad
you killed that I fired off Panic he
just got hit by something else um direct
H front direct to front behind that guy
no eyes he's off the right I see him I
see him the building yeah if he pushes I
get him but he's holding back right now
gotcha I'm going to mark on map for a
stick who's in a AA I don't want to I'm
looking behind what are you in I'm in an
a I had hopes for a another 2s3 or
something I mean he's in a terms
te I'm in a terms
te okay did not expect him to push up I
was the disappointment I thought he was
saying you were um here comes the
bombs I'm going to go on anti-air for a
second that would have been appreciated
yes I'm sorry there was a ifb charging a
line as well I I understand I understand
there's AB on fire I'm trying to help
him if I
can this this this feels like you're
insinuating it's my fault you died
STS I didn't mean for it to be an
insinuation can you cover the air I'm
going to push back out I mean I I'll
try we're about to have tanks our lap
here I already have one where is it yeah
he's
got front of him on that way there's
also the
um some sort of wheel tank destroyer hey
there's a plane at heading 10 moving
right to left looks like the Chinese
four- whe one or I have something
revving behind this
building I'm just Wai for the well I
have good news I have a backup that I
can bring on my a boat behind you you
think he's behind me it's going to be
yeah I think it I think that's the uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah to your
right to your right to your right I got
my left hold
right thank
you let's this get
Rowdy I could not get in time the thing
behind me was also chasing me yeah I
just saw that guy starting to peek
around the corner so I appreciate it was
kind of boxed in there every time
tonight when you've asked me where do
you want to go yes I've done nothing but
get a
killed yeah I don't imagine that I'll do
much better but I feel like that
responsibility should be taking off my
shoulders just so that stick boy has a
chance to
survive oh that's sweet of you to think
that he had that chance look he's the
best of us we have to let the future
Prosper he's basically the sea turtle
hatchling of our
group don't say that as he's the last
tank I spawn I'm sorry second to last
there's still I'm just a laid ahe
sure he's the one to get smashed by a
tourist stepping on him yeah either that
or the seagulls will get
him it it shot past you to take me that
little tree that you're hiding behind
has completely camouflaged
you I have the worst luck tonight then
again I did paint my tank kind of like
neon green like a circuit board Mosaic I
think is the fancy word that artists
call
it that's actually what it's called I
think it's a digital Mosaic or something
digital Mosaic experimental Mosaic
that's fancy the the tree did not help
by the way no I got killed
immediately that tree gave you more life
than it gave
me well that's probably because I was
more camouflaged than you I actually
thought about diving into the uh water
there to escape what was going to happen
to me and I said no I will stay with
sterms I'll be a good teammate and not
abandoned him that was a mistake yeah
hiss now stick boy's out there by
himself trying to take the a point
without his sad mates yeah he's actually
doing a pretty good job he's last a lot
longer than the rest of us how much
longer you live on that
corner I mean how how many times are you
going to keep mentioning that I'm alive
on the corner you pushed that right
flank pretty good by
yourself feel to be alive right now uh I
mean it's fine I'm a little hurt a
little banged up but you know we keep
running we're going to know you alive
we're we're we're really going to hit
them hard on the second half you know um
if he lives longer than I do
again I'll be really upset I'm actually
diving into the water to hide even more
but I don't think there's a way up from
the water is the problem there isn't I'm
happy down here this is my life now good
job on the kill we're going to see a
little little a couple of lineup changes
you
know yep yep he's killing we take we
take the hits on the chin we build we
improve imagine the Vikings play like
that on Sunday oh they'd be undefeated
still way to beat a man down when he's
riding High got to keep him honest you
know got to keep him
humble so Bo if you regreted your
decision
yeah well if you can hold it long enough
there is a su2 and a little bird inbound
to your
location can we get some more ground for
no ground ground force is dominated by
wield destroyers right now can we hire
some
mercenaries uh what do you think you are
right now not a very good mercenary well
that's because you're a pirate not a
mercenary so not even a pirate this is
more like gilan's Island Russian Edition
happening over
here I don't know they showed some modum
of Competency on gillig Good's Island I
feel bad about our su2 he is his best
now but
there's that just fire from that corner
at
him there's something over there but
they won push the corner could have shot
I can't see him but I just saw the
missile come from that
corner you see how many marks were in
our spawn yes I feel bad about being
stuck down there but also I don't after
I
saw the circle of red
engulfing
spawn the massive
encirclement I think that Abrams is the
most aggressive real estate agent I've
ever seen is he selling real estate
right selling 120s to people's faces
right now over there I'm actually kind
of an
awe okay well I'm going to push to the
right and get away from
that horrific thing I'm
watching he's doing his job we can
support him though if we uh flank out oh
okay
support your local business support your
local Abrams make sure that they get the
resources they desire from the local
Village I got ared to death by following
you okay I feel responsible for that but
also uh I'm sorry I guess I'll apologize
tick you want to follow me I I mean not
really after have opening you're
directly apologizing for the death of
sturmling
like but that means job opening for
you yes but that
that job if you go with the abrs nobody
near him die you can be assistant to the
manager you mean assistant manager no
assistant to the
manager I also think there's a tank to
the front left that's why I've not been
pushing see where that Mark
was I mean I see the mark on the
map if you do a really good job we can
find you a house to buy around here I'm
sure they're uh in his budget prices are
fair reduced even is worble
use that was from your close left no
yeah close right it just kept pushing
along CL
right yeah okay looking at your mark I
don't see him you good up there I think
he might have just got taken down by a
teammate I don't know for sure though
yeah got hits on the r right in front of
you oh that's one right there close I'm
going to take barrel barrel that one's
out to your left I prair you right now
but I figure it's best for me to defend
you from back here no that's probably a
good idea it's only 20 seconds it should
be fine I'm going to push up and repair
you
now if you want you can push and kill
the one to the hard
left since you
repaired I'm going to watch the hill for
you yep let's go ahead and cross in
front of me and remember there you
go oh I've suffered a grief this wound
I'm
dead I feel like it's punishment to get
in the t72 after my 2s3 was taken out
immediately cresting hill by a spike
missile I'm been shot
you've been shot all from right
somewhere
right H my smoke grenade
launchers I'm not going insane am I well
I don't imagine you I feel like I'm
losing
it see I made it to you without is
nothing shot you something shot me and
it hurt me maybe it doesn't like you it
all it only does not like you
though or maybe my camo works better I
think I look very fashionable thank you
yeah if we were in a
desert okay I was telling about how I
got mistreated by a spike missile and
then you insult my
camouflage yes just h a man on every
level I saw what your 2s 38 was camoed
with so well now it's this charred
somewhere it is burn more camouflaged
see that Mark over there yeah I think it
just died it's
dead I think there's more to the right
though yeah right in front of you moving
uh right to left yeah but I don't have
an angle at it he's moving back the
other
direction we looked at each other I got
his can breach he got my Barrel okay I'm
going to try and push up get him I'm
going okay good thank
goodness 20 seconds for me
here I come like what happened to you uh
Tam decided I no longer deserve
life that happens sometimes Sams are
very powerful like that they
are terms that was from that direction
I'm not loaded
push I'll keep them off you
repairing yeah
started yeah he's just hiding back there
now s can you flank that Mark I made
from your side
sure I'll do it as quick as I can can
you watch out that direction just in
case cuz I'm very telev visioned on
right I'm let's let's move in together
you can't possibly kill both of us I
think they very much can and they very
much Happ if we line up like this like
tus
Raiders I'm going to push more into the
Rocks I'm very paranoid about your left
I would to
paranoid shot you I up on top up on top
the guy crawled to the top of the hill
copy saw his smoke uh s be careful maybe
baring down at you in a second oh okay
yep it is uh basically right in front of
me right I'm pushing I still can't see
him oh he's right there beside
me thank you got him he's behind that
rock yep good work
we're the best he says that as my t72 is
in a giant hole I'm trying to turn
around in we need to push back towards a
if we can
yeah what was that lever two
yep uh going to say yeah you got it I'm
sorry I didn't know he was there I
didn't see him either it's that camo
netting yep that's difference
[Music]
n