can you imagine being the office that
approves Soviet tank designs in 1930s
and early
1940s I mean you get a lot it's just one
stamp that says approved yeah we'll try
it that was their model they were
willing to try everything there's
something to our right by the way this
tracks already here I am very slowly
calling you okay well you now are
volunteered to watch right you may be a
tunnel route for
kv2 um do we have anything more suitable
look at this face it's a perate
Tracker yes that's clearly what it is if
you're a small tank hunting back here
and this face came around the
corner you would uh you would
surrender or you just die a fright I
think he's back here in the corner
anybody over
here did he just run into you and you
just casually shoot him there St yes
okay serms I'm not a great tat I don't
know where it is um well I found most of
them they're over here and they can
actually kill
uh stand by for a few more seconds if
you can put those two turrets to work
there you go one of the turrets that
explosion went over the buildings over
here you're
welcome
no I'm making my grand entrance how can
I assist you uh puma and Swedish Cas oh
Puma's gone and I don't that one's way
Zoo why don't you start off that one I'm
going to crush him this one's mine I've
got him for 15 15 minutes Crush smoosh
smoosh smoosh oh I killed you I'm sorry
Shucks more candy for me there you go
Crush I don't want to be here anymore
everything is suffering serm I need you
to push me where over here behind me
never mind he's gone thank you just
doing uh what I promise you I
do I appreciate and we took the try
Point without much dramaa yeah we only
lost killed a third of our combat Force
Z dead people don't talk unless you're a
ghost are you a ghost nice Halloween oo
spooky he's got a point he's got a
point is that you exercise a uh bag of
Earl grain and I just light on fire
smoke them out bombs those are
bombs I'm pushing to the coastline
become a defensive
gun KV two Coast Guard
Edition yes as it was famous for p
coming down the bridge and also one on
the bridge I'll take one on the bridge
first okay I'm going to push your way
yeah the problem is is I don't know how
I'm going to hide this thing since I
painted it Red Panther 4 up there is
going to hurt a
lot fighting crell thank you so much
Cromwell two Panthers over there serms
one on the main Bridge coming in going
Mark guy on bridge for teammate in case
he's not seeing it CU Kel is kind of
driving straight into
it I am pulling up almost loaded Panther
3M he sees me but he doesn't see cruml
he sees crumel two Targets on
bridge all right paner 3 is gone I got
the commander loader a transmission on
that thing nice work got it completely
we need to shift to other side right now
cuz they're moving around us
yep you came I came back where's the
candy you think I got candy for you
thether neighborhood you know what the
best thing about trick- or- treat at my
house is I uh take the dogs out and we
just put a bll at the driveway and then
we let the kids come up and pet the dogs
and the dogs think it's the best day
ever the dogs think that Halloween is
for them of course because hundreds of
kids come by and pet
them hey STM if you need something to
bomb there's a Panzer right here don't
ask how I know I I exploded in the air
oh there's so many of them Target Rich
environment and he didn't even notice
his friends's Di behind him of course
not milk truck is most powerful except
for artillery artillery is bad I
softened him up for you you cannot take
credit for softening him up for that he
did I watched him as I exploded those
are wise absolutely
wise I shot them I didn't get the kill
unfortunately but he just got three
assists
how does no
that's yeah yeah I I deserve a share of
the Halloween candy from that yeah he
does and I deserve a portion a smaller
portion of the Halloween candy for
verifying now I feel like I'm getting no
portions of candy here you're just
getting a substantially smaller portion
of candy this is why I don't like
communism but it's our
candy oh yeah start using that Wei word
like we're part of the team
see how that works
out terms it's your favorite map yeah
it's great potentially the last time you
see it before the
rework oh and even better aactor is
coming aren't you excited more a factory
it's going to be shiny shiny you know we
should do with the a factory since it's
empty right now and the points move down
to the middle what we can open a haunted
house with
kv2 first thing we should do at the
haunted house is put a kv2 with a
chainsaw
why because that's pretty scary it
doesn't have
hands just uh tie it to the end the
barrel yeah faic it's also very
important to take the uh chain off the
chainsaw huh
otherwise there may be a
lawsuit yes that that's the lawsuit
waiting to happen smoke uh no just it's
out here it's out
here nice shot okay other left further
left I think Sur just wants to die he's
just hitting W going straight in I was
hoping that other people we're not as
fast as you were
kv2 gentl there's a puma behind us
there's a puma behind us I've accepted
death going for
T14 one right there I'll try and repair
you there's a front of
me my track
anybody wants to murder veralin with
their bare hands I'd appreciate it I'm
at uh 70% loaded oh he's over
here s you went off to the wrong person
I was helping serms cuz he was repairing
while I was I'm trying to multitask with
the reload B it's not
working hold on I understand no I see
who your favorite is he was broken I
won't take that person one at all no I I
understand what's going on behind us
bomb behind you it's fine I'm dealing
with
it the decision was made for you
stick I'll see you later I'm just going
this way I told you to' be a haunted
house it's too spoopy isn't
it I just want to go home everybody
hates me right now and I love it so
much you're all trying to bite your
tongue and not say mean things you can
say mean things I'm okay with
it no look the only scary thing here is
your
jokes okay pun
Master look it's better to be punny than
to
be he got shot didn't you cuz I heard
that from
here that pause and that smack made you
got shot in the face no that was his
brain
buffering I got smed the one brain cell
just ran to the door at full speed
knocked itself
out there's three of them on my body
I see this two panzers an M10 and uh an
AA I'm surrounded by them maybe that's
because you know we're going to the
abandon their Factory to make it a
haunted house you're the ghost haunting
it I had to take out the M10 I hope
nobody noticed what about the uh Panzer
4 outside Dicker Max is push me paner 4
is fine they uh yeah are only targeting
things that move evidently yeah like me
like me trying to get to you Hi friend
would you like some candy or a tour of
the a factory please don't shoot me I'm
sorry oh is this the valley parking spot
is that Sherman alive I don't have a
machine gun yeah that is
alive now he's less
alive good work
Buddy if we get bombed because you're
parked up there and they see you for
some reason there appears to be a stug
in the field to your North copy good
luck
sck are you interested in fighting the
St or we just pretend to be a che one
sec something just went over yeah you
saw it good I'm glad you saw that
one I'm going to push around this way
it's a lot harder to do math when you're
at a 45°
angle enem is also on a like behind
us what St is going to shoot you in the
back
St to be honest he probably would have
gone for you you were a much bigger
Target I don't have side on him also I
see another Target I'm sorry oh there he
is all right he's
down welcome zoo and friend we'll get
little
guys so um like offerings we have
offerings to give the eny team the other
team know these are the offerings for
the other team look at them I I don't
want to mention you know something no I
do want to mention something here what's
that okay please why why is you want Sho
that talking when when I needed your
help you immediately said oh sick sorry
there's another Target oh there was an a
shooting in the building and I had BL
sign on him you were going to take the
AA this going to be a trick shot t on
that corner right there if you be
mindful of him I One driver on the
corner
or if you want to shoot him he's a track
right there boy you can do whatever you
want I'm trying to keep him
alive to
front AA to the
left also R for Zoo AA to the right
right yeah there's one fling left and
right if I could Bop you on the head of
this thing I
would uh zoo I watched yeah there you go
turn your guns that direction what I was
thinking also there's bombs
oh yeah but you're fine how's the
pressure feeling right now zo um
absolutely fine the hurricane save
me here
stick I'm swich
shells no I'm switching
anti-air nobody's shooting me I don't
know how to be more menacing you're
hidden in a bunker that's why you're not
being
shot uh stms how you doing
good no I'm dying you feel you feel
great he's not shooting you I've been
shot or was that your small turret that
shot me you have now shot me more than
the enemy hats I think I'm hitting him
I'm loading if he pushes up again
I have the correct shlo for
kb2 or we get a double
kill what's really strange terms is
after they killed you they stopped
pushing never mind very convenient kv2
is dead thank you my camouflage worked
do you see that yeah he thought you were
a monster instead of a
kv2 z T3 please don't anchor them I have
to reload oh they're shooting you
now use me for cover if you want
I'm okay with it where are they through
there one's pushing left right there
they're
literally almost
loading there's a paner for right on the
corner he's pulling forward slowly I'm
going to take T oh I see I just lost my
ability fire Z can you get the P
for you by 3 seconds two second no okay
fair enough going to machine gun me
barrel
down I don't know what just happened I
tried to shoot low cuz the only shot I
had I didn't fire that was
lag that was
strange I kind of feel like I have to
apologize for that one I don't feel too
bad he's shooting at our teammates but
also a kv2 snuck up on him I do not feel
sorry for him he needs to learn
awareness also he could have killed you
if he had the chance I am mighty kv2 No
Such Thing will happen if you got to
your
side nothing fls kv2 except K2
uh tank FR right there another one to
the right of that actually I'm just
going to charge him
because be heavy T did you see that shot
he
missed I did not miss no no he missed
paner oh he missed I got my Barrel a
little bit he's right here underne the
bridge somebody wants to like poop on
him or shoot
him oh guy behind us just requesting
some of violence
here got me
again still marked thank
you hello don't tell me he got your
Barrel too no he got my machine gun and
everything but I pushed him out the way
for you well I need 35 seconds to repair
so he's trying to get around hey stms
yeah if you're not busy in a few seconds
I could use you right here okay let me
drive over to you and stare at you oh
he's actually going
to I got to
go shot me
again he chasing me I don't have the
ability to fire so he's just chasing
after me where where is he Mark right
there okay hold on Panther 3 remember
when I said that kv2 can't be out
flanked yeah and I mentioned that that
was entirely possible thms please shoot
him I know you don't have bar depression
but he's right there
please I didn't get him and I flipped
onto my back we are so good at the War
Thunder Ser Target in
Road I got the fall up shot for you
thank you no worries there's probably
more of them that is z shop now actually
t34 right there never mind is gone hoay
there's still something else on the
point though now it's your Jobing why is
my decal murdering a body
pillow Halloween mate
Halloween
no not how oh lookus on St we can't stop
him but the CH one gun tried to help you
uh I got the the the chaffie though wait
what I got I got you there you go you're
good thank no worries always happy to
help he just got atomized but BL
overkill for a locust yeah I mean I
could have just backed up he got on your
fleshy meat Sid though I he spawn a
plane well time for me to go see you
later being the big bright red TV to
that has murdered him is probably not a
good idea for me no no you are going to
stand out just a little I'm running for
the Border there's a Sherman rolling on
to B I have a shot there he's down
excellent uh there's
another M3 Le on that ping the best part
about the K2 is once you shoot somebody
you then get to stare at the next Target
hoping they don't realize you're there
yeah as they're frantically trying to
put a giant two-piece shell into your
breach
yeah you get to play dead I could go
make a snack in real life and come back
and then shoot this no I hit the
DI I believe you oh please don't bully
him he's just a simple guy he's gone the
flag pans are one no no somebody else
zaring oh oh
okay because an SE 152 just obliterated
a he killed the m43 in front of me I
believe it's a locust on Bravo you want
to do this I've murdered many of locust
today yeah literally just like 10
minutes
ago I mean technically the Locust is
below you it's quite a short tank and
you're quite a tall
tank yeah you do sort of loom over
everything D first start is going to be
left of that building at 40 left
side
yeah um never mind I was able to hit him
thankfully it was a bit of a tricky shot
so I wasn't sure I was going to go
through you got him yeah dangerous thing
as well the
105 I think we beat him in the size
Department I mean not for is size
everything in this case though when it
comes to derp guns yes size is
everything yeah but I don't know more
boom is better yeah yeah yeah that is
true the bigger the Boom the
better I think velocity comes into play
as well the fun word we uses assault gun
a that poor oh he's alive why did I say
that switching shells d right there uh
that's not good that's a uh yeah P area
more problems right there not immediate
problems but if he starts going for my
Barrel kind of like
that half loaded
give me your loaders there we go I want
to keep that c we can because he's kind
of helpful yeah I'm loading AP at the
moment for the kind of four so am I
excellent great M think like I've got a
St I got a
hunt watching The Gap
again P fall gone I you can you watch
like over there soon in case he flanks
around yeah where my is pointing cuz I
don't know where he went I don't have
the machine gun my
kv2
yeah oh he's moving there's a Mark I
mean I hear him there he is he's gone
excellent yeah one more back there to
the right of him that is puma and
a okay I guess I don't need to tell you
what the second thing is now Su there's
a paner for waiting for you right
here oh I just want to give him a slight
bit of Hope as he saw the truck drive in
front of him before I killed him I'm
being shot in the back that is
absolutely karma that's very much Karma
hey any chance you can shoot this over
here what is it oh
I'm die die die die die die die no that
goes the gun part of playing kv2 is you
have to bully a little
bit just a tiny
bit where's it at where's it at right
beside me I'm almost on your position on
your position prepar B do not bomb me I
have this to bom you I have this do not
bomb me
I was going down
any I just I don't know what to do
anymore I I just like that broke me on
the inside watching that all
happen and then this little oil slick
just tried to drive away too and that
was what made even sadder oh yeah cuz I
strafed him on my way I'm recapping
Bravo good we need
it then you can go to
Alpha there's a b plane up at 40 never
mind there's a i16 chasing him I don't
think that I6 thing to do it is Bully
the
h51 playing over by
a all I can do is spectate my giant tall
turret which is why the Germans like
them for observation like to put theas
on
them stand up there for fancy uniform
point at things
have a
radio I feel like there
are more suitable platforms for doing
that with like you could just build a
tower on top of your tank put your
commander on a ladder yeah but why would
they need to
ladder why build the own when it can
just take what the Russians land this
battle is brought to you by the Home
Depot the Home
Depot self-propelled laders since 1957
somebody needs to make the kv5 skin with
a bucket a Home Depot orange
bucket from my perspective you
are are you in a buom
crater no I dug this out myself did you
did you absolutely you didn't you didn't
borrow it at all
no I'm going to perfectly duck hole you
want to see how well hidden I
am I mean if crazy Zoot wasn't here if
his flashing light and
why are you eating Bears eyeballs
because why wouldn't I be eating Bears
it's Halloween you got to be
scary look at him with the
stripes yeah it's gnet
kv2 well no I mean these are these are
my also in front of
you thank you for shooting that I have
the bar depression I have to wait till I
drive another 30 ft forward to go down
the hill to shoot him I was just stuck
staring at him like hi as I'm waving out
the barrel of my hand
thankfully he did not notice us I how
could he we're in such small I look back
and I see that face looking at me I'm
not turning around again do you not like
it so stealthy I'm going to break you to
the left and uh protect you from
anything pushed on this hill Oh yes this
place must be protected at all costs
remember as long as we're attacking
something that's above us we have plenty
of
elevation downhill bat there plane
coming in oh wait it's a 4 10 a I know
that was the most obvious thing I say
but I just felt like I should say
something it's
appreciated that was
auka you are alive how are you living
and he got a maneuver kill maneuver kill
basically landed right on you yeah so
did the other one uh once again the
tracks are gone no what he did was M him
so another bomber can come in and take
out
three I heard airplane engine as soon as
I started saying that
you just have to say that I think every
single one of us Lo up there to Charlie
it'll be a short trip I promise y just
just around the
bend when k2s go
uphill yeah it's just they were made for
this yeah yeah clearly oh I mean it
could be done oh thank God you just got
killed and said thank
God the climb was that bad Hill The
Climb was not that bad it was bad you
know it's even worse now you got to
climb all the way back to us yeah but I
can do it in something that isn't a
kv2 I just see this anxious antenna
moving left or right every time I move
forward at
him anxious antennas I have a treat for
you how did you miss no no no here it
comes here it comes oh you should
probably share that plane with me cuz I
wasn't ready I thought you were oh no I
thought you were pushing
left hey Zo you really should have saved
your own because that was a disaster you
just died to him I don't know why I'm
laughing I'm
next give you some Ang let give you some
good angles here you like that you like
that angle right there how about this he
didn't like that
angle
oh how did you miss
[Music]