um oh God don't worry I got you boo good
kill I'll never let anything happen to
you that's why you have emotional
support anti-air well something has
happened to me I did lose my driver in
that but where you go it's okay well
good news the law firms of Hans Hans and
Hans is here to help you with your
lawsuit against that
pt-76 we saw everything happen I got an
angle right here you got a you're the
witness he did not stop at that
intersection
I I don't know if you can be the witness
and the lawyer both he is liable I need
a I need a hospital sorry uh can you get
past oh God everything's kind of going
poorly you cuz I have no turret is this
a bad time to point out that I think
that my turret looks like something from
Star
Wars you know what I respect I respect
your enthusiasm like should I be
defending the Death Star right
now Luke May trying to blow it up oh no
help Jim I I can't do anything it's a
jumpo Jim there's a jump boo I I lost my
turet Rebels are here Jim and they have
a
jump
oh I was too weak Jim isn't it real nice
just to be two guys out in Panthers
having a fun time oh yeah real panther
party over here wait do I not
exist uh it's almost like you can hear
voices you know Jim just out here
enjoying our fun time about to say like
what what noise was that was that like
some some feedback I don't know but with
pan party Panthers only you're just
jealous you can't feel the air blow
through your hair I didn't mean for that
to rhyme I'm going to just oh down the
street down the street down the street
down the street cut left cut left cut
left cut I right I'm here to support you
no cut left you want to live there p34
big thing like it's hard to aim around
your giant panther
head one right there right side one
right there right side I try and keep
you alive and you insult me I'm trying
to assist you on support vehicle I have
no transmission no driver I'm coming up
to repair you I'm going to pull front of
stick
boy no I promise you guys can just go
and live you do not need to defend not
sacrif emotional support vehicle is here
how are you feeling
today I feel horrible I friends are
laying down their lives well we're going
to get you fixed up you're going to go
out there and you're going to conquer
all be the best Panther you can be I
can't hit a shot go team track on that
one he's wiggling he's
giggling
Jim there's about to be a sede over
here is there I got the first a but
there's going to be like two jumbos
pushing on this road in a second on that
road oh gosh he just shot the body right
here let me spin around let me spin
around oh my God there's one there's one
there's one he's down nice job there's
going to be one more at
least uh yeah he's on this corner right
here I'm going to push away from him I
might be to help here in just a second
you can hold it's
onos transmission out okay bait him bait
him bait him him bait him or he can't
move uh he's got his Rus rifle is poing
right at the corner
he's don't worry oh my so much violence
I need a track in a drive train there's
another one pushing at you guys be
careful I almost died to the splash off
of that okay uh he coming from the road
that the on on M6 M6 from the the all
right do not do not move forward because
you will block my shot come on do it do
come on kill me oh he's got an Arnold
accent now man
behind us behind oh no but but I me kill
me I mean don't find time for you he's
TR spin I need to
spin I got his Cannon Barrel thank you I
get on side if you want watch
front okay he'll be on second he's down
nice all right I'll watch in front the
three Hans would like to express concern
about their lack of armor and the
situation there in Stick did you just
shoot the back of the m41
head okay so we want to wait to fire at
the enemy until the friendly is out of
the way just a hot game tip I want to
pass on to
you you're also repaired by the way you
can move forward hey Jim
yes if an 88 ends up in our teammate do
we need to report that I'm your helpful
sidekick
today I'm here to help you be a better
player
stick okay well there's um never mind I
got good job with the art kill now that
is how you do it yeah stick I would take
the support take the support from the
strange convertible did you feel better
after I told you good job about the r
kill I did I actually make you feel
better it it was really nice having you
compliment me people don't get enough
compliments in life I'm here to make
sure that oh
God good eyes you see that tank right
there of course you did okay okay on top
of it okay now that call
out I can't hurt any of these things so
the best thing I can do for you is just
be there's a PT 76 to the left go around
the corner be careful
or are you lying to me so I the m41 is
fighting him just please be careful I'm
going
in I see I I hear that I didn't know
about the Sherman I'm
sorry please don't go that way please do
not go that way something
down b b how that how's that how' that
pt-76 go B didn't see him oh he saw the
Sherman somebody try to shoot at me miss
it was an M36 don't worry thank you okay
there's two over here I'm going to come
help you with that one so give me just a
second track one down there I that's not
the big one that I they're
retaliating careful it's already behind
you br already oh this is not a good
spot for me thank you so much for yep
hold if you just hold and pushing up
front your front oh that's a 36 that's a
36 I'm leaving him to you about the
heavy
tank the heavy tank showing me his
booty I'm doing what I can for
you is a very unhappy in 36 right now
how's B I hear a
sta well that should be on our side
hopefully that should yeah that's on our
side okay it
is M36 while back to
repair okay I'm going to try and push up
on that heavy oh no he has a friend what
is it German German I
bounced nice one
stick I got the corner I got the corner
yep yep yep shot there's two on that
corner now that are
mangled that
one there's M36 still back
there oh he's gone never mind we're good
bomb
nope work on the R Bo good work on the r
who wants to uh find an alternative
route because this is getting a little
hot over here yeah I only have two crew
members left so my reload is like 90
seconds s attack plus two
yeah pull that speeder over I'll let you
take out the other tanks now that they
know we're here thank you now that all
of two need notice how he took the easy
one and now we're left with the the big
brothers that eventually will come and
be upset in his defense that's got a
heck of a gun on it so I mean guns I
have four of them or we're talking about
the M18 talking about what you killed he
all yours what is it that thing thank
you no worries happy to help as always
I had no clue what in front I just saw
tracers oh my gosh what are AER Bulldog
I can help thank you good work good work
I I'm sorry I called your vehicle
uneconomical but can you help me put my
track on please yeah sorry also I didn't
mean to shoot you that many times
careful careful careful careful there
that is I just need to
reload I'm sorry never mind it's dead
I'm I'm panicking for no reason why am I
panicking I have no idea but R's
dropping and that's very bad for me so
take deep breaths deep breaths deep
breaths no I need more that's what I
mean I need more coffee I need a Jim I
can't fit can you move this body for me
or you can do it for you bud I would
really appreciate that thank
you I think making you more bad bad left
bad left is very bad shooting shooting
shooting what's left what's left uh it's
a Rell
maybe work
Jim I am so lucky he missed you two are
just the controllers of the city for now
until we get voted out office okay we
really need to push off that door if we
can there's artillery falling on that
door why is it everywhere I go there's
artillery it
seems
anxiety anxiety produces
artillery more artillery dropping I'd
like to leave all right let's go I'll
take my chances out there where are we
going hard
falling run just keep just got you go on
without me I'm going to help you
repair yeah I set underneath the arch
waiting for it to
cease I'm going be honest you saw
mve left left right there machine gun
plane plane plane plane I should
probably focus on
that okay nice I got your target I got
your target thank you for the repair
plane is somewhere behind me yes yes no
bombs no bombs he is currently
East there's a b my way waiting
oh bombs he have bombs he very much have
bombs oh gosh I'm going to try and get
on top of a Hilltop see if I can get one
of these AA popping in you guys you see
that thing mark behind
you yep yep I do I do throwing some
blood into
it uh no good hits from me but it's a
American Heavy T1 or m61 I see it I see
it I see it oh oh yeah they got a lot of
a down there I went a little low but I'm
okay wiggle waggle wiggle waggle wiggle
waggle yeah Jim I see your AA give me a
second okay
I'm actually not turning too hot anymore
so but it's a leopard 40 uh 40 mil I'm
uh I'm missing some uh surface controls
here I think I might RTV something else
important ones uh yeah elevator um oh
there is so many things happening here
oh my B yeah it's a
party hey I cleared the other side of
the cliff for you you awakened the
Hornets Nest oh B don't go first B no it
seems like you needed help so I'm here
to help no that's go please I'm helping
I'm trying to hold the flashlight for
you Dad I'm sorry it's it's actually
working wait Jim it worked what I guess
maybe one of the one of them just just
had a second mark on them or there's e
flanking around
you do not move not moving it's like a
shark over there I can see his face
where what do you mean I'm not going are
you moving why don't I get a move but
you get a move because I I'm handling
the situation for you
let me know if you see any planes cuz
I'm kind of focused on ground sorry uh
there is a plane currently flying at us
right now at 109 but I don't see a bomb
on it so I was kind of just going to let
it happen I see your
plane he's down nice oh my I can solve
all your
problems I can be your hero uh can you
uh help me with a couple things man I
just need someone to talk to yeah
absolutely what's the matter Jim oh man
a lot of things you know I got like I
got like seven problems and stick Bo
five of
them five five of your seven problems
yeah man he just doesn't get it that's a
large percentage yeah he's also he's
also the reason why like I have to like
do a bunch of chores tomorrow around the
house why I haven't done anything well
you're the reason why there's so much
dust in my
house wow I have to put air in one of my
tires that was a tree poen joke I
think yeah
it's going to it's almost going to be
the time of the year where stick boy
makes me sneeze every time I go outside
cuz he's just you know shaking his
seasoning all over the place there's a
Locus shaking his seasoning there no I
would like to interrupt my bit for there
is a locust on that Mark that just went
uh eastbound westbound North no no no I
I can't let you just get away from
shaking his
seasoning yeah's shaking it tree P
shaking his seasoning I'm I'm pushing
forward ready to die I've G to be other
team take me there's a little onto
sitting right at my mark big one behind
him never mind it's a Kill
Zone wow you handle that all by yourself
that was really unexpected to have a
second one drive up behind him while
it's was firing and they're both
lightskinned vehicles too good for you
don't worry next will be a heavy tank
looks like you're judging me when you
stare at me like that what no I'm just
admiring my my my pal it's like a Duff
comb stop looking at me with your four
big
eyes p paner paner Panzer paner Panzer
what you're a Panzer I'm a
Panzer wait are you good wait a minute
no no no no hold on no no I thought this
was Stick Boy no stick is over there to
your left stick is to your left
it wait a minute so wait you didn't
shoot it because you thought that was
stick boy coming say hi stick boy cuz
you I just saw Panzer 4 I didn't realize
he was in the 70 so I'm like oh hey
stick and then he then he's screaming
Panzer Panzer Panzer and I'm like dude
it's
me and then oh my we've been playing
this game for too long D if I rolled up
onto you why would I yell paner because
I don't know may you're in a panther
well it I mean technically I'm a
Panzer uh it got burned down it closed
and they're going to build a shopping
mall over
it there's already some Urban Decay uh
YouTubers doing very very very snobby
artistic videos about it and they're
just taking photos of rust are you
talking about the a factory yes the the
a factory has never been the same also
be careful Sherman and it never will be
the same unfortunately I missed the a
factory you know I had some really good
times
here J it's still here it's right in
front of us but no it's not the same it
burned down they're going to make a mall
out of it this this is the closed a
factory now B yeah it's closed it's not
the same the gift shop is empty there's
graffiti on the walls the tour guides
are gone it says Billy was here on that
wall who the heck's Billy I never Billy
here I I remember the tour guide that
used to say welcome to the a factory
make all forms of the letter A like it
was
yesterday I miss I missed that person
did you see anything to your
right I didn't okay I was just asking in
case there was a tank
sitting I'm sure that's fine no it's
okay sticks got it I'm I'm just kind of
going down memory lane here I missed
this place I'm sorry for your loss
oh that's my jum no hide that's bad
hide sorry I never had an angle at it
but I had a great seat to watch it
happen and fire in the
hole
he's I if I fired I why I'm sorry are
you okay no because I watched him
execute stick as I fired it's okay I
took a half a second longer to make sure
I had
don't don't do that guilty enough stuff
to
you you did what you had to do I feel
bad though it's okay Bo I give you
permission you can you can live on in my
memory in your
Shadow of Your burned out tankle over
there I'm sorry well I'll leave I wasn't
going to say it but you know this is
almost turning into an emo
song what song live live in my shadow in
a burnout tank
hole
oh there's one right
there how is the AA going Jim uh it's
good there is no uh a for me to AA at
this thing going be very upset he
thought he was that's actually double
kill two for
one they thought they were flanking our
friendly t34 and they walked into
me that was awesome I love it when you
do it to them like
that we're looking better over
here damn will reclaim the a factory to
its former glory an right here you might
be able get him all right moving in
moving in he said is it just a single AA
uh it is it's firing at me right now
he's trying to take my munition that I
have on my snout it's very bad if he
hits that anymore I'm moving up moving
up moving
up bomb on
him okay I might have done a little bit
of
Overkill overkill's best kill he was
trying to do things with me 4 so I
appreciate the help I'm
you do not compare us also is that the
concealed carry variant of the
m19 list what happened to your Barrel o
wow I I modified it so that I could do
CQB and m19 doing cqv is terrifying hold
on hold on the I like how the two
vehicles that have the weirdest looking
barrels are making fun of each other's
barrels no my Barrel is awesome no your
Barrel is
like I don't know how to describe that
in a family friendly way his brain broke
trying to come up with with an insult
yes because I was going to say naughty
things I don't also there's a tank ping
here I mean to be fair B like the end of
your Barrel looks like there's supposed
to be another pipe attached to it it
does it's an incomplete piece of
pipe where but where is it I heard
something left there's a uh is-1
possibly on that Mark there's also
something taking B
so behind that wall behind the wall
unfortun yeah the wall is the issue
right
now it's gone
firing he is down oh my thank you you
saved my life that really looked like
you missed and I was very worried for
half a second you can count on me I got
you can I count on you to fix my breach
yeah give me a second I'll turn around
help you I don't have Parts we're not in
a great spot here hang on there's
something no this is a very poor spot
something behind me I'll be right back
or well that was really tragic wow 2,000
lounder that
time we felt it we we definitely felt it
you know what I wish I could have helped
but I I actually had to uh be a ground
vehicle like and kill something Jim
there's a very loud engine on this Mark
right here okay uh that might be an is
one I saw maybe creeping I don't know so
Bo did you pull away from repairing
because of the plane or because of the
thing on the ground and then
okay I think I have two Targets on me
yeah I'm going to try to get to you
there's uh couple couple holes in the
road here come on is one right here
other side this wall can't do anything
about that button can you get the one
behind me what's the one behind you same
thing I'm I'm boxed
in I'm sorry j i canle I'm leaving you
now no it's okay I can I can I can I can
do something no no B I just got here
survivor's guilt oh there's one to the
front that was an immense amount of
Overkill that that was a double kill so
it was
not Jim that was uh very sad to turn
around see yeah another one showed up
right when I fired that oh hi there can
we be friends I'm doing the friendly
wiggle at
him uh t34 right there on that Mark I
know you guys are really far away but
I'm just let you know who murdered me so
that you can avenge me at some point is
he not accepting the friendly wiggle he
is very much not a friendly no please
get the K off the side of my super
structure oh no well now he's behind me
this is not
great I missed Jim you too sure you have
the situation hand I don't know uh Jim's
still alive so what's ring at you please
hold I actually do not know I can't tell
that's a jumbo M4 A3 you too I love
about stick is
just running towards a jumbo of Open
Arms I you said it like I hit a building
in front of him okay I'm trying to push
up behind you but there's not much I can
do no no I forgot I don't have
armor you're an
m19 Z please don't leave me I need you
right now memory is not don't poke up
then I would get hard to your left well
I'm concerned about my m19 friend well
the m19 is about to handle the situation
don't worry okay I'm going to go back to
plan if I can I'm on
fire do you have fire extinguisher yes I
do we're under control everything is
under control all right I'm going to
take out the plane
then um I'm just watching you judging
you I just want you to know that when
when you have a when you have a chance
oh you need repairs yeah that's a lot of
orange pooke dropped on you that's I
don't want to go near the Ry I'm sorry
that's
fair was that Ry that just hit or the
Sherman that was the Sherman it's okay
I've just backed up like a foot onto the
point and they're given me parts so
we're going to fix myself myself I feel
safe nowhere right
here you don't feel safe with me so if
the jumbo has you basically on lock down
how am I supposed to cross the road to
you no no no no no I listen oh my engine
is just kind of leaking oil from
everywhere but it's still running so I'm
just trying to stop it
before see we're all good now okay good
luck it was like preventative
maintenance you know good
hunting I wish you the best on killing
this jumbo the Jumbo's gone I thought he
was still
alive no I thought there was a second
one by how you were talking no I thought
hey there's something on a so is that
the second jumbo oh hey um
maybe right there right there 234 234
right
there
[Music]
a