you know I've been looking for the enemy
team yeah I found all of them there's
two what one ran this
Direction moving to engage going to take
a bit I'm going to take this one over
here I think I can oh no I don't think I
almost
loaded he is gone nice all right one
escaped out to left
though we must go on the hunt he's
called a witness we can't have
that well hold on a second
no we we we just got to go ask him some
questions take him for a walk 155
questions no Witnesses I see what you
did
there I hope all my Burger Kings get
their selves a burger Queen in
2025 Jim there's been like a uh exterior
gym watch the past two
weeks oh everyone's wondering where you
are Jim people thought I kidnapped you I
have you locked in the basement in a
trunk of a
car if they really need to know
Thanksgiving night while at work while
delivering gas to all the good girls and
boys on Thanksgiving one of my ribs in
my spine decided it no longer want it to
be part of my spine
anymore I told you be careful with the
golf
momies well you know they need to be
careful with me I'm an old man I get
older every year hanging out with the
wrong crowd they got chaffes now boss
chaff are on our side well look what you
have AER me reaching clear well there
was the
breach there's the clear clear all
right I'll fix just just a little delay
I don't think that was a smart thing to
do Jim also um we're both broken
different
ways all right I'm fixing myself oh gosh
I didn't know I was injured I'm bleeding
I hope you can shoot because it'll be
well for me also plane barrel red I'm
glad they're shooting you not that's a
bomb I it's on me the bomb is on
me but you caught it I did hello
everyone and welcome to the new improved
a factory where we make all forms of the
letter a uppercase lowercase and now new
for 2025 Corf that's right do you do
comic Sands no that's bang anyway so
with the new
revalation revalation what wow wow with
the new revation yes that's a word we've
just made at the a factory cuz it uses
the letter A we have automated all all
of our manufacturing for the letter A
that's right there's only six people
that work here automization is the
future there's more people in my
m44 well I could say you're overcrowded
maybe you need some Automation in that
anyway did you know that automation
starts with the letter
A yes I just met the paner 4 on the back
end is that a HR complaint at the a
factory no silly you don't actually work
here you're tourists anyway with the
proud involvement of Elon Musk and Tesla
owning 30% stock in the a factory he has
fully automated the a factory to where
only six people need to make all forms
of the letter A including Curson you can
also see that we've repainted the bricks
here in the a
factory you doing okay Jim Jim do we do
we need to get you some fresh air have
you been inside the factory too long oh
no there are no harmful chemicals that I
can constantly inhale from more than 10
hours a day 5 days a
week something's aggressively revving
there it is head towards
you engine and
transmission I hope we don't lose to
this I tried so hard just to get it with
the machine gun I should have just main
gun d i just Panic fired the 155 trying
to hit him sorry t34 uhoh almost
reloaded t34 on the point yeah I got
you that one I hit I'm sorry for missing
earlier oh thanks than
you we may still have stuff pushing down
from the back side of
a okay I'm going to start looking at
a we're not in a good place are we no
we're not I feel very
exposed all right I'll let you cap the
point I'm going to push off just so we
don't both get bombed thank
you cuz you know my stability with the
whole open top situation yeah you can't
exactly draw straws and have one of you
lay on top of each other actually let's
go over here what does that even mean
mean well you know someone's got to be
the
shield I do have a lot of meat shields
in here you imagine like they're crowd
surfing like the new guy protect us from
the
bomb all right you want to push around
uh this way towards a yeah that's want
to get a different
angle be a great
idea that could work very well Jim if
the new guy is you know like it could
work really well it could read really
bad that's got shot right I didn't even
see him I'm
10 please tell me he's Hing really well
he's behind this Co pile Oh
that's coner three up there I got him
Mar 3 is on the
way there is so much happening up there
yeah that M10 is still there all right
let me know if you need me I'm going to
focus on the guys on the back side a
okay keep doing your thing um all right
I'm going to leave
now I hear them to my close right on
this
wall okay I'm going to help up push you
also one up
there they're just kind of being shot I
want to fire in there see if I can
Splash damage him but I can't see him
real close to me it's getting
louder he's looking at me copy it's
behind the wall driver Gunner
Finish watch up there I'm reloading
you're
looking see where that shot just came
out from yeah I did right there also
how's the uh M10
doing uh I don't know I kind of ignored
him fair enough I will I will turn
around for you though I'll go see if he
moved out of the coal pile that's a stug
that is a stug
6:00
understood I don't have eyes on it yet
I'm going to mark on the map for
teammates I should have done that sooner
I'm
being everything is closing in on you
yeah they are cuz they're machine gun me
now and there's also this guy there's a
stairwell in my way knock that down he's
down I am am totally trapped
here engine noise is pushing
me I'm just going to barricade myself oh
here it comes here it comes yeah I'm not
loaded
yet I surviv the shot I got
him very nice wow 23 Second repair and
also the planes are
now planes are angry I just want to live
that's
it I'm still paranoid of
M10 over there are you sure he's still
alive it's possible I mean he also may
just maybe one with the coal I been
watching a kill feed that closely so
neither have I I will tell you backup is
on the way it may take a while there's
also no guarantee he gets there you've
been warned I also hear what's closing
on
me what is it sounds like an armored car
of some
type there's a Sherman up there on our
team
but I hear something closer I feel you
know I'm going to be honest though I I
think you know you you should just stay
there and hide you know just make a hole
I'm going to push out and help that
teammate oh he's so brave oh there it is
I knew it was coming back this way I
don't have machine gun to shoot down the
wall
so hey Jim there's a friendly little guy
right here wants to talk to you a
friendly little guy you want me to shoot
the wall um he just smoked me oh gosh I
got left armored car it's a
truck I'm taking that
one the mall security here's getting
pretty aggressive for the
holidays oh it's all those last second
Choppers somebody's behind this wall oh
I see
you hello there no shoplifting think you
are so brave for pushing out there cuz
there's no way no I can't shoot through
these shelves oh the tank behind you
just died yep and that's you know that's
why I'm just going to not hit the break
shot it pushing here no that's a bad
Mark about to your to the wall your wall
my wall I'm right with you your what you
followed me sck right there oh no I
didn't know you followed me I thought
you I was trying to help
you okay well then we can just forget
that one well there's right now a uh
challenge to see which m44 is more
dominant a civil war if you
will you know this is like one of my
animes
bro why do you sound like like a
grandmother telling me about the book
that she just finished reading you know
son just like one of my books you know
your grandma watches the Channel first
off so you better be super careful
because you might not be going to
Christmas dinner if that is your
impression of her you know canonically
no no no no no no it it's just it's one
of those grandmas at work you know what
do you mean one of the grandma at work
telling telling
me at the libraries what you doing at
work
stick how many older hussies do you have
bringing you cook what is happening with
the traffic J older hussies older
hussies
that's I'm going to keep pushing
forward you know actually all the cool
kids say hack now you can't talk about
the Librarians like that so you do have
a
type
stick oh young man you have an overdue
book I'm going to go die this is how
rumors start what is it is it the
glasses with the chains around remember
your grandma watches the channel I'm
just going to keep saying that oh stick
you'll find yourself a nice sweet woman
who likes
to doing Kim I haven't been okay in
weeks though I'll take that out for you
thank you uh contact right okay I got HP
behind the kv1 direct right yeah I just
got shot in front too gosh no kv1 near
my cover try to back up try to back up
please give you one come back no don't
break down there when are we going to
find a nice
woman worse issues this veral one got a
hold of me discount verble yeah I'm
going to assault it cuz it killed me
understandable that thing is quite
annoying
actually this this is entire generations
of karma hitting me in the face right
now yeah it's called being a Vikings
fan okay got shot right I you know what
it can just take me just accept it with
open arms
I don't know it's probably in the
field you know what this reminds me of
stick boy I have a bone to pick with
your generation oh no stay away from my
women you know how many articles I see
why gen xers are going for 30 plusy Old
stay away from my
women or excuse me uh gen Z's you
completely distracted me I drove in
front of the Sherman and just stared at
it saying please please end me
I I I don't like I don't like all the
Gen Z's that that think they can just
date you know how old you sound right
now I will be 32 in January I'm an old
man I know what I am there's a tank and
a puma back here but I'm taking the Puma
to set example for the others oh I
killed the French
thing Swedish tank went up here behind
that
hill Oh wait I have the angle thank you
that's very deadly so I appreciate that
one yeah yeah that thing's got a heck of
gun oh excuse me KY goodness I'm sitting
here just having fun with my
Mobility look Jim if you don't have the
angle you have to create the angle oh
true Jim witness me all right young
man I'm out of control I'm sorry this is
not spin to win this is fight to
win the price is wrong Bob you're like
that grade schooler who gets a swivel
chair for the first time in computer
class then falls off it or is that just
me no or the teacher just has to take it
away and has sit in a normal
chair describing my childhood no I was
describing mine
actually look it can be multiple
people's
childhood uh I hear
plane I hear bombs oh no never mind
we're good wait we're good oh we're good
oh I'm I'm sorry I forgot you pushed up
to us I'm I'm sorry I did not mean to
discriminate against your lack of armor
I'm sorry I'm past tense now there is a
Sherman that is driving on to B copy
plane that's a plane's more interesting
50 cal up I just lost so many of my poor
poor boys what what happened were they
not huddling together for protection
they were huddling too close together
and uh they made a very small Target for
the airplane oh I see okay also the
plane's coming back Chim I don't have a
50 Gunner no leave him alone you bird
yeah yeah you better hey Jim there's a
tank behind me as well I got shot I
can't
fight Jim is the chosen one no I am most
certainly not I want to go home if we
keep talk about how well he's doing and
how he's surviving all this I'm sure
that'll help prolong his life no no it
will not I'm actually doing terrible why
aren't why aren't I dead yet I already
embraced my death wait please please no
oh come on you are the chosen one get
bombed what am I the protagonist yeah I
did how are you still alive in there I
don't
know hello I would like my tracks and
breach back please repair lucus is
almost
there's got no
Gunner oh gosh in front of me you me
take it or go to gym go to go to gym go
to gym I got a perfect you got it
or you can take him if you got shot I'm
just worried about you all well look I'm
I'm worried about Jim I can't lose you
and him help me I'm almost there help me
it's in front of me it's scary I'm going
to go to the right okay it's hairy it's
shave hairy what is it shave it it's a
Swedish oh it
is oh finally
sweet I feel like I witness something I
shouldn't
have thanks S I don't want to talk about
it there's one more standby behind me
somewhere can we just move on and not
anything that just happened it is a M10
at the
corner marking uh that
direction 185 South for me yep we're
rolling around I would just wait for him
to
push he's posted up pretty good
there we can move the train
cars maybe that'll make him
interested yeah you're an Tyson
M it worked it worked it worked it
worked he's very curious now keep
enticing
him I took his engine go I got the
driver loader he's down what's
everyone's goals for
honestly I want to buy a new car I've
had the same car forever and it's not
doing very well so oh I like to put
enough money back to get some reliable
set of wheels may I interest you in the
uh Nissan Frontier oh God are you trying
to sell your truck also I'm being shot
from front no oh my God I just made the
worst shot in the history of War Thunder
I slammed on the brakes and fire at the
same time the barrel went up like I was
a Snus and it just went into space from
my angle look like you got shot with a
space Marine's heavy Bolter like 17
times I don't know what I hit some poor
bird down range got smacked in the
face I didn't know stuff alus sent
things to the Moon do you even know who
he is I I I no not really I'm going to
be honest here oh I stick hi just a
moment we got to stop meeting like this
Jim's Not educated he's not I'm waiting
for you to figure it out and he was like
a he he he was like a big purple thing
right with a log nose wrong
color you have to least know where he's
from no alus
Town
Jim have you ever heard of the main
streets of Sesame Street
actually the worst Street in New York
City one to your front left in the
Gap k s to the left I feel like I just
called out your death and made it worse
for
you there's going to be a thing right
here towards me I got this thing on the
point one down very good I just want to
get rid one of those
k7s I have a Reload also speaking of
Sesame Street if you really want to Ru
it for you I I recommend Dave
Chappelle's bit on Sesame Street forget
that yeah you know exactly what I'm
talking about every Millennial remembers
Wayne Brady for that reason that's a
different skit but you know what I mean
yep our reinforcements are running in
you see this oh my God I'm being
straight my plane I should not stop also
he just crashed bomb I'm sorry you just
died and I lived why I literally drove
on top of the bomb thank you thank you
for jumping on the hand grenade also R's
here they better give me a medal you
know Jim I don't think that actually
another plane I'm just not meant to
live hello B that's
terrifying uh somehow missed me got
Gunner so many loud noises when you load
into more things yep yep I'm I'm coming
back yeah there's a whole bunch I'm
pushing put my fire almost be
there yeah I'm going to stay tucked in
here nice kill should be one more with
them holy turret yeah there's a lot of
them oh
wow I'm not going to be able to do much
to him almost there stay hide hide hide
help us on the way I never hide from the
face of
adversary
adversary adversar that
word I got him good work Jim I thought
you trying to say anniversary at first I
was like what adversity adversity
adversaries
what's ASAP
score 34 I'm working on it thank you I
know it's not that one Jim there's more
there's more I have the power of God I
need to reload those it's going to take
five business days I know what you're
talking
about I'll push
up how can I help you my le um I would
like a Jack and Coke and maybe a baloney
sandwich nothing close
side we need to Boogie cuz we have no
capture points right now yeah do do we
want to go down the street or do we want
something a little more cover I can be
bait use me as um I'll draw them out go
forth and please don't die I'll feel sad
I'm in a duster buddy and he's in a
chaffy so let's do it what oh
gosh left is clear thank
you I hear engine noise to front
left yeah I'm going to start slowing
over should be right over
here
okay
actually let's bypass
him okay I'm going to clear this go for
the point will do there's something
right in front of me
here I think it's
Russian yeah it's looking up it's I can
handle this
made him very
sad oh there's also planes that that
that's my job oh no no no sorry sorry
it's okay that's
okay hey
stick yeah we need to put up a giant net
for these airplanes I
okay maybe some balloons hide to steal
cables yeah I think they're called
barrage balloons I I I don't have any of
those available I have a bunch of drones
think that'll
work I'm concerned about all the planes
I'm that's a
tank I can't see either stick it's
silent he'll fog up in this
thing also could you please help me fix
my breach so I get another gun in the
fight I am fixing my breach I'm
contemplating how bad I want to get back
to you guys to help you I I you know
what I think you should go on vacation
I hear
aelier it was I'll take rare tanks for
500 I ran to him once before so I'm glad
he's
gone is this smoke going to dissipate is
this is this a not no we're you didn't
know Snoop dogs on the
map Snoop Dog getting called out like
that for no reason we're playing at a
permanent disadvantage hey skip Dog Skip
dog's an old man okay leave him
alone also look at this collection of
things trying to get crew members right
here yeah including me don't make fun of
me oh don't worry I'm joining you thank
you they shot my bush off Jim that's a
little TMI I'm going to drive away now
which one we take the t34 the Panzer
whichever one you can hit better shot T
still can't H me so he's gone thank you
paner to the right of him
gone is that a
tank yeah that's the Panzer I the way he
said gone shoot that well no that no the
Panzer is gone that's that's a different
thing that's the pan right there that's
a hey look a couple oh it's SP
stls
ow I can help out
got oh wait that's
not I don't know anymore I just don't
know anymore the gizzard wizard Z you
never been to New York
that was just a confusion when you're
saying that you never got a steamy hot
Lizzy
oh for the record I'm talking about hot
dogs in New York
Lizzies the way you said that though
yeah I mean they're steaming hot GES
they're in hot
water better go stick you know sometimes
I wish those shows were meant for me
some of the best to the right it's to
the right the best hot dogs in New York
come from the he looking at me talking
about wizzies well I'm watching the
battlefield he said that was to the
right is that down the road towards
um oh STI what was the right relative to
you cuz I don't know where you it's on
the map it's on the map okay so towards
their
side well I guess we'll go see it's it's
Scout right there okay that's a
different
thing I don't see what kills sck neither
do
I doesn't matter anymore so what do you
take your Gizzy
with mustard ketchup little bit of
pickle relish I mean pickle relish is
always good want a chili
Gizzy okay I don't oh do you know what
he's talking
about hot dogs but he's just doing it
yeah but he's but he's saying he's
saying things on the hot dog that chil a
chiling dog it's not that complicated
I'm a big fan of the cone dog
[Music]