Storms, I hope you realize you're just
playing with two toddlers that have no
plan or idea on what to do. I picked up
on that pretty early in the video.
Prepare for the toddler swarm.
I took gunners. I took gunners. There's
three. Something else shot
me. That was through you and to me,
though. Just run. Just run. Just run.
Just run.
One's
down. I'm sorry. Escape. You got the
cheese. And run.
I'm actually going to flank around. Take
them from the six if I can.
Oh, there's more. Can you mark them for
me before you die? Oh, yeah. One right
there. Marking. Marking. Marking. Oh,
no, no, no, no. That's a bad BTR80 came
to cut me off from the direction. Time
for a little War Thunder real talk. And
these are my opinions and my feelings,
and you can judge me accordingly. Okay.
I don't like people who play the
XM0000t, but I like playing the XM00.
Does that make me a hypocrite? Yes. Do I
feel sweaty and dirty when I play the XM
T? Yes. Mhm. But there are like swarms
of these things that just come through
and disembow villages and it is
piranhas. But we're part of the problem.
So here we are. You're part of the
problem. Secondly, it's going up from 80
to 83 in the proposed changes. Yes. And
I kind of was like, well, that doesn't
do a lot because I run at 83 anyways
with my lineup normally and um I have no
issues. But then it occurred to me if
you really want to punish the
XMT, drop it down to like 77 or 70 and
let it face World War II heavies or
IS-6s, IS-3s,
IS-4s heavy armor. Yeah, that's how it
needs to be nerfed. It needs to go down,
not up. That's my hot take right now.
I mean, that is a big brain play right
there. Also, don't judge me for the
things I'm about to do. If you want, we
can go at the same time. That way, he
has to pick who to shoot. Uh, there's
one out there. Sorry. Moving to the
left. I should tell you about that. I
have a lot of rocks in my way, so I'm
pretty safe. I'm kind of worried about
the close one. He's flanking around the
village.
Flanking around whose village? Sorry,
let me mark a map. Something is sitting
out like here.
Okay, probably closer by
now. Uh, stick push. A shot. Go. That
was a D 105, by the way.
Just working on your tank recognition.
I'm not judging. Yeah. In his defense,
that's an oscillating turret. It was I'm
just I just saw the turret and went
French. I know it wasn't a bad guess.
You were partially correct there. Kind
of.
Should be one to your front left. He's
thematically correct. I got this one on
the right. Look your left. I'll get the
one on the right with both. We're
getting two different things. No.
No, we were. There was one to your left,
by the way.
Look what I can do. Oh, wow. He actually
I'm actually coming back to repair you.
I just
Oh, I won't be coming back to repair
you. Ice terms were both
broken. That does not help. Also, please
don't melt the ice. I'm standing on.
Oh, you'll be fine. You see how far our
two teammates ran past A? Yeah. Yeah.
That's what happens when you have comps
and
XM800Ts. I'm not going to lie, Bo, I
really thought you had launched off the
right of that jump and was about to go
into the water. Wait, we're just going
to let his remarks go unchallenged.
Okay, fair enough. I I don't have a a
challenge to it.
We need to make a solid rebuttal here
when we have it. No, no, no, no, no. Bo,
you No, please. Somebody, somebody
please. I'm fine. It's too late for him.
No, I'm fine. It's like I can still hear
his voice sometimes. I've got two
sitting right here. Okay, I'm going to
see what I can do in terms of One's
down, other one's down. Hooray.
I was just going for breaches and t crew
first, but no. What is
that? It had eyes and it was staring at
me like it was a giant frog and it
terrified me. Well, at least you killed
it. You know how it has the two
launchers that are sitting far out wide?
Yeah, it had giant eyes on each one. It
scared me. It was just sitting there
staring at me. I am not clear further
left.
Oh,
I can push that though if you want.
Guess that works.
Excellent work. Oh, there it is.
Front front storms. I'm sorry. I
couldn't do anything about that one.
I couldn't either. First map of the
night and it's your favorite. Abandoned
factory. A single cap. A factory.
It's the best, right?
I have the happiest little factory
worker, too. The little gremlin with
small hands that can make anything.
There's There's really only one thing
that's recovering this night for me.
What's that? You'll find out in just a
second. I'm going to guess CSU.
57 and it's a flamethrower. You're going
to light me on fire. That's what's going
to happen. Yes.
Go ahead. Get out of your system. There
we go. Bathing in the Why is everybody
shooting at me? The entire team is
shooting at me.
Why? Wait, now you're getting bullied.
No, that that it's a tight fit.
Everybody tried to go at once. Yeah,
I'm going to outrun all of you.
Actually, no. stick to some Xer. It is
an absolute mess back here. Just keep
going, Bo. Look at what we're in. Look
at Storm saying you have fire. That's
amazing.
That thing reaches so far. It does.
I'm going to push pretty aggressive and
try to cut them off. Okay.
I'm going to go all the way through this
building and see if I can stop them at
that fence if they're not there already.
Watch. If you can pull them off, the
rest of us should get there shortly.
Yeah, I'm pushing straight through
there. Where's that one at?
Is not want to be seen by that.
Gone. It was down by uh where the B
point usually is. Uh BMP just roll past
me. Okay, I am holding the cap
though. Scouted.
Okay, I'm rolling forward. I'm going to
see if I can swing around. He is
That's not worth the risk. He's coming
back my way. He's
tracked. I'll see I get more of him.
Never mind. Nice job, Storms. One went
across over there to the left.
Affirmative. I don't have a great angle
on that. No, I just watched that corner.
Yep.
I'll see if I can watch for you. He's
marked over there now. Yeah, I should be
able to fire over the BMP's corpse. He's
terms. Yes. Hi there. Hi. What are you
doing? Oh, I'm just watching this
corner. You want to be neighbors? Not
really. Oh, that's hurtful. Okay. I'm
sad. Well, I mean, what am I? I I'm in a
field. Like an empty space. Can't live
in that.
You're like a tank that grazes.
A T5 would make a great Just call me a
tank.
Yeah. Now we know we really feel
disturbed. Let's get a move on.
No, I'll try that again
later. Oh, he died. The joke was that
bad. You died. Yes, it the joke is what
killed me. Not the AMX30 behind that
smaller building. No, it wasn't a French
tank. No, it definitely wasn't. I just
just exploded. I love this watching me
like the guy just drove off
caring. I got him scouted up. I'm hoping
teammate pushes.
We got people up there.
Yes.
Should I now just run around like a
gremlin? I mean, isn't that what you're
already doing? No, I'm playing
tactically kind of.
Wow. Tactically kind of. It's a real
thing.
Well, there's Oh, never mind. You see
them on your left? Yep. Working on them.
Feel free to do anything you want. Okay.
Yep. A real thing. Don't worry. Scouted.
I saw you on fire. He's wounded. He's
under crew, too.
Uh, reach is out.
I hear helicopter. I'm going to look for
that. Don't worry. He's um he's not dead
or shot down, but No, I hear it to my
left though. No, he's down. He's down.
He's down.
Is it just the one?
Yes, I believe so.
I'm going to push back around. Dragonfly
looking ones.
Oh, look at that big guy.
All right, back towards you. Driving up
on
He's just driving up on everything. I
told you. Gremlin mode. Okay. Well, I
hope he doesn't need assistance because
we're all I just reverse past and the
other guy's following me, too.
Two targets moving there. Scouted.
trying to be helpful.
I can take one easily. I can't. I don't
have enough pressure.
That'll come later.
Oh, I'm keenly
aware. There's also one to the left
apparently. I'll jump that one. Sorry,
that was your right. No, no, no. He's to
your right. Hard right. Hard right. I
see him.
Okay. I thought I saw a tracer coming
from the left up at the aactory.
Uh, stick. Uh-huh. If you have Oh,
something's trying to teach you at me.
Do you need help? Uh, and no, it's
fineish.
Okay, cuz I got I got the one on your
left. Yeah, it's not
fine. It's amazing how quickly it
converts to not fine. Hey, Storm's to
our right. There's two of them moving.
Okay, I'm going to try and keep an eye.
Yeah, let's just move into the low
ground. I was going to say if you want
to finish your guy, I'll just push those
ones down already.
I don't have tracks anymore. Okay, turn
around to help you. I'm sorry. I guess
I'm going to turn back and watch the uh
situ. Never mind. I'm going to get autoc
cannon by Gapard.
I traded with him at least. Hooray.
Small
victories. Oh, dear God. What'd you
find? I came around the corner and ran
to a leopard one.
That's a scary round the corner target.
That's the guy.
You just lost a leopard one. Yeah, we do
that sometimes.
Uh there's something else back here near
us. Okay, I'm pushing back into the
town. In between sick and I in between
us.
Found him. Oh, good work. Hooray.
Hi. There's going to be one behind you
in a second. Oh, okay.
I'm just running off a plan. Sorry. I
mean, isn't that how you know normal XM8
things is you just run around uh never
take the mode throttle and shoot as you
go? Hold down W occasionally. Left click
and try not to keep up with you guys. I
don't know where you're going and I
can't keep track of you on the map.
We're just circling you Sterms. That's
it.
Sir, look to your left here and say a a
I took his gunner in his right track.
Wow. Also, something direct front of me.
I'm looking. I'm pushing. I'm sorry.
It's machine guning me. Don't know what
it is. It is a ZTZ 59D1.
I was trying to buy you time there. I'm
sorry. No, no, it's it's good. He got
blown up by somebody.
The enemy just doesn't seem interested
in me. I've noticed yet they just
completely ignored that. Literally, he
had the chance to fire at Bow and take
him out and just shot over him.
Oh, I'm undesirable.
Wow. Storms, you died again. I am sorry.
I'm so They are to the north of our
spawn firing in. Head that direction. I
see on the map.
I'm sorry. I feel bad for you. I don't
feel too bad.
Oh, wait. No, no, no. The other one is
like way up there. It's a TAM. I was
going to repair this guy. Ignore him.
He's dead. He's got a face. I see the
TAM. I see the TAM. He's not dead. He
just looks mangled. It's too late for
him. I'm literally repairing him right
now. Tam has no cannon barrel. If I held
down the button long enough to repair
him. Plane friendly. Okay, thank
goodness.
How's that one still alive back there?
He's behind a corpse. Got him. Hooray.
[Music]
I can't repair the friendly thing there,
but I can make that shot.
We did it, guys. I shouldn't be that
impressed because I fired like 30 shots
with one click. So, okay. Now, now what
do we Now, now what do we do?
You didn't think this far ahead? I
didn't.
What if we just
like I don't know. I mean, we could go
to the cafe. It says they're still open.
Where's the cafe? There's no cats at
this cafe.
Yeah, that's because this is America in
like the early 60s. Yeah, but look how
much they like have a sale. Yeah. Why
are we going to a cafe that has 50% off
anything? That's not good. Well, no. 50%
off 20% sale 30% off sale 20%. And
sandwich
my whole plan here is going to come down
to surprise and hopefully no heavy tanks
being outside this ridge. I don't feel
so good about that second half. There's
going to be something hard left. Yeah,
they've already passed us. I'm pushing
through. Martyr taking in first. Yep.
I'm looking left. Got the one left.
There's two. There's one more. There you
go. Nice
job. I think we just run at this point.
Yeah, run. Cut bait and run. Yeah, I
lost my breach. There's something in
front of you. Shot in front of you, Bo.
Got him. Farf, never mind. We're good.
Well, I guess Well, you're just going.
I'm going to see. Bo, there's one left.
Just You need to keep moving. There's
one sitting right here.
Okay, hold on. I'll turn around.
He's not pushing though.
Do you see him there? No, I do not. I
think I shot a rock thinking it was him.
Okay, I'm going to hold here for a
second.
Died over there. Nice job. Yeah, I heard
him back there. Swing fire. I'm going to
move back towards Surms and help him.
I'll get just a second. Don't worry
about me. All right, I'm just going to
see pushing over this hill.
I'm just trying to do some uh practice
scouting for you if I can.
Okay, I'm actually going to try and get
down to A. Actually, yeah, something's
on A. I'm going to move that way.
Yeah, something just literally got on to
A. You've got a Bradley also possibly
helping you. It's looks like a Leopard
one. I'm right behind you. It's going to
fire at me. Never mind. You good? Nice
job. Yeah. Would you like us to capture
it? Yes. Oh, so we get max
air. It's like a tandem dive right
there. Those Oh,
we collide.
So, competent teammates, we aren't not
that thing.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Bo, I think
we're doing a pretty good job at what we
plan to do
so far. Yes, actually. Do you see it,
Storms?
Nope. Wait, there's a bomb under me.
Oh, my turret popped off, too.
Yeah, I don't I didn't get a good look
of mine
did. I see the mark. I saw something for
a brief second pushing up the hill.
There it
is. Oh my.
Remember the ME262 that bombed us? Yeah.
He now has HVT.
Gotcha. Don't challenge that man. When
they're attacking me in swarms, it's not
my favorite thing. But then when you
play
it, you have to become what you hate.
Oh, which is a knife wielding grat
gremlin. But I don't feel any remorse
when I'm in the X800T.
Yeah, that's the uh the great mystery.
I'm very conflicted.
I I don't think so. I feel like I should
have shame, but there's no shame be
found.
No, the the feeling that you feel when
you're fighting the XM800T is actually
the desire to simply be in the XM800T.
There's a thing. We lost Dick Boy. Um,
an 81
that's in front of me on top of the
bridge. The bridge. The circle. The
clover bridge. I love the description
he's giving us. I know what he's talking
about. I do too. But
anything gunner and breach. You want to
finish him? No.
Okay. Uh well, you're going to have to
cuz I can't get through the turret.
Okay.
Safe. Uh nothing over that way. No. I
can jump him. I can go push him. Okay.
I'm going to try and push around because
he's probably pushing down by now. Yeah.
I'm going to hop over here if I can.
Uh Sturms.
Um yeah, don't push that way. Problem.
There's a problem. Large problem. Okay.
It's named Mouse and it's looking for
stick.
Ah,
what? No. Tell him I'm gone.
He only want I don't want to answer that
phone call. He lit just said, "Where's
Stick Boy? I need to talk to him. He owe
me
money." What he said, but in German.
I don't know anybody. I couldn't do a
proper translation.
Sorry. So, I went with that voice for a
mouse. I don't know what's wrong with
me.
Okay. I just need you to hold all the
enemies there. I ran away. Your thing is
now shooting at me from the bridge, by
the way. Okay.
Wait, the mouse is on the bridge. No,
he's in that direction, though. Yeah.
No, he's marked on the map. See that
heavy tank mark on the map occasionally?
Yeah. about um
there that's
uh there is a class three on top of the
bridge. I can help with that. That is I
think one is slowly taking me part by
part. Can you mark it or something? Do
you know which bridge it is? There's a
Leopard one underneath the bridge.
I'm going to be honest, the bridge seems
to be where it's happening. terms. I'm
concerned. I got your uh whatever it
was.
Good call out. Yep. That that wasn't
even what he called. I got a ruicat that
was on a bridge. Probably not his
bridge. Ser, I'm nervous right now. Is
it because of the bridge? Just the
things that keep popping up from every
angle.
Oh, I see. No, the mouse is here. I'm
not even kidding. Can you escape? Uh,
I'm going to try. I can't leave the BMP.
Yes, you can. No, I can't. I left him
earlier. That's not very nice. If I can
tone him down. Oh, I need more weight
and power. Come on. Come on,
buddy. He's also trying to appear, so
he's not.
Hey, Sterms. Yeah. Who can I call right
now? Push to you. It's fine. There's
something on the bridge.
There's a mouse directly in front of me.
Okay, I am trying to get to you. Never
mind. The leopard found me. Where was
the leopard, Surms? Actually, really
close to me. It was uh the north bridge
nearest to our spawn. He's hiding in the
shadow of that. Come pay off this mouse.
I I I have I am taking the focus of the
mouse. Never mind. He's back on you. As
you're saying that, he's swinging his
gun over to kill me as I was trying to
help you.
Ser, this tank just looks completely
lost and just done with life. He was
trying to escape
being chased by a BP1 at X00T. The poor
guy was just like, I'm done with this
game. Get me out of here.
He almost
managed, but no one can escape the light
tanks forever.
My primary goal at this point is to try
to tame and domesticate enemy tank as a
Locust.
That guy
is other side of the train tracks. He He
if you pull too out of the open bow,
he'll get you.
Stick. I'd like to highly recommend do
not push me because there's about five
tanks on my
position. I'm friend. I'm not food. I'm
friend.
Wow. He seemed hungry.
I'm apparently hungry enough to eat his
friend.
[Music]