Oh, there's the revving. The nervous
revving of the engine. He's peeking.
He's That was two. That works.
He is down. Oh, nice shot. Uh, how's
Tiger Tiger? His barrel's up. His
barrel's back. Barrel's up. Barrel's up.
I will sacrifice myself for the cause.
He got shot in the face. He's down. Oh
my gosh.
Where did you pen for monster? He got to
rub that belly under his belly. Get in
there and scratch it good. Oh my gosh. I
was too busy worrying a man out here
actually like petting tigers like
they're kittens. Ground forces video
1,00. That is a pretty crazy number to
me. And thank you so much for allowing
us to keep making content and allowing
us to hit such a crazy milestone. I want
to thank all the people who have helped
me create content. This certainly
doesn't just happen by myself. We have
the guys that show up in videos of
course, but there's also a lot of people
who never get a second of screen time
that are the unsung heroes of this
channel community from community
managers, Discord moderators, Twitch
moderators, people who have donated
resources, time, expertise, and skills
to help us do this. And they are the
unsung heroes of the channel. and I want
to thank all of them for any and all
contributions they have made to allow us
to reach this milestone. I also want to
take a quick moment and thank all of our
Patreon members, YouTube sponsors,
Twitch subscribers. Your generosity has
made all this possible. Thank you so
much to an amazing community for
continuing to support us all these years
and allowing us to keep going. I can't
express that enough. You guys have
absolutely blessed my life and have
allowed me to live my dream and I will
be forever thankful for that. So,
there's one last thing I like to talk
about before we get on to the subject of
today's video. And I'll be quite honest,
I record this part now like 10 times
because I can't find a way I want to say
this, but in the last video I mentioned,
hey, if you like the content, please
make sure to subscribe to the channel.
It really helps us out. And we had over
200 subscribers in 40 hours. I can't
tell you how much that has meant to me.
It has been an absolute slog on YouTube
the past year and a half. And I'll throw
the recent analytics on the screen there
for the recent subscribers. I don't want
to get too much in the numbers or get
too far into this, but I'm sure you've
heard other YouTubers talk about just
how the platform has been lately for us.
And uh thank you so much for just doing
that. That helps us so much. And again,
I'll mention if you like the content, if
you like to see us make more, please
make sure to subscribe. If there's other
content creators out there that you
enjoy watching, please subscribe to
them. It really helps us out. So,
hopefully that didn't come off too
awkward because it felt really awkward
to me. I hate talking about this stuff
and I'm definitely a person who never
likes asking for anything. So, thank you
so much again for the support. So, I
have what I wanted to say off my chest.
And now, let's get on to the subject of
today's video. In the previous video, I
asked, "What would you like to see for
our 1,000th Ground Forces video?" The
winning comment with 2500 likes is
whatever vehicle you did your first vid
with for War Thunder or choose your
favorite vehicle to play. So, we decided
to do a combo video. The first kind of
proper ground forces video I did, and I
say proper very loosely, would be the
KB2. And that's a classic. Now for the
favorite part, nothing jumped out to me
immediately, but I thought about it for
a few minutes and there is a MBT that I
have over 600 battles in. And when I say
MBT, I mean mini battle tank, the M22
Locust. Let's get that Gremlin energy
going. So, if you haven't figured out
from the thumbnail already, we're going
to be doing a KV2 and M22 Locust
combination video. So, there's going to
be two rounds of KV2 and then we're
going to jump over to the M22 Locust and
run it at a bunch of different battle
ratings, including top tier and a couple
really fun rounds at 6.0 and 7.0. I know
at this point you're probably sick and
tired of hearing me say thank you, but
we had such a overwhelming response in
the last video in terms of comments and
ideas for what we should do for this
video that even if your idea wasn't
picked for this video, you still may see
your idea resurface in the future
because there were some really good
ideas that we're going to draw
inspiration from and use in the near
future. So, thank you so much to all
those who contributed in the comment
section last video. There was a lot of
gold in there. And now with all that
being said, I think it's time to just
simply start the video before I talk
forever. Well, there's something I need
to admit to you. You're disappointed in
Nissan? No, I'm disappointed in uh
Midwestern barbecue.
Okay, that's a take. My My loving mother
for Mother's Day wanted barbecue.
Immediately threw your mom under the bus
on this
Also, take way out there. That's not
very loving, Jim. Well, he's a grown
woman. I'm a grown man. We can we can
take the
L's. She wanted a barbecue from this new
barbecue place. Okay. Fast forward $120
later and about 50 lbs of
food. I realized that. Could someone
please murder that? Uh, I'll try. I
realize us Midwesterners, we do not know
how to do brisket.
No, you you needed up to spend 130 bucks
to learn that. Well, I love my mother
very much and she wanted brisket and I
proceeded to consume about 5 lbs of
shredded spare tire with Alabama white
sauce. The Alabama white sauce made it
palatable and I realized that we really
really should leave brisket to everyone
from Kansas down to Texas. My face right
now is a lot of confusion. I A puts
white sauce on B $130.
I My family eats a lot of food. It
wasn't just for like me and my mom. It
was like for the rest of my family. Come
down here. I'll cook you a brisket for
$130.
Okay.
Also, that corner is clear now.
I got shot from because there's one
behind us. Don't jump. I'm trying to
turn. You confused me so much. I drove
right past that Sherman. And I
apologize. Oh my gosh. Yeah, he's hiding
in damaged.
Not enough. Oh no. Okay, I have a 30
second repair. I'm going to keep staring
in front of him.
I was going to say you can use me for
cover. I'm going to block for you.
Actually, I got him out of the
apparently. I was able to fire, but it
did nothing. Jim, behind us, there's
another Sherman. Oh no. 50 second
repair. That one drove off. How's the
one in front of us doing? Uh, he he he
drove off like There's one to your
right. I would not pull any more
forward. Okay, I cannot uh repair it in
6 seconds. Oh, I see him. Okay, it's an
M10 actually.
You have that side cuz I have no ability
to slew turret. Okay, I am halfway
reloaded. Oh, I'm sorry. You're fine.
I'm trying to cover your six right now.
I am dead, which was a dream of mine.
Good news is uh good news there is no
good news, Jim. Okay, never mind. I I
reject that statement. You got ripped
off on some Alabama white sauce brisket
and we failed. I'm gonna bomb the guy on
A first. I'll come back around for you.
Actually, there's a bunch of them there.
So, two
bombs. Four targets there. These should
fall good.
There's five.
Excellent bomb. Unfortunately, the
flying wasn't as good. I'm going down.
Oh no. Jim plane over you. You see him?
Yeah, I do.
Oh, there's the revving. The nervous
revving of the engine. He's peeking.
He's That was two. That works. Whoa.
Okay. Oh my.
And reloading again. The KV2 experience.
Hey, look at that. The parade is gone.
I'm going to have to make my way to
Bravo here in a second.
I'd be happy to join you. What are you
in? T34 BT5. Never mind. Yeah, BT5. A
sport model. Why do you say BT5 and
start laughing sick? It's this miniature
team. Oh, you're gone. You just
kidnapped. Maybe that might be why Jim I
poked out of my little hideyhole for 5
seconds and then Okay. All right. Thank
you. No problem.
Unfortunately, he had friends. Oh, no.
As much as I do love KV2, it is not the
optimal tank to try and hold an entire
city by yourself when there's multiple
targets.
Think of the anxiety of loading that
giant shell back in that that breach. I
see that guy in the corner. He's down.
Very nice. One flanked around here to
the right. He's pushing fast. Okay, I
got a sto. I can't do anything to stop
him. Good job, Jim. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you. Oh, yep. He's He's just
going to cross the street. I'm watching
one right there, one close to me here.
Okay, I'm going to try to angle and get
the shell to have a shell loaded so I
can stop some of these. I'm marking a
map for team. That one's right there.
Looking at your marks. I'm Oh god. I
leave that one to the KV1 if you can.
Focus on the panc of you.
I'm actually going to help that. All
right, that is done. That noise has been
put to rest. Okay, thank you. I'm going
to help him repair his barrel. Set
danger right there on that line. I'm
almost reloading my barrel once. Uhoh.
Where's the me? Uh, right here. There's
a lot of ammo in like 25 square ft here.
So, yeah. There's also there's a lot of
fences in that way, Jim. So, if you
can't take You got right there. I got
him. Nice work. I used the uh I used the
sap shell. So, I was able to get through
that fence. KV1 has a repair, but he'll
be done before we get to him.
So, do you know why I picked a KV2 as
like one of the first things I play in
ground forces CBT back in the day? No,
let us know. I was kind of obsessed with
the KV2 in Company Heroes 2 cuz it was a
nuisance and a static defensive posture.
I see. And I was like, "Oh, it's not War
Thunder."
So, the obsession kind of just
transferred to this game. I think
everyone went through their KB2 phase
where they realized that this this
vehicle was so comically silly that it
actually existed and it has some really
good lore. It's just a phase bomb. My
favorite KB2 lore was it that was there
not a KB2 that held a road for 3 days
during the uh Winter War. I wasn't
there, but I I can't confirm that. Okay.
I know there was something. Yeah, I've
heard the story. I'm just making
Yeah. Uh, that was from front
firefly down
the street behind the pharmacy. Why did
I shoot that apartment complex? Not the
chaffy. What's wrong with me right
there? You got a friendly KB1 behind you
trying to get a shot. Maybe I snapshot
that so quickly. I don't know why I did
that. Okay, friendly uh KB1 is uh
repairing you. That's okay. No, no, no.
Let's get old together. Also, I realized
you have right there. What? Jim, you're
left. What?
Yeah, getting old together didn't really
work out, did it? I was distracted by
the drinks on your fender. Forever
alone. Those are molotov cocktails, my
man. Those aren't for drinking. Oh,
there's gasoline in there. Well, I mean,
there's a they're for a different type
of party.
Resist. That's another awesome Russian
lore that I love. The origin of the name
Molotov cocktail.
Please do
tell. Well, so as the
uh Russo Finnish war was kicking off, I
believe Molotov had to testify in front
of the League of Nations that no, we're
not bombing Finland. We're actually
dropping them food. Though the Finnish
caught wind of that, designed the
Molotov cocktail, and I quote, because
we thought Mr. Molotov would have a nice
drink with his
picnic. Though it may not be, I may be
leaving out some details, but that's
actually the uh TLDDR on that actually.
the worst thing that could possibly
finally found me.
You know, I often forget that the uh
Collia Sherman is a thing until I'm
brutally reminded that it is in fact a
thing. Jim, I'm looking forward to
seeing if the YouTube comments verify
your story as true or fiction.
Well, the best thing I can say is that
uh call it trucker history. Trucker
history. I tell it like a truck driving
story where I may exaggerate a couple
things, but at the end of the day, I
mostly got it right. And it's been
passed down through a couple of
truckers. Yeah. Through a couple CB
channels. I'm in danger.
Oh
no. Try to get to you, Pooky. Uh, just
drop art on me. I can't do that. I want
to start throwing molotov cocktails at
this chaffy. Yeah, please do that. I I
am a heavy tank. I have no no arty. Hey,
running away
there. Okay, I will have visual shortly
if I pass by a couple of these block
flats. So, for the second half of this
video, we're going to play my favorite
ground forces vehicle in War Thunder,
which is tough for me to like define
because there's like five to 10 I would
call my favorites. And I'm looking at my
service record. I'm kind of ashamed at
what it's M22, KV220, M18, Cobra King,
IS-6,
M43105, R3T20, KV1B, the Scorpion, and
the Panther 2.
I think I have a type. There's there's a
lot of like heavy tanks mixed in there.
So, you're telling me that as many years
as this game's been out, and this is
your thousandth video, the one ground
forces vehicle you have the most battle
in battles in is the M22 Locust. Yeah. I
don't know if I should be proud of that
or ashamed. I should be proud. That's a
proud thing. You know what? I like how
that's a hill you're willing to die on.
So, what battle rate you want to play
locust at?
And why is it 70? That's Oh, no. Why is
it 70? Because I have my Locust in a 70
lineup.
Why?
Because it's fun. I promise you it's
fun. Here. Here we go, Jim. Okay. I
Okay. Did you find a bigon? Oh my gosh.
I found a big Yeah, that's the sounds I
was listening to. I'm sorry. That's
okay. Oh, Jim, where was it?
Hiding in a building. Hey, you pick on
me. Come back
here. I got the first one.
There's so many. I hear so many engines.
I got the Rattel that was trying to get
behind you.
I think they're mad. There's one behind
me, by the way. If you could let through
the soft squishy things and kill the big
Soviet heavy things, I'd be very
appreciative. It's a Tiger 2 stick. Uh,
okay. Yep. I'm turning. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Cuz that one I don't want to rumble
with if I don't have to. Cannon and and
gunner.
Help him with the track if I
can. Hey, I need that guy to die. That's
scary to turn at me. Commander and
horizontal. I know. I know. I know. I'm
I'm You are way more stressed than I am.
You actually have a cannon for this
battery rating. Loader. Don't go back.
Go back. Don't. What was that?
There's two. Take a breath. You're okay.
I'm the one the locust. Why are you
stressed out? Cuz I have to keep you
alive. No, you don't. Take care of
yourself. I'm fine. I'm a
locust. They won't find you cute and
adorable. There it is. See, they just
execute you on the spot.
Nobody likes
T92s, but M22 fun and cute. Hi there,
sir.
Can I follow you? There's three of them
there. I know. I'm following him. Oh my
god. Jim, please help him. Uhoh. That
one follow me. I'm trying, but guess
what? I'm coming back in a locust.
I recently found out that there is bars
in Japan that celebrate, some would say
even worship Texans. Have you seen these
honky tons? I actually I've heard that
Texans have gone over there and they're
treated like celebrities for the night.
I mean, think about it.
You know what that means, Jim? I want to
go. We got to take B. You bail off trip
to Japan. I would be found
desirable at a bar for once in my life.
I got shot. I deserve that.
I deserve everything that's happened to
me right now for saying that. He He was
living in a fantasy and he's crumbling
down. Just like every anime fan when
they go mouth. That's awesome. What? I
got shot. Yeah, it's right there.
Jim, he don't look happy. What are we
going to do? I'm I'm ready to die by
you. Trying to live. Don't come back for
us. Oh god. Your bids flew over me.
Inappropriate.
That's That's very LWD. Jim, what do we
do about that? I'm fantasizing that I'm
at a maid cafe in Japan. Oh, well, each
to their own. It's your fantasy, not
mine. They They call me senpai and son.
I'm not going to I shouldn't repair you,
but I'm going to. Thank you. Can we go
to the Texas? The Texas. We're going to
run. That's what we're going to do.
Okay. I want I want to be in a better
place. Left is bad. Go right.
Understood.
Uh, left is very bad. Look at that guy.
It's here. Oh, it's a Ferdinand. I ain't
afraid of no ghost. You want to pick on
him? I kind of want to pick on him.
Yeah, he ran into a wall. Let me Can we
get his ankles? I'll go for the right
one. Oops. I missed. I didn't do
anything to him. Here. What if we go
this way? Hang on. I wonder if he's
going to be pointing at us. Let me see.
Let me see. Let me see.
Where are he?
I don't know. He's behind this building.
I don't see him yet.
Take a little peek. Oh, yeah. He's right
there, Jim. Oh,
I got a machine gunner. Take that. I'm
going around him. He just murdered you.
Oh, yes, he did. See, you have the
advantage. You're close. I have the
Yeah, I don't feel like I have an
advantage here.
Lower. Uh, Jim. Yes. We're going to need
to call somebody. Yeah. Can we call
Thank you, Stick. Yeah. Thank you. Yeah.
You almost killed me though, but I
appreciate it.
Look, you got to live. You don't get to
complain. You took my track, sir.
Also, it's still not safe here. I know,
but I'd like to go now. It could be
safer. I'd really like to go now.
Where where are we going to go? It's not
going anywhere. That's not an option.
Actually, here's a hot take. So, the
halftrack I'm in. You know what this
thing actually is to me in in the year
of our Lord 2025? An off-road vehicle.
No. The most overpriced Facebook
marketplace thing in the world. Everyone
who has one of these and they put them
on marketplace thinks they go for 60
grand. Well, yeah, Jim, they do. No,
they do not. Yeah, they do, Jim. They're
It's It's history.
Yeah, but when it has a when when the
dude is so lazy that he can't even put
the original drivetrain in there, he has
to put a 350 Chevy with a turbo 400
transmission and calls it quote unquote
all original bent to Normandy hery
dirtly dirt. No, it's not 60 grand. I
was thinking about gee, I wonder what I
could get realistically for my fully
built Nissan Frontier Overland vehicle.
The one you just bought? Yeah. and then
go buy a fully pristine 1979 Oldsmobile
Cutless Supreme Coupe in a very
beautiful blue down in
Chicago. I'll even send you the link. It
was actually beautiful. I'm like, I
would daily the heck out of that.
You know,
Jim, voices like this might be why we
don't have money. When I was a kid, my
parents had a 89 cutless that's less
desirable.
A 1993 Cutless Supreme saved my life
when I was a kid. I always I've always
appreciate Olden Bill for that.
Jim, I will let you pick what the next
battery when we play locust that is.
Well, since you've given me that kind of
power, let's rip the band-aid off and do
120. I like how you were like, "Oh, 70
is really high. Are you sure?" And then
you just push us straight to 12.
Sometimes you got to go the full boore,
man. I'm in a Locust. There's a
Challenger 2 to my left and I think I
You chose this. I asked what bettering
you wanted and you said 120. So here we
are. Well, you can't back out of this,
Jim. You're the one who put in the
application. Tank at the corner. I'm
alive. I mean, yeah, I'm alive. I fire
for effect. NBT's best tank, mini battle
tank, right? Yeah. Let Can we hide in
the corner together and cower? That's my
current plan. Let's pretend that like
we're props like we're we're like we're
that Buick over there. They're pushing
aggressively. Oh gosh. All right. That
Buick is a lot nicer looking than us.
Jim, get ready for side shot. I like how
we're all three hiding behind the same
building here. I'm I'm ready for side
shot. Maybe to take out a track. They're
going around out here. I'm going to drop
Arty down the road from us or up the
road from us. I would drop the right
there on that guy. Already did. Thank
you. He just backed off.
Oh no. I wouldn't pee that. It's not.
It's in front of us on B.
Oh, he just
you're hiding even more over there now
cuz I can see me. Can you make it to me?
Cuz I can't make it to you.
It's safer over here. I promise.
That's Oh, there's two of them just
sitting there. Do not peek out. All
right. Yeah. Uh don't go more left than
Jim's body. See you. I already dropped
it over there. When do you get your RD
back?
Uh, I'm uh stick
places front front.
Good news. They picked me. This is
awkward.
Jim, to your front right. Trees are
falling down. Jim, around the corner.
Just drove past you. What do you mean?
Around the corner.
What? I was speaking about that one.
He wasn't supposed to do that. He was on
a mission to murder you. He really was.
And guess what? He's going to get my lab
a cuz that's the only thing I have
points for. Okay. Stick. Hey, can you
make it to this dumpster over here? It's
safe. I don't I maybe keep your head
down. Keep
moving. It's probably not safe over
here,
though. Let me take a little peek. Yeah,
don't go that way. Treat slow down.
Okay. So, should we go the other way?
Well, Mr. Murderface is over there, but
maybe he's distracted in full. Mr.
Murderface? I saw what he did to you.
Yeah, he did very much over my face.
All right, pushing across. It seems
relatively safe. Relatively for now.
Pushing up here.
Was not safe. Huh? Oh no. Where'd that
come from? Behind you. Behind the rock.
The rock to your right. The rock to my
right. Something's
burning. A lot of rocks over here. Stick
marking a map. I'm kind of flanking
around. Thank
you. Okay. I think it's dead.
You think?
Yeah. I don't see anything else that's
uh moving that's alive. Jim, can I hang
out with you? Uh yeah. Let's get to more
cover here. My flank is exposed.
That's a little thing. What is it? I
don't know. It's quick and fast. It's
like a BMD. I'll push left. Okay. I hear
Yeah, it's moving this way. I might be
able to get it. Jim, that's not a BMD.
That's a TDU1.
Oh goodness. It was moving so fast I
couldn't really tell. I'm sorry. That
was the worst call I've had today.
It's been a while since top tier. I
apologize, sir. I thought I had a
chance. An MBT just drove past like He's
now speeding off, by the way. Oh,
really? Okay. Hit and run,
coward. I hear him. Yeah, he went down
there to the right.
I'm just watching my dead body. This is
very sad. Yeah, you'll come off that
way. They'll be to You just Jimmy's
coming back behind you. Behind me. He
just shot the guy that was following
you.
I got him. I won. Good job. I'm proud of
you. I'm the best. Giving you a thumbs
up. You can't see it. Thank you. No, I
appreciate it. I'm going to go try to
capture A now and probably die. Have a
nice life as you explode.
What hit you? Uh, their AA hit me with a
freaking like anti-ship missile. So,
after that traumatic experience, it is
your choice, stick boy, at what battle
rating we play the Locust. Oh, I No, we
we should go to its
home nice and safe and and be effective
teammates and go down to 2.0. You just
want to live more in 14 seconds.
That actually makes a lot of sense. I
agree with Stick, actually. Hey, Jim.
Yes. Thick said 2.0.
Yes, he did. What was in your lineup?
M1 A1HC.
So, uh,
Jim, that's um,
why do you want to hurt me? I It was an
accident. I was distracted because my M1
A2 SE was screw locked and so so I
swapped it out. I said, I'm ready to go.
I forgot I brought the other Abrams.
Jim, the team is not happy with us. I I
know they're not. They can They can
write a complaint to
corporate that. Okay. I I I deserve
that. You two instantly perish.
Yep. Meanwhile, I've been adopted by an
Abrams. And where I've gone, he's gone.
And he keeps trying to protect me. And I
appreciate
that. If I stop moving, he stops
moving. I'm his emotional support
locust. I found a home.
I'll peek the corner for him.
Be careful. There's a lot in that city.
As you say that, the poor Leopard 284
next to me has uh
vanished. I mean, the tank is still
there. The people inside are no
longer. The Abrams has left
me. One pushing in the corner at me,
too. This is not good. Abrams,
I heard the A factory is having a
lowercase A special just for us. It only
makes sense we get this map for 1,000
ground forces videos.
Welcome back to the another exciting
summer season of the Aactory Tours,
where we have a special on all forms of
lowercase A's, including bold and
italicized. What about comics hands?
Sorry, that was yesterday.
Tacoma.
No,
sir. Please hold your questions till I
can't drive.
That's what I get for saying comic
sands. Yeah. Pushing through there.
Terrible. Oh, hey Jim. I would hide. I'm
hiding. I'm hiding. I'm hiding. Where
are we hiding from? Hiding. Contact
close right to me. T28 entering by the
pipes.
Okay. Moving up behind Bo to get a shot.
I'm just trying to push up as far as I
can.
I got a lot of movement to my close
right over here. Yep. Yeah. I'm not sure
how my six is looking.
One immediate right of me. Okay. I just
realized I was actually following stick
and not you, Bo. That's
okay. Hi, Jim. I'm hiding with you. Oh
my gosh, there's a big gray beast out
there. I'd recommend you two pushing
that side if you can. Just flank around.
I'll hold this corner. That's a good
idea. Actually, I might push for this
guy.
I see one running out from over
there. That is a Stewart maybe or M2 and
AA coming up from this side back here.
Okay, me and Jim are pushing around now.
I'm just kind of in intelligence
gathering mode right now. Thank you.
Thank you.
You guys good over here? Yeah, I'm just
waiting for the artillery to kill me.
It's a lot of orange smoke by me. All
right, next push is over here. Friendly
to me just died. Careful stick. moving.
Oh, I I am not stopping. Don't worry
about that. My shot's no good. Mark
right there. Stick
ricocheted. I like how he wasn't even
distracted by you.
Waiting for you to finish. Got his crew.
Got his crew. I don't have a gunner.
I have no angle. Oh god. Stick. Bad
things are happening. Stick is knife
fighting that guy.
Need help over there. All good. He's
down. Okay, good. BT over here. I have
no shot. Sorry. Bad mark. Okay. I'm
trying to look. Trying to look. BT is
sitting right there. Okay. I also have
no shot. I'm too far back. I'm hoping
you can't see the top of us. Okay. There
may be something right here. I need to
look. I just got shot on the back.
Looking for it. Turning. Turning. Or
that could have been from the right.
Just glanced off me. Oh, it was it was
in here. So, I'm not crazy. He's hiding.
He's hiding with the machinery. It's a
Stewart. I thought there was a couple.
Got an engine. Engine on him. Gunner.
What? One swarm. There's so many of us.
Okay, bounced off. Come on. Nice kill
stick. Holy moly. All right, now now all
our teammates are here. I broke my
transmission on that. Oh, stick. I got
him.
All right, I'm hiding in the building
because I'm scared. Oh, hi. Another
locus came in. This is getting a little
weird. Yeah, I'm not that Locust. Please
do not call me that
Locust. I think he's watch. I'm not
sure. I I I don't I don't really know.
We got teammates wishing Bravo. So, we
either help defend A or move down
towards B and C. There's going to be a
thing. Hello here.
I hear bombs. Big Japanese. Big
Japanese. I think that's a ho, Jim.
Hoor. Yes. Thank you. I I had forgotten.
All right. He's down.
Oh god. Can left. Oh god. I'm sorry. I
sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry. I'll get beside you. Jim, I'm
sorry. It's okay. It's okay. Things
happen. I was trying to keep IKV alive
since I kind of got in his way. Stick
right there behind that. When you're
tiny and fast, things happens. And autoc
can to your front left. Yep.
I can't see the guy behind
there. Thank you for killing that.
Uh-huh. I'm going to go get a crew
member now.
I could use one as
well. Let me mark this guy on map for
the IKV.
and I'll make my way to
you. Jim, your tour didn't really uh go
well there. Oh, it was actually awful.
The uh the AAC has actually been caught
slipping on a lot of their tours.
They're having a lot of industrial
accidents as of late.
What kind of safety standards do you
have around here?
Well, there was a lawsuit here, a
lawsuit there. Uh, they actually hired a
safety guy. That really should not have
been the safety guy.
Was it you? It's a long story. I'm
actually waiting for a uh a drama
YouTuber to come out with a video essay
uh bomb uh on the uh Just kidding. Never
mind. It was just plain freaking me out.
Just kidding. You can't say that as I'm
stuck here getting a crew member. I
looked up and I saw this big old plane
and I was waiting for the bomb and I
realized that he was just waving off.
But yeah, no, I'm actually waiting for a
drama tuber to drop like a 90-minute
video on like the fall of the aactory.
What they don't want you to know. Are
both of you okay? Oh, I'm perfectly
fine. I think Jim's having a little bit
of a moment.
Bomb is here. Oh. Oh gosh. All right,
we're good. No stick. We're not good. We
are absolutely not good. You're on fire.
You're on fire. Put yourself out. Let me
fix you. I'm getting I'm getting now.
You're dead. Jim, maneuver kill. BT BT
engine radiator BT5. I cannot see the
BT. There's a flaming airplane in front
of me. Don't worry, I got it anymore.
God, I hope not. I don't want to be here
anymore. Yeah, let's go to the B point.
We're abandoning the A factory and going
to the Bravo factory. I don't think the
B point is safe either,
Jim. At this point, I think it's the
fact that we're all together. I think
the B factory has better food,
personally.
How y'all doing? Welcome to the B
factory. We make all farms the letter B.
It's a different voice. Of course it is.
You think it wasn't going to be a
different voice? We make cursive bees
and we make little bees and we make big
bees. I heard a thing that if you write
in cursive/ uh you know normal print
font, if you do the 50/50 thing, you
either had trauma as a child or you're a
serial killer. Really? I I didn't know
that. I as you know someone who's who
writes left-handed. I've been told
constantly that apparently I'm a
psychopath. But all right, whatever.
They don't know me. Oh, that's just cuz
you write left-handed, Jim. I need to
stop reading these theories. Also, what?
Wait, wait, wait. What? What kind of
trauma results in a person writing in
cursive and regular at the same time? Do
you write like that? Yeah. You've had a
lot of trauma. What kind of trauma?
Childhood trauma. Oh no, my barrel's
out. Help. Help me. Can we get a mark
where that target is? Uh, end of the
railroad tracks.
It just got you.
Have you ever heard of the broken bone
theory as well?
Like if you've broken a bone? Yeah. If
you've never broken a bone, that means
you're going to have a life of emotional
trauma.
But I've never broken a bone. I've
cracked bones, but I've never like
straight up like broken a bone in half
where I need a cast. I've had
reconstructive knee surgery. What does
that count for?
You play football? Wait. Yeah. Do I just
have a lot of trauma? Should I stop
telling you these theories? Are we
having a moment with stick where he
Every single one is my truth? Oh gosh.
So, now that we're out that match, I can
actually properly read to you more on
what this theory is. So, the never broke
a bone theory suggests that a person who
has not yet broken a bone in their body
at any point in their life is said to be
made or is meant to experience immense
physical, emotional, and spiritual
challenges. That make you feel any
better? No. I've never broken a bone.
Also, for our last match in Locust,
we're going to do 6 because that is the,
in my opinion, the most fun bat rating
for Locust. Personally cannot wait to
bully all the German heavy tanks.
Panthers are actually really fun to rats
in the
Locust. That's my favorite target. First
off, I' like to apologize for the map we
got. Oh god. Secondly, I'd like to just
make a note that the Locust is very much
trash panda energy as
well. It's kind of cute, you know, looks
docile. Get close to it, it might rip
your finger off.
Can we find a dumpster on the A point,
please?
Jim, I don't know if we're going to make
it across that field, but I'm going to
just run straight at the cat point. Me,
too.
It'll be like the last of the
Boheans. That was a reference that I
don't think Stick will ever have a
chance at getting.
I'm glad you understand when you made
that that you knew I
didn't. And you should see it. You
should watch that movie.
I feel like at this point we're just
going to need to make a list of all the
movies that you think I should watch.
Jimmy, you got that reference right,
please.
Totally, buddy. You've never heard of
Last of the Moheakans, the movie. Oh,
Moheakans. I thought you were saying
Boheans. I said last weekend. It was a
pun.
Oh, because of what's about to happen to
us. Okay. I try to make good references.
I'm I just You try You try to raise
them, right? You know, it's okay. I I I
know things that some people don't know
either. It's okay. It's all about things
on the point.
Yeah, I see right here. I messed up. I'm
sorry. Goodbye. What is it? What is it?
Oh jeez. He just fired. Swarm. I got his
engine machine gunner transmission.
Okay. I
Somebody's got him right before he fires
again. Commander. Commander, he's down.
Okay. Good job. Good job. Hiding places,
everybody. Hiding places. Okay. Uh, can
somebody stay in the cap if they can
find a spot? Yep. I'll find a I'll stay.
I'll stay. Yeah. Let me uh I think I
need a small repair here. Please be
small. Just kidding. It's a 30 secondond
repair.
I'm looking for targets pushing us.
Thank you, sick. They're all up
here. Drop already on that mark if you
can.
Hey, I'm also going to get a crew member
cuz that really really hurt that first
round. So far, all I'm seeing is tigers.
That's the bad news. I We can't do
tigers. It's out of my pay grade. Yeah.
The problem is it's like there's five
tigers. Oh yeah, it's actually pretty
bad. Couple of them are down.
They're just Cresting Hill looking for
us right now. See what what what big
brother Sherman told me is that like
there's only one Tiger. Can you call Big
Brother Sherman? Uh, no. I think he
blocked me. Tiger on me. Push you in
this corner. Uh, firing for effect.
Prepare yourself.
Uh, his track just kicked that. Don't
worry, he turned. Yeah. Oh, he's coming
towards you. He's coming towards you.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I didn't expect him to
go this way. Coming towards you. He's
coming towards you.
He's on me. Okay. I'm I'm trying to I'm
trying to He's focused on me.
Repositioning. Repositioning. Can you
take his barrel or something? Uh uh uh.
I'm trying. I'm trying. I'm trying. Come
on. Get the gun up. Get the gun up. I'd
like to disappear before he fires again.
I'm okay. My tracks also. His barrel's
gone. His barrel's gone. I'm
repairing. His friends may get frisky
and push as well. Okay, I'm going to try
to mark a map. Try to take his tracks.
Try to take his tracks. Bomb is falling.
Oh gosh. Please.
Uh yeah, we have company here,
gentlemen. Something there. I I see we
do. I'm holding fire for now. Hey, I'm
going to back off before that barrel
comes back online and murders. Panther.
The Panther's here. The Panther? What do
you mean the panther's here? Panther's
here. Oh, the Panther's here. Driver on
him. Hey, nothing on him. Driver,
gunner,
loader. He is down. Oh, nice shot. Uh,
how's Tiger? Tiger, can we kill this
tiger? His barrel. I will sacrifice
myself for the cause.
He got shot in the face. He's down. Oh
my gosh.
Where did you pen from? Under his belly.
Under his belly. You got to rub that
belly. Oh my gosh. Get in there and
scratch it man out here actually like
petting tiger. I told you 6 is the best
battle rating for Locust.
Do you believe me? Now I can already
hear Tiger and and Panther mains like
just grinding their teeth. And we are
going to get bombed so hard. We need to
like find a new spot. Uh, I don't want
to. Where are we going to go?
Into the forest. We're going to become
like forest creatures. He did say we
were raccoons. Yeah, we're little
whimsical creatures. That's what we are.
Returning to our roots.
You're getting a little brave peeking
like that. I
am. I I'm I'm just waiting for something
like that's very thin skin to crest the
hill like a dick or
Max. Part of me wants to run down there
and harass the things they're going
around us, but also our defensive A has
been so good. I don't want to leave and
lose it. I mean, we we we kind of are
the team, I think. Uh, gentlemen,
incoming. Incoming. Incoming. 236. 236.
236.
Yeah. So, I don't fight that. That is an
Yeah, that's out of our pay grade. I
shot at it to make it make myself feel
better.
Did it work, Jim? He does have one
reload. Yeah. So, I think we're going to
be okay for about like 5 seconds.
There's a Panther sitting right here
beside me. I'm going to try to take him.
Panther just shot. Okay. Pushing on his
side. Gunner damaging his barrel.
Shot out his barrel. I'm going to take
his driver
next if I
can. All right. A little bit more left.
There he goes. Oh,
man. Amazing how you can surgically pick
that apart. Hey, something over there.
Yeah. I'm surprised I'm still alive
right now. I thought for sure they would
uh murder me.
I mean, I guarantee you you have a hit.
Looks like an ISU.
Why am I looking at what Jim's looking
at? Okay, there's there's going to be
big things. There's a plane. Oh, okay.
That almost landed on me.
Galaxy.
It's very strange getting best squad
when we basically ran three locuses that
entire time.
pretty much. And I I I drove six feet in
a Hellcat and that's really all I did
today despite watching my friend
surgically dissect panthers and tigers.
Go for the soft sides, the love
handles. I got to write that down.
[Music]