also I heard the a factory is under
investigation by
OSHA it was something about an
italicized a it leaned over too far and
crushed a worker I heard that there was
a comic Sanai running away from the
scene well I just want to let you know
that some of the workers are actually
AOK there is uh two Panthers and a tiger
2 tiger one not
a ignore me three
cats three German cats middle of the map
Courtyard copy three German meow at
Bravo meow meow meow meow
meow eyes on I see two but there's also
a friendly nearby so I'm going to drop
it long hope t34
survives might get something three down
no friendlies
nice the box has been flipped over I
repeat the box has been flipped over box
has been
flipped the kitty litter has been
changed
the catnip is dry I don't know if catnip
is the catnip is expired I mean it's a
plant catnip is freaking wild by the
way does the
matter this
scary you don't trust my aviating skills
in a four engine
bomber that's my home you're flying like
it's a fighter I grou up watching Tail
Spin go get another water heater it's a
barrel of tea excuse
you can't believe how ungrateful stick
boy is being he's demanding you to go
get a barrel of
tea before we get too far into the video
with the AC4 which is a really enjoyable
tank that I've always really liked and I
don't know why we haven't done more
content with it got a very capable 17
pounder Cannon really decent armor for
53 and uh pretty capable in terms of
Mobility really nice Australian tank and
uh speaking of Australia gan's running
this really neat promotion that kind of
came out of nowhere where they have a
bunch of stuff bundled together for $25
us so I thought I'd take a quick second
and just run you guys through this
because it's something that I personally
bought for $25 you get the AC4 here
which I particularly like a lot and then
you get some of my favorite planes the
boomerang Mark
1 so you get this guy and then you get
the boomerang Mark 2 but you also get
this camouflage with the boomerang Mark
II you get the rway with this camouflage
you get the Spitfire LF Mark 9 with this
camouflage and then you get a Catalina
Mark
3A with this
camouflage and you also get let me see I
can find him here you also get this guy
the kangaroo as a portrait and then you
get a custom title so I can pull that up
real quick you also get that custom
title oh you also get the grant over
here in the US tree uh with this
camouflage as well it's a lot of
vehicles for
$25 and if you do pick it up I encourage
you to use our affiliate link 3% of your
total purchase will go towards the
support in the channel and um yeah I
just don't want you guys to miss out on
this this promotion will be running for
another 5 or 6 days when this video
releases you can also buy these vehicles
in game for a discount with golden
eagles I'll put those prices up right
now or if you have these vehicles
already and want to buy the camouflages
you can buy those for 200 golden eagles
each so pretty neat deal and if you pick
up the pack or some golden eagles like I
said if you use our fit link I really
appreciate it it's a great way to
support the channel I will shut up now
and we will get into our video thanks
for watching yeah I got to go to the
Bass Pro I got to get some ice augers
and some new stuff for ice fish in there
the Lake's finally freeze over we can
actually drive our trucks up there and
uh you know drill a couple holes in the
ice put a nice Shack out there and uh
you know drink uh drink them pippers
away there and uh hopefully the wies
don't bother us there cuz we'll be in
the middle of nowhere and uh you know
hopefully we get some walleye tuget on
them lines there in that right stick boy
oh yeah time to go get the ice shacks on
the ice oh yeah you got pull them out
there only thing you're catching is a
Lake Perch how dare you yeah no walleye
is good fishing you don't insult the
walleye perch are very
tasty perch is kind of a midf fish mid a
lot you think they're really is they're
mid well yeah when you got the Walleye
out there they're way better yeah you're
not walleye material no every every
midwesterner knows the only oh oh that
just really went tragic for you it did
somebody lost their fishing license no I
did DNR showed up J that's why you only
get two lines per person I'm sorry I got
too excited there but I had like six on
the end of my truck I just failed 17
pounder and I'm just going to break a
garage door or a shelf I'm just
I'm just sad I'll go first no I'll go
first okay we all life in life I he just
made a that joke about shelving
units I'm ready to go put it on the
Shelf I let him capture
B I'm going to push forward into here
see what awaits
me any specials in the
mall uh let's take a turn to here
yeah s say I'm he yep yep I'm hearing
things I'm hearing engines I'm here I
see it it's tiger I missed it I'm sorry
good luck um can you there's a second
tiger I'm still reloading good luck oh
that's a Sherman okay stop nameing
things off not help just Li to me say
like there's cute and cudly puppies at
the mall and they just need
homes and pets oh well I mean but this
is the problem is this is a m down by G
oh that's a
trappy hey if this was a mall down by me
I mean I could tell you about the zoo
that they put in the mall but this is a
mall down by jym think there's a tiger
right there
now I was looking for those other two
hold on ch right
there don't worry about him oh you're
gone the chaffie got
you I should have worried about him I
didn't think the chaffy was going to get
you I'm sorry I put him last in my
threat
assessment I don't want to go to bassc
ever with either of you oh you want go
to the one in Memphis where they got the
pyramid oh but Jim they're not going to
have good ice fish and stuff down there
yeah I know but like they got the
pyramid one Bass Pro was a mighty
king I don't know a hotel it's a hotel
you can actually sleep in there why
would I want to sleep in a bass TR
because it's
cool I love how offended he's
getting yeah he's he's more like a
Cabella guy even though they're owned by
the same how no
Shields Shields what is a Shields oh you
haven't been to a Shields oh he's
getting upset in that Midwestern accent
let me let me tell you about a Shields
gym you ever want to go to the store and
go look at jacuzzi then go ride a ferris
wheel
indoors B I'm not going to lie never
I've never been so afraid to be a
midwesterner when when stick boy just
started like doing those satanic chants
of like Ferris wheels and what is he
talking about look Jim I think you
should come over here we'll go can we
push the enemy or we just just going to
sit here and talk about outdoor shops we
go ride the shield sparis wheel right oh
no let me go first I just want make sure
that you good okay then what we'll do
Jim is we'll go take you to the Mall of
America and we'll go ride the indoor
roller
coasters you know I'm pretty sure the
Mall of America in 10 years time will be
the only Mall open in America I feel bad
for this one and then it'll be the Mall
of America yeah and then like the rest
of the United States will be paid as a
parking lot we've prepared right right
okay back up no I Ain the shot for you
it's a good thank you use me as
cover he doesn't know you're nice shot I
saw that thank you thank you I'm proud
of you thank you I will remember you
father we'll do a second Loop of the
ferris wheel in memorium if you come
down the Texas gym I'll take you to uh
bies you know there's a Facebook page
called truckers against bies what what
did bies do to truck drivers I'm going
to assume it's a traffic because um it
gets Rowdy in there well I do want to I
actually want to deliver fuel to the
world's largest bies and have me and
five other fuel trucks just kind of like
waiting line get some beaver nuggets and
some brisket that sounds really good
actually take need some beaver
nuggets I'm more worried about the gas
station blowing up
brisket no it's bies brisket it's not a
bies is not just simply a gas station
but it is a gas is the gas station but
it is a gas
station you know speaking of weird gas
station food there's something I want to
warn everybody who's not from the
Midwest so when you come to the Midwest
and you go to a gas station or a truck
stop you're going to see beef and cheese
right if you eat if you eat the ones in
the sealed plastic bags that are
refrigerated you'll be fine never get
the ones that are sealed and sweaty in
room temperature because you will be on
an offramp squatting on the ground
calling to your ancestors for help I'm
sorry I just remember that movie where
they had hot dogs on the the rotisserie
thing and he goes how long has those
been on there he's like 6 hours and we
can't call them hot dogs they're wizard
fingers
now you know that is true actually
Speedway tries to give me so much like
free food like hey do you want a free
burger or a roller dog and I'm like yeah
the roller dog that's so roller dog
that's what they are yeah it's it's so
cooked it's purple and it's been on
there for 10
hours have they tried to get you with
the pot stickers no what is a pot
sticker
oh
boy remember I'm not from with tank two
tanks I just panic and miss both Jim
it's all you uh oh gosh that's a big one
um I hit one I didn't do anything
pushing up I got the transmission on
okay very good I'm going to reload the
sh take your
time okay BK down backing up M6 is still
on the left yes yes it is uh no eyes I
see him there J I got shot in the back
that's the tiger that's a whole new
thing he's a magician dring already in
there hey Tiger's down St on me you did
I can see it it's a s sug one of the two
engine loader r i I just came around the
corner I went behind me and you were
staring at him like o look at this I
just came around the look at this piece
of meat on the board why it was
juicy
okay I'm going to go Decap C and hope
not die St not juicy Jim I'm just
concerned why he was allowed to live I
do not judge stick in front I'm worried
about your eyesight stick
I was thinking hold on hold calm down I
am not you're being shot at from the
right it's a paner three it's fine I you
died to a chaffer I would not just say
that he's protected be careful his
ancestors on his side right contact
right okay trying to get a shot trying
to get a
shot yeah we got bombed you got bomed I
got bombed okay I I helped don't worry
Bo you have me
B can I interest you in a gas station
make your Barrel doesn't go into my line
of fire I really appreciate that hey B
yes run why run Jim was dropping bombs
oh that's big
bomb say it with more Vigor stick like
you're actually going to
die I am hearing noises though there's a
whole bunch of them down here got the
first one there's going to be two more
to my hard right one out by the building
on that Mark there stacking up on your
left one of Panthers pt6 close was all
right looking looking looking BK engines
out you can take him okay BK Gunner out
you got him in the next shot I'm firing
PT jump scared me I'm sorry that's okay
where's the PT he gone it was 21 I'm
sorry there is a panther closer though
right there yeah I can't hit him
unfortunately these rocks are in my way
there's a bunch of stuff on I can finish
him just watch for other
targets yep if you can't get the I I got
the G breach where was that
at
uh in all of the the bung houses out
further past bu houses to your right yes
the bunk houses I said bung house just I
didn't know what that was that's why I
was confused I know that's why I tried
correcting myself before you something
from Minnesota or buck house is oh
God yeah I'm I'm here I'm going to push
up careful motan camping you'll never
come out of
them Minnesota summer camp I'm sure is a
different
experience out there
you I can hear the Law and Order music
as we enter the camp
time kind of Camp is this stick boy
Minnesota summer camps are
great are they where you fishing tons of
boating oh I was not allowed to
go I think a canoe once
how'd you do that when you shove the
entire football offensive uh line into
one canoe oh bad things happened yeah
like the Titanic they should got you a
pontoon they should have got you a
pontoon you got to stop making friends
like that he ping oh I got that was so
awesome sorry I'm so happy I'm happy for
you looks like sounds like smells like
I'm sorry I had a thought but I don't
know how to describe
it you have a great voice for putting
people to sleep you know like those um
asmrs kind of but not what I was looking
for oh like a lullaby or like a go to
bed tape better than the go to bed
rag oh yeah like how like Samuel L
Jackson like read you uh can read you uh
BL up blab with a lot of funny four
letter
words what is he listening to stick I
don't know and I'm kind of scared also
why didn't they go to bed rag not get a
reaction wait they go to that's what you
said
yes that's illegal what did you
hear I heard go to bed rap it's like oh
yeah like the go to bed rap yeah please
Jim tell me sing me the go to bed
rap we are here standing at your bed
telling you that it's time to go to bed
I rymed bed with bed it's time to go to
bed hey hey oh that's an m44 I don't
know what I expected
all right he's down okay good shot I'm
like what is he shooting at I can't see
it I was right by him lobbing a h sh at
us yeah that'd be bad they were here
with the copyright
notice look that's the chaffie I killed
all by myself I'm so proud of you Jim
good job thank you thank you did you use
chloroform no actually I used my gun in
a Sabo round oh think look really
excited to uh get to the
chappie I'm going to go left go right
yeah it's right here
ARL he has no track he can get around
his left oh no no second his left not
his
right good news he shot we weren't ready
loader out on him poking poking hello
sir shoot that side shoot that side
turret gun's out the left side I shot it
as I said too cuz IAD he's down it works
God I shot I just want to make sure the
Gunner went out that's all I was trying
to get from us do anything right Jim
you're the one who ran out in front of
him without a
plan what do you mean I had a
plan dying is not a
plan I I never is gone I'm blind you you
help the other blind people out left
side of the bridge copy no
eyes also there's a two
planes I'm going to push up oh there it
is
why are you laughing as you're driving
away from me cuz I'm laughing at my own
joke I'm looking for he's gone Jim he he
he's it's hiding behind the Rock at the
end I told you where it was I marked the
rock I know I'm just confirming where it
was I was trying to keep you
alive oh I been I was lost my breach I
think stick needs a bedtime rag the
Bedtime rag please no I've got a great
nickname for
him the beaver
duck oh like the platus yeah I just want
to call him Beaver duct though name
Beaver
du oh yeah it's like you have like
Revolver Ocelot and liquid snake Beaver
duck you can be king the other ones have
a thingy and then the animal oh so I'd
be like what would I be like evasive
kangaroo what would be a good nickname
for a claw bear
uh have you ever see a picture of a
quala bear when it's wet it's terrifying
that's from Australia right I'm trying
to remember all my Australian animals if
it's a weird animal it's probably from
Australia that's not
true W bats
aren't yeah they
are oh they're
adorable yeah they are kind of like
Dopey and doughy looking aren't
they they're creeping up on me in the
river bombats no the tanks the enemy T
are pushing me still okay I just say oh
my God what are we playing right now
well that is not going to work you got
the I got the lter but uh we got
time he's coming back again they're in
the river that's that a
bomb well yes it was a
bomb you know what that plane would be
it would be uh what's that bird that
pecks people's eyes out in Australia
what what that a
Magpie no there's literally a bird that
like I hope nobody comes for us for any
animal information we would make the wor
zoologist that's not true I know
penguins have
knees and they're in like a permanent
squat position most animals have
knees I mean a worm doesn't okay but I'm
say things that have legs typically have
knees I mean octopuses don't I just
learned human babies don't have kneecaps
though for a while those are arms oh
yeah they develop yeah kind weird I
think ducks have KNE
well they're Birds they it bends the
other way a penguin's a
bird you're a bird I have a bomb stick
and I'm not opposed to dropping on you
ducks have
knees he just Googled it I wanted to
double check if I was right or
wrong we would write the
misinformation zoo
book uh Jim you got a tank coming on the
road but it will be evaporated shortly
okay thank you I'm going to leave it to
you then
you have a great view see the
bridge no I don't he stopped at the
bridge oh there's two of them it's a
party actually boy you want to know an
animal fact I learned today what's that
I learned that there are naturally brown
pandas okay how did you learn
that uh I was at work and I was we were
helping somebody and we were waiting for
their computer to update cuz Windows
takes forever and they just started
telling me facts about pandas Mr
anti-air
oh hey guys ain't looking too good you
got it good work I got one of them
there's more I yeah okay do you see the
shape of my Lancaster right now it's not
good it looks like your average Faceook
continue on your story I'm just saying
uh multitasking would
be get a big thumbs up from me right
now
multitasking that's a big you're it your
job should be revolving or multitasking
I was good at my job whoa
self-report anyway continue on about the
animals about the
panda well they they there's only like
300 of
them and um they live in the quing Ling
mountains that's not important I just
like saying the name of the mountain I
feel like this is what you did at work
today instead of working have you ever
seen a compilation of like pandas having
like the worst OA accidents like they're
falling out of trees oh yeah no like
like if you ever see like a like a a WWE
like ladder and table match like that is
that is a panda bear in an enclosure
again we should never teach about
animals kind of crazy one one of the
favorite one of the favorite facts that
they told me is that unlike regular
pandas like the black and white Pandas
where their patterns are semi randomized
and their eyes have a full circle around
them the brown panda
only get like extended coloration at the
bottom of their eyes like they're crying
oh I actually I have an I have an animal
fact I'm missing a wheel did you know
the red panda was the original
Panda no wonder why they're so cute yeah
red pandas are
dope I made it back to base safely if
anybody cares your plane's gone no it's
right here I'm looking at it no I I I
you mean the H that was chasing me yeah
I'm helpful thanks Beaver
duck
oh I can call you Platypus no If he if
he was in the Metal Gear Solid Universe
it'd be like promiscuous platypus a
platypus and he would be like a final
boss he's like liquid snake it's me
perous platypus and then like you got to
plug your controller in the second Court
to defeat him like the old game there's
a bunch of guys over here
probably help B out yeah I would
appreciate that cuz there's um I don't
want to die to that one oh I got his
Commander I got
the he angle just a little bit too much
I'm going to be honest though that your
theat right there please please take the
meatballs okay never mind now the level
of panic and the amount of uh large
somebody's face in a
second at usce Burns it's it's aing at
us I have to repair my breach one down
there's two sitting right
here okay stick's almost fixed I got to
I got to remember Jim I cannot try and
engage how B socially awkward you're
like sitting beside each other Jim was
repairing me I was fixing stick battle
buddy you don't want to get lost at the
concert oh well somebody's getting lost
at the concert I got
lost oh well that's what I get for not
holding hands I didn't I didn't for some
reason I want to quote the girl at the
rock
show I'm old I'm sorry Elder emot I'll
leave no it's okay I was there when the
magic was written were are you Jim the
sacred Scroll of Le 1882 yep and Myspace
profiles I'm going to set my song to my
mood Lincoln Park
Numb oh God remember remember the quoes
hey you know if you think about it
Myspace has lasted longer than Tik
Tok he had to make this about him that's
why that's why he said Tik Tok yeah Jim
zomer he's just like I deserve that
foring there Panther friend oh gosh my
turn and a tiger hey s not to tell you
the um bad news but you're kind of the
only one on the 56
line
oh we're all counting on you good luck
we got teammates on the four line
but I'll drop some Rd on a for you Lely
I'll try not to drive into
it I'll be surpris we make it to
a okay I should have said that wow cuz
right right when I said that you got
bomb
wow I was more thinking that you're
going to run into a hord of Tanks I
didn't think you're going to get bombed
I'm so sorry that was so mean I got to
keep those internal thoughts oh I'm
going to die to a
panther yeah see there's the hor tanks
now so I was correct in thinking that
there's going to be a bunch of them I'm
it'll take me a bit the plane didn't
wait for your sentence to
finish no the stairs typically don't
there's a
panther right beside me but I don't
think he knows I'm
here it's drawn the
movement so just stop
moving he's got a friend though now so
I'm going to take the
shot down a
transmission he's got a friend all the
way down that line I hope he doesn't
shoot at me loader okay we're going to
take a few minutes on this one I got the
commander okay I'm going to go for the
driver Department there we go very nice
uh you're getting shot at from the left
I think no that friendly oh okay it
better be
friendly was it tracers yeah it was
green Tracer that's a BTR J close right
oh yeah you're right I see it yep yep
you're going to have to shot at him I'm
going to finish him off oh wow get it
bt42 and here all week sorry I'm getting
shot at so I had no time to laugh yeah I
just don't feel like you appreciate good
tank humor no I do just you know I feel
pretty tankless right
now no here after we get this jumbo
you'll tank me later you just stole my
material and re used it back at me
that's how Comedy
Works sick that's a skink that's not
going to work
mhm well no I'm here to help with the
planes that eventually will come for
your bad joke push him push him it's
foreshadowing oh come on can you get
anything Ang
no I can't bar all right I got to move
all right he he's angling he's looking
at me he's looking at me he's
pcking can we get a shot uh not yet junk
in the way he's he's charging towards
you he's he has no Barrel he's got a
knife he he's ramming
me DC oh that's you all right if you
want anything go for the tracks hold on
I got to get around you you're too big
I'm trying I'm too big I'm being called
out now
oh I'm reload that's bad reload time put
this right on his side give him a good
old slap thank
you we got to push a pushing a
Roger this is a weird mly Crew lineup we
have here don't make fun of the church
there is definitely one on our
right uh well fine go around for
him I'm sure he'll turn around the
minute we touch a Jim I'm going to push
right if you watch left okay we'll do
that I am not looking
left all right decapping a okay looking
left looking left I'm going to go try to
chase the noise that stick curtain all
right do that I'm going to just keep
watching over here oh no Jim that means
he's trusting my hearing oh jeez oh
you're right there's a tiger going wait
for him to turn more keep turning well I
don't feel that bad about my hearing
anymore Tiger's down oh nice
shot it helps when they turn side on to
you
of
course I don't think he saw me though so
he didn't know the tauris in the hair
right that's what it is yes the
difference between a tortoise and a
turtle is very similar to that of a hair
and a bunny yes the tortoise and the
hair well it's not like you're a
father thanks as I got shot in the face
by M36 Point Blank Range that such a
weird display of events
[Music]
a