This round's gone so poorly. I'm
breaking out Team Fortress 2 spy
tactics.
See, it does work.
I just got a double kill party. Hey,
triple.
>> Oh, baby, a triple.
>> Pack more M18s in there next time, boys.
>> Yes,
>> the trifecta Hellcats. Let's go.
>> We'll go for round two.
>> I didn't realize we were out hunting
with artillery. We're big game, not big
artillery.
>> Indirect fire is best fire.
>> Nice shot, Jim.
>> Don't mind me just shooting down the
shooting gallery there.
>> We're way out of this way that I'm
headed.
>> I don't know. I was figuring I flank to
the right, but then I also decided I
want to go this way.
>> Be careful. There's a lost child in the
mall friendly puma. So,
>> copy.
It's trying to get to you guys. I don't
know why every single time we're on this
map, I go through the mall and every
single time I get lost in the mall.
>> It's not that big of a mall.
>> You want candy?
>> No, but it's I I I forget which walls
are destructible, which ones aren't.
>> Are you good, Stick? I just saw you
shoot.
>> Yeah, there's a PT behind that little
little half wall there.
>> Oh, okay. Oh, by the cat cafe. Let me
shoot.
>> Yeah, by the cafe. No.
>> Do we have to go there? Meow. Damn, they
worked very hard on that side.
>> I worked very hard on that joke.
>> Oh. Oh, no. Oh, you
>> all righty. I'm Yep.
>> Can't just take that.
>> Me, please.
>> I don't know what's happening. This is
traumatic. I'm just going to keep
driving.
>> Have we Have we reached that stage of
the battle?
>> Loud noises and and bombs are falling.
>> Contact this corner.
>> Oh, that's a big boy.
>> Contestant.
>> That ain't no Sherman. Shoot that right
there if you can.
>> I am trying. That's a
>> Puma might get it. Eat, Puma. Eat.
I have to take it.
>> An American T34 is stop.
>> I've lost the Puma.
>> Oh no, there's an M18 on me as well.
>> Do you have that corner over there?
Because things are very bad.
>> No, no. M18 close.
>> Dropping more RD.
>> BT76 closer.
>> I am also dropping Ry. Be advised. Do I
just need to push this corner because my
six is collapsing?
>> If you push on that corner, you have to
look hard left. There's two.
>> I got Tiger 2 for friend. His name is
Bonk. Bonk Bonk. I'm following him.
>> I see how it is.
>> Sorry. I have Jim. We've been replaced.
>> Bonk Bonk got bonked.
>> Trying to save him.
>> I got another one party.
>> That's my fourth. Wow.
All right, I'm going to repair him.
>> That one's got DNR on the phone. You got
to make sure he's got a tag on that.
>> At this point, if you got our artillery,
put it down cuz apparently he's hot.
>> No, Bob. Bob.
>> Oh my gosh. There's a Sherman right here
next to me by the mall. He got my
important things.
>> A very large roadblock was just deployed
there.
>> This is the only spot I have for you and
it's very risky. Drop.
>> Drop it.
>> Why did you just die when you did that?
I had hopes for you.
>> Because I'm bad.
>> Oh, stick.
>> How can we make you good?
>> Um,
give me a tank identification book.
Make me
>> two bombs out.
>> There's one.
>> There's a bunch.
>> I'm going back to base.
Hi, welcome to War Thunder, where Bo
becomes a serial killer.
>> I want to make a joke, but I'm going to
be hate because it's probably going to
>> Oh, are you going to Are you going to
have a cool name though, Bo?
>> I probably just have a case number at
some agency.
>> Oh,
>> there's also a lot of planes up.
>> Good night on Netflix. The case the
Texas tickler.
>> The Texas. No, I'm not.
>> Yep. Nope. That's it now.
>> Also, did you see what happened to Elmo
on social media? Somebody didn't tickle
him in a while and all a sudden he just
snapped.
>> Oh, dude. He uh
>> Elmo got out of control.
>> He uh he he took a pill and it was uh
not a very good one.
>> That a tank? Oh my god, that's a tank.
>> Dick, I expect a lot of you and you died
to an AC85.
>> The one vehicle always makes fun of
>> Hey, hey, so when sick boy says, "Wait,
is that a tank? Oh god, that's a tank."
Can we immediately not follow that up
with stick boy, I'm putting my trust in
you. I believe in you.
>> Well, your death didn't affect me
anyways. I'm back at the airfield.
>> Like, I've I've already admitted that I
messed up. I don't need then like the
>> think I'm messing up. I did a very bad
landing over here, so I'm trying not to
>> I'll be back with you in a minute.
>> Like, I already struck out. I don't need
mom yelling at the umpire that it wasn't
a strike. You know,
>> just saying your favorite baseball team,
Minnesota Twins.
>> Okay, now we're just
>> Wait, that's their baseball team?
>> No, now we're just
>> I never knew that.
>> Yeah, Minnesota has a baseball team.
>> Wow, the twins. Like the Twin Cities.
>> Jim, have you ever had somebody look at
you like bonk bonk bonk looks at
Charlie?
That was a mouthful.
>> I don't I don't even know what to say.
How does he look?
>> Also, I got enemy plane on me. Uh, where
should I bomb? Uh, you might as well
just bump B.
>> Is Bon Bon Bon be okay with that?
>> Go right ahead.
>> What is up with all the tracers down
here? What is the
Here. Oh my.
I got two.
>> Well, don't worry. We can always give
him the bonk bonk bonk.
>> Now you're just making it weird.
>> I know.
>> Uh, Jim, contact front. T34.
>> See, trying to get the gun down. I tried
to stop them from firing.
>> Don't worry. Uh,
>> radiator. They both
>> finish.
>> Hey, they got my barrel.
>> Is that a Chappie or Walker Bulldog
left?
>> That is an M18.
>> Of course it is.
>> I'm repairing my barrel. Not fight.
>> Uh, he is. He's just to the left of the
uh C34.
>> They ran off. Landing on me.
>> Oh god. Calm landing on me.
>> Chop from right.
>> They took my legs.
>> I'm flanking left.
You good?
>> Down for 20 25 seconds. Down for 25
seconds.
>> Where's that other shooter?
>> Probably right about
here.
>> Corner. Corner right there. Got my
breach.
>> M18 pushing out right there. Jim,
>> 10 seconds. 10 seconds. Can't do
anything.
>> Uh, guys, commander before I go.
>> You might be fine.
I just assume the same six is going to
No, he's still pushing.
>> Pushing up right there, Jim.
>> Back in action. Back in action. Trying
to get shot. Trying to get a shot.
>> He took most of my crew right there.
Marking again.
>> Looking. Looking. Looking.
>> Thank you. I'm repairing.
>> Good shot.
>> All right. Advancing.
>> We need to push Bravo as fast as we can.
>> Yes, we do.
>> Uh, go ahead and go past me. Bonk. Bonk
has my repairs, I think.
>> Oh, I see.
>> I'm dropping RD and Bravo cuz I can.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Watch me RD you and I'll be very sad. I
was going to say like first he leaves us
for bonk bonk bonk. Now he's going to
like hey go to B. By the way I'm
dropping RD on B. Okay.
>> I got to get more artillery kills.
>> I say next thing you know he's going to
want me to give him door dash or
something or you know change the oil his
car.
>> Will you do door dash?
>> No.
>> But say that's not a very reliable
vehicle to do door dash in.
>> Oh yeah. I would Oh man. Can you
imagine? Do you know how cold your tacos
would be in this thing?
>> Cuz they never get there. Yeah, cuz they
just break down on the side of the road
while I'm waiting for uh you know,
>> contact me.
>> Actually, you right there.
>> Yeah. See?
>> Oh, nice. Okay,
I still hear more. There's still more on
the mall.
>> I am down to just the gunner. So, takes
reload. We have to get on Bravo.
>> I'm doing what I can here to get
>> that ticket bleeding.
>> Oh, yeah. It's bleeding really bad.
>> Contact right me. Go and go for Bravo.
Okay,
>> M6 backing up right there.
>> Backing up. You might have a shot.
>> They'll back up right into you.
>> There's two though on the hill.
>> There's two over there.
>> Got him.
>> Marked on map right there.
>> Oh, yeah. I see I see there's another
one. T34. Mission failed. No.
>> No.
>> Actually, that's an IS-1. Correction.
>> Why is there always so much industrial
sabotage at the AAC? The aactory has a
very very interesting history. It's been
both a museum, a historical site for
many assassination attempts of uh world
leaders. It's been bought, it it's done
buyouts, it's been auctioned, it's been
shipped overseas, brought back here, and
now I don't even know what the A factory
is anymore.
I know that they make all forms of the
letter A, bold and italicized,
but like I don't know who owns the A
factory anymore.
>> Not the community, Jim. What world
leaders came to the A factory?
>> Uh M18.
>> Oh, another one bites the dust. Oh,
>> that was assassinated.
>> Uh, Princess Zelda. Pyrole.
>> Princess Zelda. Wait, wait. We're in the
universe of Zelda.
>> Yeah, like Pyro is a real place. You
ever been there?
No, Jim. I have not.
>> Yeah, we'll pick up excited now.
>> He is.
>> You're telling me that I can go to
>> looking.
>> I have no ability to face that way right
now.
>> Okay, I am you and facing there. He's
shooting at me right there.
>> Don't worry, I can get him.
>> I'm 5 seconds back there.
>> Oh gosh. Oh, it's a big one. That's a
big one. That one hurts.
>> You got to go. You got to go. You got to
>> I'm going to use your body for cover.
So, I'm going to do
>> what you can and then uh give me a call
at the back when you get there. Think
you got a shot?
>> Nope, not really.
>> Jim's body is great cover.
>> I took down 164.
>> T34's down.
>> We should drive.
>> We need to push forward now cuz we're
going to lose that factory completely.
>> It's clear.
>> Watch your front. It's not clear front.
Contact to your front right through that
wall.
>> Whoa. That's not good.
>> Any repairs? Cuz I can't repair you.
Jim, is not a bad time to invest in the
AAC?
>> I You know what? If I were to go on my
cash app right now, it would say it
would say uh uh hold. Actually,
>> who is shooting you?
>> I don't know. Artillery.
>> I feel like now's a bad time to arrive.
A bomb just landed on you.
>> Oh my gosh, my stocks.
>> They're burning.
>> They are. I lost everything in the AAC
stock market.
>> It's plummeting, Jim.
>> I even used Acoin as well.
>> Uh the the A factory. Yes,
>> there is a tank here somewhere.
>> I think I hear it.
But I'm going to be honest. I could be
hearing friendlies. I could be hearing
>> another bomb.
>> Brace.
>> Oh, good. He didn't get you.
I have a radical new idea how to survive
this round.
>> What would that be?
>> A disguise.
>> Well, it's a disguise. Oh.
>> Oh, I see.
>> Why' you say it like that? Cuz
my disguise worked and yours didn't.
>> Okay. Yep. Uh-huh. All right. A likely
story for a spy.
>> See, he kind of took a shot at me, then
stopped because he realized, oh, wait,
that's friendly. This round's gone so
poorly on breaking out Team Fortress 2
spy tactics.
See, it does work.
Back in 1875, the Aactory was founded by
Alistister Adams Alexander III.
He was a Norwegian immigrant
from the city of uh
a with an umlouse. Sorry, I I don't
speak Norwegian. And uh he founded the
AAC.
>> Please not again. Anything but this.
Tune in next time for the next exciting
episode of a factory lore. Ah, yes. The
boy band on the foldout stage. All three
of them.
>> Would you stop making me feel bad about
my vehicle choice? Also, where's that
T2?
>> It's uh
>> I hear him, but I can't see him.
>> I just saw him. Where'd he go?
>> I see the ME410. M410's on him.
That's a yak.
>> No, that's a yak.
>> Where's the tu?
>> Please don't let me die to him another
time.
>> Is he behind you?
>> Is he Hang on. What's that thing behind
you? Turn around. Turn around. Turn
around. What's What's that giant thing
in the sky?
>> The Oswin is firing at something. The
act 9. Something flew.
>> No. Hall front. Hold front.
>> Pull front.
>> All front up. What is that?
>> All front up.
>> Those are warning shots to go away. He
just dropped another bomb. Come on. this
bomb out. Get the bomb. Get the bomb.
Shoot the bomb. Shoot the bomb.
>> I got it.
>> Yo,
>> I want to leave.
>> Please shooting clay birds.
>> Please let me leave.
>> When you're when you're in an AA, shoot
the bomb. Don't run.
>> I was driving away.
>> No, just shoot the bomb.
>> I already accepted defeat this match.
Even though we have the cap, but we
could win. In my heart, we already lost.
We have to.
>> Just because your morale is gone doesn't
mean you got to give up on this team.
>> Gem stocks burned. My disguise failed.
>> My stocks haven't burned. They're just
low. If we get the cap, I can get my
stocks back and then I can retire.
Another
>> playing 345.
>> You know what, Bo? That's life. Okay.
>> That's a Bearcat.
>> That's a
What's a Bearcat?
>> I'll take it.
>> The boy band's kind of rocking, Joe. I'm
sorry.
Are they like more in sync or are they
like uh um uh 98 degrees? Backstreet
boys.
>> He's 47 with HVRs incoming.
>> I see something out by the spawn.
>> Reloading.
>> Please.
>> He's got one more bomb. I can't fire
that way very well.
If he comes back, I'll help. Actually,
he's come back around towards dark self
stick.
Okay. Looking. There you go.
>> I shouldn't have told you that. I guess
>> I look away for two seconds.
>> M18s really like you.
P47's down.
I like the way his wing fell off. Made
me happy. In the '9s, there was a
politician by the name of Bob Dole. He
was very famous for making a speech
called the giant sucking sound of
American industry. The aactory was part
of that giant sucking sound. And the
Aactory has not been the same since,
especially since they went public.
>> Are you going to tie Al Gore to the AAC
next?
>> No. No, he has nothing to do with this.
He's actually he works at the G factory.
>> Why the G factory?
>> Gore.
>> Oh, I see.
>> Is that where they made the internet?
No, the the internet actually was uh
made at the tube factory because there's
a very famous news uh interview where
the internet is a series of tubes from
like 1992.
>> So, you're saying the Gactory claimed it
made the internet?
>> Well, the G Factory is kind of weird.
That's one of those like weird like
companies that
that it's it's it's got a lot of I I
know more about the AAC um because
number one, I also have a a really good
portfolio in the AAC. I'm actually a uh
second generation a factory employee.
>> Contact left ambush.
>> Oh god. Oh god.
>> Jim, they're coming for your stock
office.
>> Shoot that one. Shoot that one.
>> Trying to. I don't know where it is. I
just see Mark.
>> Shoot that mark.
>> Shooting the mark. Oh my god. I got the
gunner.
>> Now shoot the R3. Murder the rat car.
>> There's a rat there.
>> Yes. Shoot my mark down. Rats down. I've
lost my barrel.
>> No rats. The a
>> contact right. I've been shot again
through the gap. I'm trying. I'm trying.
Yep, I see it.
>> Hi, Jim. I have trauma.
>> Hello. Are you You're burning.
>> I am.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> Fire hot.
>> Guys, do you want to know the the real
dark secret of the AAC?
>> Uh bomb landing on you. I'm sorry I
couldn't catch him.
>> That's okay.
>> I think that was the CIA trying to keep
you from talking about the AAC anymore.
>> No, I'll come back. I'll come back. I I
refuse to be a victim. I will not be
quiet. I'm going to go on all of the
podcasts that have all the
whistleblowers.
Where does the A factory get its
funding, Jim?
>> You know there's a weapon that's often
referred to as the A bomb.
>> Are you saying they developed the atomic
bomb at A?
>> Yes. All forms of the letter A. Bold,
alticize, and nuclear.
You see, the A factory,
>> the Lauron, this just goes everywhere at
this point. I don't even know how to
connect this. The aactory is one of
those very very sketchy companies that
has fingers in the pies of all the
players of World War II.
>> No, that's that's different. That's next
episode.
>> Imagine if Amazon was in World War II.
>> We just prime shipped everything to
Europe.
>> Oh my god, that'd be hilarious. Can you
imagine just like all all of the
electric vans just showing up on
Normandy with a bunch of like packages?
Amazon flux drivers with crates of
grenades.
>> Instead of Liberty ships, they're Amazon
ships.
>> Instead of like the duel at Cologne
where it's the the Persing versus the
Panther, it's just like the Amazon truck
running over a freaking Panther.
>> What is the Amazon brand stuff again?
Like Amazon Choice
>> Prime.
>> No, they have a name though, right?
There's like a brand like the
>> Amazon Choice.
>> I forget.
I I think it's
>> I just imagine 30 out 6 Amazon choice.
>> Oh my god. Instead of D-Day, it's it's
Prime Day.
>> Prime Day.
>> All amphibious landing crafts are half
off.
>> Yep.
>> Something's wrong with us. We've been
hurt by industry.
>> We really have.
>> No, I think this isn't War Thunder.
>> Uh plane over the coast coming back in.
>> Where?
Here's another really dark thing about
the A factory or
>> main road.
>> Every every letter A on the on the
Allied side in World War II most likely
came from the A factory, but there are
conflicting sources that say a lot of
German materials that use the letter A
also had uh a factory serial numbers on
it. It's very it's very corrupt
>> at this point. Just let me drag a banner
behind me so I can do some advertising
and make some money because
nobody is shooting at me.
>> Well, stick boy, we've had a really good
ball game today. We'd like to take a
moment to thank our sponsor, uh, the
ME410B pulling around there by Mr. Bo
himself there. He's been a really good
sponsor. Thank you very much. I I am the
sports cer calling the plays. Thank you
very much, Driver.
>> That's a bad sound.
>> And someone has a Hail Mary nuke. Let's
see where it goes. Stick boy, what do
you think on the field? Uh Jim, I am
pleased to announce that it is for the
home team.
>> Hey, I'm being shot at.
>> Factory is going to be
>> I can leave soon. Please, please shoot
more accurately
>> here. I'll turn right towards you.
>> Well, if I could if I could uh my
greatest mentor is John Madden. Let me
let me just draw some yellow stuff on
here. You're seeing the big the big
>> hostile takeover.
>> This offensive push on a you see you got
the running back here. You know, he
thinks he has a hole with the offensive
line. The problem is the guard trips. He
forgets his block and the offensive line
>> that nuke cannot come fast enough.
Please
>> is now in strike everybody down
>> is now in a bad spot. See this is not
good for coordinator is losing his mind.
>> And see what they always say about stick
boy is the best defense is a good
offense and vice versa. You see, I'm
going to keep drawing yellow stuff on
the screen to make it seem like I'm
talking about because you have to
realize that a lot of sports casters,
your dad, if they watch enough football,
they could probably do their job. But
never mind, they don't have the voice.
Anyway,
it seems the blimp is shooting at the
booth. That's very weird. Anyway, and
touchdown.
And that's it. Your uh team has won. I
actually don't remember who dropped the
nuke. The the A town atomics win the
game.
>> Today's good broadcast is brought to you
by the letter A. No, we don't have crazy
ties to to weird dictators back in World
War II. We swear.
[Laughter]
>> We're all slowly going insane.
I was holding it until I heard the dog
go off NFL team.
>> You want to rock paper scissors? Who
goes first?
>> Yeah. Uh, all right. One, two, three.
>> We have to like do with the Oh.
>> Oh. Oh. With the barrel. One. Hang on.
We're very slow. One.
>> This isn't working very well, is it? Cuz
I can't do the up and down motion very
fast.
>> Yeah. It's like It's like we're playing
rock paper scissors in slow motion. I I
hear that tank to the right of us.
Should we?
>> He's trying to figure out why we haven't
pushed yet. And we're trying to figure
out how to play rock, paper, scissors
with a tank. All right.
>> Do you want scissors? I'm going.
>> Okay. All right. Oh god. You got
>> I got paper.
>> That was a rock. Sorry. That was a rock.
>> Okay. He's down. Are you good? Are you
good? What hurt?
>> Emotionally. No. He's about the bush
right there.
>> Okay. All right. I'm angling. I'm
angling. I'm angling.
>> All right. I'm almost loaded. I'm almost
loaded.
>> I'll push first.
>> Okay. Go ahead.
>> Make sure to advance around the corner.
Take him when he kills me.
>> No.
>> It's M18. He was snuggled into the
building.
>> What are these things? There's one,
>> I think. Oh, type 61. Okay.
>> Okay. Uh, Jim.
>> Yes.
>> Dangerous ugles.
>> Oh, you won.
>> There's only two, right?
>> Yes. As far as I know.
>> That was so close to me dying.
What horrible thing happened here?
>> I don't know. Oh gosh. What did Hang on.
>> Contact right. M19.
I'm looking.
M42, I'm sorry.
>> Oh, I just realized I'm fixing a friend
by me. I'll be here for a second. I'm
still looking down.
>> That VK was broken.
>> Both VKs are broken.
>> Mitro passed me because I thought he was
AFK. I didn't know he needed help.
>> No, I'm I'm fixing one and then the AFK
one just now needed a repair.
>> So, he didn't need repairs passed,
right?
>> No, the guy next to me needs a repair.
>> I'm just Yeah, it's it's it's weird. I
think the prototypes are failing.
I just want to make sure I No. Right.
Contact. Behind him. Behind him. Danger.
I'm gone.
>> ASU.
>> Why is he still driving at us? Why is he
killing people?
>> Wait a minute. Uh, I got the commander.
>> He just got bombed.
>> He did.
>> What was happening?
>> I don't know. But that ASU for some
reason did not see the menacing of me
turn.
>> Did he want cuddles?
>> I I don't know. But like you have to
understand like we're at the BR where an
ASU57 is like a Chihuahua with the
plague.
>> If he took me out, everybody else is
looking a different direction. So he
could have got a multi-kill on Panthers
and Protype Panthers.
>> Both these VKs are just so transfixed on
what is going on down here. They they
did not realize how much danger they
were in.
>> All right, this one's repaired.
I think our work here is done.
>> I I think so, too.
We need to work on our rock, paper,
scissors game.
>> We really do.
>> It's so weird watching him try to slowly
raise his barrel as I'm just staring
down at him.
>> Tell him you had the higher ground.
>> I did. That's how I won the battle.
Star Wars face awesome times.
>> I love you, Anakin. Like a brother, you
were the chosen one.
>> Thank you, Jim, for that synopsis of the
movie.
Meanwhile, Anakin is just sizzling there
like a sausage. I hate you.
>> I want the director's cut.
>> I died.
>> The Disney lawyers coming in to make
sure you never talk about Star Wars
again.
>> I forget that Disney owns Star Wars now.
What a weird time.
>> I think we all try to forget that. Also,
there's many tanks pushing up in front
of me here.
I'm going to have to make a uh move
here.
>> Yeah. And it might be a contested move.
>> How many tanks are I going to drive over
here?
That's how I was spying on T18's gunner.
>> More than one.
>> I regret that decision. I got him a
party though. It was worth it.
>> My goodness.
>> There he goes again.
>> I may die, but he suffered and that is
okay with me. I sound really cool for
saying it like that.
>> No, it's an M18. It deserves it.
>> Okay. You just sound like you just
really dislike M18s. M18s are
technically an invasive species
depending on what map you're on.
>> I'm just finding it really funny that
I've already now like half a dozen M18s
today.
>> You're sinking them like three-pointers.
>> I see one tank in front of you right
there.
Bomb is away.
>> I have Yeah, there's also a heavy tank
to the Never mind.
>> That's two down.
Neither of those were heavy though. So,
is there another one or artillery
coming?
>> Wait, no. No. What? And then what did I
but they were
>> thick.
>> Hey, so I might have confused heavy tank
in the
>> What?
>> I blew up good.
>> What happened?
>> I blew up real good.
[Music]