You know, always cheers us up on a bad
night warn gym. What's that? The A
factory. But unfortunately, this is the
lame battle version of abandoned
factory. So, A is over there on their
side. Welcome to the second location of
the Aactory.
My name is Margaret. I will be giving
you a tour of the Aacto's remote
location, street vendor. What if I want
to go to the original AAC location? A
Factory is closed. You're not allowed.
What if I'm one of those YouTubers that
breaks into places and We will call the
police and get your channel demonetized.
You can't catch me. Oh, yes, I can. I
have a drone.
We have drones, too.
Drone on drone fighting. You You were
trained on drone combat.
The year 2025 has been very weird in
advancing for the A factory. Okay. I
want to let you know as you're fighting
for your life, we also have a letter A
cryptocurrency on Coinbase if you would
like to invest in the cryptocurrency
called the letter A.
My favorite part is it sounds like he's
just holding his chest.
Oh no. T2061 in the gap machine guning
you currently. I think you see him. I'm
sorry the information came too late to
help. I took his gunner. I hate how I
was useless the entire time and I just
watched you both die.
I'm more concerned about the
Ghostbusters secretary voice you were
trying to do there. That just sounded
like pain. Ghostbusters.
What was her name? That drives me nuts
now. I don't know, but she was cute.
What?
What? What? I'm just saying.
Ghostbusters.
Damn. Please tell us your first
childhood crush was the Ghostbusters
secretary. One of them. Is he like 80?
No, no, she's not.
She just dresses very
conservative and has kind of a
um what was her demeanor would you call
it?
Sweet and bratty in New York. Sweet and
bratty.
Yeah. Uh you know what? You know what? I
looked up a picture. You know what did
it for me? The glasses. The glasses
holder.
The necklace loop thingy. That's what
did it. Bunch of targets over here on
this wall. Okay,
I hear them migrating behind us. Don't
stick. It's a bad idea. Okay, good luck.
Just thing to your right, though.
There's one to the left. Yeah, but I was
more to the right. Sorry, I didn't think
you're going to go just do that. Hey, so
B, I'm very concerned. T26es. Oh, I'm
watching one of them.
I don't like T26s and I'm I lost a
wheel. Help me. I'm trying to hunt one.
I'm still movable. I'm still mobile. I'm
still mobile. I'm still movable. Was I
gonna say get mobile? Movable. Hey, Jim.
It's looking at me through the wall of
his barrel. Okay. I'm I'm I'm coming
into the uh Oh, god. Stay away from my
friend. Transmission radiator.
Get him. Rub him. I need to put a wheel
back on. I'm repairing. I am also
repairing. Sick is all you right now.
You're doing a great job out there.
It's all me in an R3. This one's barrel.
It really needs to go. Why'd you play me
out? Engine radiator again. Engine
radiator again. Still fixing breach. I'm
sorry. Two barrels here. I just Okay,
there's two of them. I'm not even going
to try to fix this wheel. It's not worth
it. I have to I'm dropping already
myself. Jim, you're not going to be able
to shoot with three wheels.
How do you think I got the engine
radiator on one? Target scout again. Try
to push through. I'm going to poop
this. Go, go, go, go. Okay, moving,
moving, moving. You got shot again. He's
trying to
leave. I did nothing. He's got a machine
gun. He's very upset, Jim. Oh, I'm ready
for battle. So sad. I'm ready for
battle. Help me. I just dropped already
here. What am I doing? No, you back up.
Stop. Just stop. I'll repair you. Just
stop. I'll repair you. Okay. Okay. Okay.
We're supposed to look like
professionals. Act like we know what
we're doing. I did what I could for you.
Okay. I appreciate cleaning up the
entire time. I'm glad that T-34 is over
there doing I can I can walk again. Uh
gym airplane. Uh hey guys. No, they're
bombing the A factory. Oh no, they are
they are lighting the A factory up in
bombs. A factory is responsible for any
injury.
This is going terrible.
Bombs. The roof just fell in. Something
just tried to shoot at me and missed.
Did you see that guy just die in front
of us?
I did that 4 A285.
I think this is why they moved the A
factory like the actual like a wife was
miserable enough for him. Uh I guess
I'll go first. I raised my hand. No, no,
no, no. I No, hang on. I got shot. I'll
go first.
Thank you for concluding your tour at
the original site of the AAC.
Unfortunately, you've been trespassing.
I'm surprised we haven't seen anything
yet.
You know what? That's I shouldn't say
things like that. I knew it. Can you
please take them? Yes. Yes. Yes. Hang
on. I I need to get the barrel. Barrel.
Come on. Barrel, please. Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm an
amateur. Hey, stick, can you take him?
Stick. Stick. Um, just right past him. I
can try. I'm trying to get on his side.
I was trying to let the one coilless
rifle get the kill, but I whiffed that
so hard. I'm so sorry.
I kind of noticed.
I just froze up. There's a P8. Never
mind. There was a P8. Oh, thank God. No,
it was on our team. Oh, never mind. I'm
sorry. Rip that guy.
Thank you, sir. Let's go repair him.
Let's go
repair this guy. I don't know if
grouping up is a great idea right now.
No, no, no. We're fine. Rats together
strong. See, look at that. So, uh, you
want me to go, uh, stick a wheel on a
contact front. Oh, that's really bad. I
missed a shot.
Hey, Jim, you are the one proposed
rifle. I'm just going to keep saying
that. I know. A right there. I'm
reloading 19. You're unfortunately Jim's
cost me my life. They're both dead.
Oh, he's just looking at me, too, like
I'm a snack. I am so sorry.
I think this is a learning moment mainly
for me. There's tanks moving down the
valley. Mark right there. Yeah, I think
I saw one of the Koopas going from the
left to the right. That's 800 m. If I
see another one pushed right there, I'm
going to take a shot.
I'm going to keep watching low over
here. Contact close to us. I hear an
engine approaching very quickly.
It belongs to an American T series
heavy. Possibly T29. High or low? Right
beside me. Oh, hard left. I guess I
should have set that first. That would
have been helpful information. I kind of
want to poke out, but also I remind
myself what I'm in. He just fired. He's
got 50 kills, but I'm going to push him.
I got your backup. Driver loader. Hey,
looking a bad idea.
It worked out though. Good teamwork. I
was worried about detonating myself.
Also, one's still back here. Yep. Okay,
pushing up. I'm looking for it. Can
breach. He doesn't have a large machine
gun, so he can No, commander.
He's down. Nice work, guys. Nice work.
Good push.
Now, I think it's time to scattle before
payback comes. Yeah, I was going to say
like they're probably really mad that
couple of rats. You want to go get C?
Triple rat attack. Yeah, triple rat
attack.
Here we are, actually. I mean, wheeled
vehicles like this, I I often call them
rats. R3's all We hit them with that
ratat.
About the rati, but I'm going to dive
off this cliff. That's what I'm going to
do. Oh, Jim, I have a mission. I'm
sorry, Jim. I'm sorry. Help. Help me.
Help me. I'm sorry. I have a mission to
complete. Okay. I My people need me.
I just fired from I'm so sorry. I can't
stop laughing. I was dropped into a
hostage. I'm commercial boss down here.
I can't stop laughing. I'm sorry. Oh
god. The hill. On the hill. It's up
there laughing at us. I'm looking at the
hill. I'm looking. We're good.
Oh my god. Wait. Where was the one that
got Jim? I'm not going back to find out.
Being far away.
No, he's at our level. Oh, he's down
there.
Sorry. Brain's running at max
computations right now.
I'm worried about also low right,
but see that mark
stick. That's probably Yeah, I see the
mark. Yep, that is. I think that is. All
right, let's push carefully.
All right. I don't like that shell just
phased through me. Well, I mean, that's
a teammate. B plate. We're good. Never
mind. All right. If Yeah, you push that
way. I'll push closer left.
He's in here somewhere. See that
scumark? He's hiding behind a rock right
there. I can see top of him. That's Jim.
He got bullied by antos.
Yes. Uh there was someone who wanted to
speak with me at the se point while I
was going to be uh watching your guys'
back. Good work, sick.
Yep. On the way to you. I'm repaired.
I'm going to watch up at Charlie for a
second.
Yeah, there's one firing again up in the
rocks
here. I'm going to see if I can sneak a
shot in. Saw the scout mark.
M18 did not see
him. That's from my rear. Uh, he's
watching right now to your hard left.
Are you breaking up with me? No, I just
feel like you can find better teammates
because I feel like your tubs are my
fault. I'm sorry. That one I had nothing
to do with.
Okay. I don't know that T3485
say we're having a moment here and I
just Are you breaking up with me? 85
millimeter shell hits you in the face.
God, what a what a day, huh? That
timing. What a day.
Oh, I see
him. There we go. Vengeance was served.
Thank you. I'm just got a tank up.
There's one pushing on our side. That's
M18.
Holy moly. I was looking for Yeah,
that's him. That was the M18 I was
looking for.
Wow, his turret went
like a whole grid square away. I like
how I'm hiding behind this body, using
it for concealment a little bit, backing
up, and then stick just parks right on
the edge of the cliff, silhouetting
himself like, "Hi, I'm here. Witness my
AA greatness." There's a plane flying
right at us. Plane. Oh, that's a bad
time to run alone.
Don't worry, I helped. I'm so concerned
for our futures. It sounds like there's
an entire motorpool of tanks on the
other side of this wall.
It really does. I'm kind of afraid. Is
someone going to Kool-Aid man through
this? Yeah, one just broke the wall.
It's pushing
fast. You see him right there? Yep. He
sees me. He's going to push me a second.
He just shot the two.
Oh, that's a left.
I'm
going driver, machine gunner. The other
one's got a lot of 50 cals on
them. Also, there's a Tiger just running
free. That's a T34.
Gunner, machine gunner,
Tiger. Okay, this is a I'm sorry, big
boy. You have to go
first. Or they can all rush in here.
Aren't those tanks more terrifying when
you're that small and they're that big?
I was just thinking they're generally
terrifying when they all push together.
I just want to find somewhere where we
can
um capture point and have a nice
life. I don't think that's in the cards
though. No. Why did I go this way? Why
did this go this way? He can't look at
me. He can't look at me. Did you go the
same way? No. No. I I went I I'm off to
your right. Stick. Be careful. There's
big things. Get to your front through
that wall. Yep. I'm hiding behind the
alo. Contact left up on the hill. That
was a bad mark.
I'm surprised I was able to make it
through this. Damn, we need to push
through that. That shell went through a
stick and almost took me out, too. Okay,
I go through the tunnel. Yes, please go
through the tunnel. Go through the
tunnel. Go through the tunnel. I hate it
here. Oh, god. You're close left. There
might be something.
Close left. Is it clear?
for now. Yes. There's a We got tigers.
You have a plan or you just panic to
keep driving off cuz I'm following you.
I'm going to I'm going to go to B. Let's
go to B. We just gave up on A. Yeah, A.
A's a silly. Well, you can't be. I'm
going to push past and see if there's
anything over here. Here. Hide behind
the flammable tank with me. I found
something. Tell me about yourself. Oh,
what' you find? There's a rare tiger. A
rare tiger.
Your
favorite. He's processing. Oh, he looked
in the kill feed. Oh. Oh, yeah. The one
with the hybrid noise to let you know
that it's coming when it's slow.
What? Yeah. Have you noticed how all the
teammates around us are kind of just
vanishing?
Yeah. Is there something scary over
here? Yeah, there is.
Where? Wait, that's a in front of me.
There's a tiger right here. No, I'm
sorry. That's something big. There's a
big thing over there.
Um. Oh boy. I'm scared. I have to wait
for him to break the wall. I didn't do
anything. Oh. Oh my god.
Protect yourself. I'm I'm Got my gunner.
I only got his commander. Pull his tail.
No, I don't think that works on a tank.
It's a tiger. I'll just shoot him and
blow him up with a heat shell. Okay,
thank you. It's time to run. We got to
go. Oh, hello. Oh, you didn't finish
capping. I'm trying to help. No, cuz you
were in trouble. Do you want me to go
finish?
Wait. No. Jip. No. No. Jip. Jip. No.
There's a Churchill. I don't know what
he's trying to say other than I heard a
Churchill. Goodbye. Goodbye. I'm
leaving. Be a lost cause. Goodbye.
Where's the Church Hill? Uh, it's
apparently it's over there.
Thank you for this information as I'm
now pushing my face into danger.
Somewhere over there. It's over there.
Yeah, it's somewhere over there.
It's there. Go on your track. You can
swarm it. See if you can break his
barrel.
Okay, trying. Okay, let's see if I can
take the rest of
them. Drivers out cuz we're worried
about him, you know, trying to run away.
There's a Panzer 470. Where's the Panzer
470, Jim? Other side of a building from
you. I don't know. It's just concrete
all over. Man, about that Tiger.
And we're going to go this direction
now. I want to
go. What a catastrophe this match is.
Really like truly a catastrophe.
I just want to go home. Stick is broken.
I can't even get any information out of
him at this point.
A fun experience for the whole family. I
would watch to your front right.
I see it behind the barrels. Yeah. Copy.
Driver gunner. You got time if you want
to flank it and kill the twin bill. You
want me to leave it for you or take it?
If you got it, take it.
I was reloading.
That's okay. How about that airplane?
Oh, hey, there's a PL. Yep. Don't worry.
I think I'm going to work with M18. He
seems trustworthy.
He's leaving us for tank destroyers.
That makes sense. You heard, Mike?
Oh, can you do anything to it? Let's
Yeah, you're good. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Nice work. Front
danger. Oh, I got the track. No, I want
to back up. I would like to back up.
Back up. Yes, I'm back. Back up.
I don't want him to turn.
So, that was a hit not to drive forward.
Okay. Do you want to turn around, go
back home? Maybe. I think we should go
across the river and flank whatever is
taking everybody from the other side. I
was going to say we go home. I got pizza
rolls in the freezer. I can share them
with you. You just want to leave. That's
all you want to do. Yes, I do. I want to
go home. There's no place like We can
make the run across this bridge, Jim,
and then make the run across the other
bridge, flank those guys, and become
glorious war heroes. Okay, I believe
you. If it goes to hell, it's your
fault. Oh, let's focus on Jim. Save
yourself. I have no front wheels.
No. Oh, just save yourself. Oh, no. I
ain't got no legs.
Uh, they also took the thing that makes
the other wheels drive. It's right
there.
Thank you. It's dead. Okay, it's dead.
Oh, you look ridiculous. Get yourself
together. I'm sorry. There's a lot of
trauma happening here. You look so
silly. Okay. Got wheels. There's a No.
No. Not again. Not again.
I didn't know which way to cover. I
could have had pizza rolls and been
comfy. And you drag me out here. You
lose your wheels. I lose my head. I
mean, the pizza roll is very convenient.
and I can put it in a bowl and just kind
of munch on it like a glutton. Whereas
like a pizza big, I'll have to put it on
a platter. Hey, just a status update.
We're being pushed pretty hard by tanks
on all
fronts. Marking one right there. You got
a close rifle or something? Sorry.
Another one marked over there loader.
Does anybody have any weaponry that is
attached to like a heat shell or not?
Not really. Unfortunately, the best you
get is air.
Yes. You got anything like light
skinned? Like maybe like a a truck or a
You got a plane maybe? Yeah, like a
tractor with some corrugated steel
plate.
Uh the sink just fired me down the
river.
Also, very slow plane coming in. It
looks like he's going towards the
building.
No, beer covered. I two or 10 over the
river.
Hey, I got him.
Like I was shooting sporting clays. Is
that a locust?
Wait, what? I don't take any solless in
that. But
no forgiveness. Forgiveness ended. No.
Oh, the P8 that dropped the bomb on me
is named slap lettuce.
You think he slaps his lettuce?
Oh, I thought his lettuce slapped. Why
do you think he does the cabbage? Hey,
so these three bombs I was going to drop
on their team just got reallocated to my
squadmates. I see a whole herd of them
over on
Bravo. That looks like an ontos,
which I could use cannons, but a bomb
feels way more necessary right now.
That's a bit intense. No, no, no. Hetos
deserves it. It's been that kind of
match. It has something I try next to
you. Stick.
Do you see what I'm in? You're the only
one that can stop it. Or I could stop
it. I could stop and I could have just
Never mind.
We could have came up with a better
plan. You said I was the only one who
could stop it. I mean, on the ground.
I'm I'm in the air and I technically did
stop him,
but next time I'll be sure to say you're
the only one on the ground. Also,
something you right here, Jim. Yes. It's
a bat bomb. I'm trying to help you.
You got him. I got tracks in a
barrel. Also, something hit me pretty
hard. I got
him. Thank you for your assist. No
problem. The thing that got me is on my
left now.
Flying towards you. Unfortunately,
trying to locate you. Where's my friend?
Where's my friend? I'm going down. He's
over the city. Oh
no. B1's down. Awesome.
I like how gave me soft landing for
that. That didn't feel soft
or really landing. Was it the kind where
like your teeth fall out? I love those.
I was expecting to find a big heavy tank
over here, but I found this little
guy. And I just missed that somehow.
Oh, okay. All right. Good news. We have
a machine gun on our obble, and I'm
happy to use it. That was slightly
embarrassing. I'm happy you're happy.
That was actually kind of scary. Front.
I see it. I did nothing. That was an
awkward time to jump over the concrete
barrier. Hey Jim, there's IS-6 that
wants to meet you. There's an M103 that
actually is taking me out. Why did we
just run through the two biggest tanks
we could possibly find? Because we are
in little rat tanks and uh yeah, that's
how it goes.
Okay. He's like saving me from the M103.
This is awkward.
Did he want cuddles? Was he saving me
for later? I don't know what just
happened to me. Was I just offered up as
payment 103 over here?
Engine track. You want to try and finish
him? Driver loader. Driver loader. All I
can get. Unfortunately, he took my
gunner. It still had it shell for me.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to
do very much, but uh go for his barrel
if he
can or keep him distracted.
I was hoping for more of that hit.
We're okay. I just keep circling them.
Yeah, I'm just just make sure I friend
doesn't push in here as well. Uh, can
you take his tracks? 50 cal's gone.
I'm almost loaded. Hello, Jim. Welcome
back to the party. Thanks.
I am here to help. Let's go. Put that
one there. And then this. I like how
there's two Tiger 2 staring at him,
though.
All righty. So, now we got to go find
the IS-6, right? I don't know if he's
still alive or not. It's been a while
since I've had a sighting on him.
Understandable. We can we can pick we
can totally pick apart number six,
right? He's still alive.
All right, let's just assemble it.
Oh, you guys know where he's going.
Okay.
Well, I did nothing, but he should be
distracted by me. Okay, I'm I'm putting
a new belt in. Putting a new belt
in. I'm keeping him kind of over here if
I can. He's still pulling towards me.
Keep driving. Keep driving. All right,
here we go. Uh, there's a plane about
Jim. He's turning faster than I can.
Bo, I'm trying. B, I'm trying. Got the
gunner. We have time. Just take that can
if you can. Trying to We're in a another
fight that's happening like this. Okay.
Can we uh like put some bomb music in
there? His machine guns up. You can take
it. The top one.
Okay, it's down. Picked them apart. Oh,
there's a jet.
I six down. Yeah, it's it's quite big.
7 seconds. See, that shell just almost
hit me out there. Yeah, it's actually
really scary. Oh. Oh, hey, there's a
plane.
I don't know why I'm laughing cuz I'm
next.
I should have been there, man. I should
have saw it.
[Music]