Plane at 185 heading away. Let me
randomly shoot him and see if I get his
attention. That just hit. I just hit. Or
you can just absolutely nail his wing.
Gunter driver. He's all yours, Bo.
I cast follow-up shot.
Thank you. Also, that's really bad.
That's like worst case scenario for me.
There's a greater wizard here than you,
Bo. I'm traumatized. Me, too.
Are we clear otherwise? I I guess so.
Stick's here. Hi, Stick. Hi. Plane's
coming back. Coming back. It's coming
back. It's coming back. No. No. It
lights me. I'm the chosen. That counts.
I claimed that kill. I point at my
monitor, too. That's not how that works.
I am such a good target. He had to come
back. I was desirable. He liked you a
little too much. Hey, it doesn't happen
often for me. Okay, let me have it. You
ever fall into these traps on YouTube
where you uh see these videos that are
like this 5x5 wood shed was built in
1785 and was used and this this and this
and it's like a four or five hour video
and I'll just sit there the entire time
fascinated by just a random history of
some structure that's been abandoned for
60 years. Actually, I do the same thing
cuz I have a couple of structures in my
town. the abandoned Six Flags videos.
I've watched all of them.
I am a really big fan of uh the uh urban
explorers that go to abandoned places
and like, you know, they respect the
area. They don't vandalize everything,
but they are just kind of walking around
maybe a place they shouldn't be. But
it's really cool to see like malls and
stuff that like haven't been used in 20
years. I found this video that talks
about animatronics. I can't remember the
channel's name, but he went on a big
Chuck-E-Cheese deep dive and there was
this one ride that's like a I say ride,
but you know, like the helicopter thing
you used to go up to the ceiling and
back down. It's just a video of him
trying to figure out what that was
called. Really? I watched all of it.
Something wrong with me? No, cuz I was
about to bring up something else that's
cursed about Chuck-E-Cheese. Did you
know that there's a really really like
welldetailed authentic old school
Chuck-E-Cheese in VR chat? That's very
heavily populated. Of course, you know
that. It's really weird. I was also
going to mention that same channel did
performance reviews of all the different
characters on Chuck-E-Cheese and how
much effort talent they have. Oh god. I
am so sorry. I just saw I was thinking
about Oh my god. Same. I'm sorry. Here
you go. Go forwards. I'm just going to
go forwards. That way you can go that
way. Oh well. I guess I'm going forward.
Hello. Thinking about that awful cheese
pizza that's cardboard.
possibly reheated. You want to You want
to know a weird thing?
Oh, the tank that's in front of Jim that
just took him. Oh, boy. That I just
stared at and blankly thought about
cheese pizza. I'm realizing I should
probably say something or shoot him.
It's okay. I stared at him, too. I'm
hungry. I'm sorry. Growing up, I thought
Chuck-E-Cheese had the best pizza. Cuz
you're a kid and you're just happy to
have pizza. Yeah. You don't know any
better. What an awkward way to greet
someone. S there's one in front and uh
behind me through there. Okay. Yep.
Coming up behind the one that I've got
the one that's behind you. I'm just
going to keep driving cuz he's behind
me.
Yep. Yep. Keep driving.
I'll circle back when I can.
Nice kill.
One behind you. I hear I hear sounds. I
hear sounds. We need to recap. A by the
way.
American tank on A. I'm sorry. I have to
pick what street I go down.
Actually, you might be pushing me.
Hello. You're not an American. Uh, hang
in there if you can. I'm sorry. Not the
greatest vehicle to respond with.
Uh, bad news. Are you winning? No. And
he shot. I'm sorry.
T34. He's left. I saw his exhaust
towards the point.
He's just right there. He's down. Yo,
look at that cool old bus next to you.
I'm over here looking for tanks. And Jim
is looking at transportation vehicles.
You're so excited for Transport Fever 3,
aren't you? I really am, actually. I
They better have all my my sweetheart
locomotives and trucks and buses there.
Maccados and what else do you like? Uh
the New Haven EP5 electric locomotive.
I've activated something inside of him.
Uh the uh Pennsylvania GG1.
Um let's see here. What else do we like?
You know, every train person is judging
you right now for your answers. I mean,
it's okay. to each their own.
I can also start listing off like trucks
I like uh you know when you when you
when you get to like the 19 early 1900s.
Please no. I'm sorry. Two planes. B and
you go from the Mac truck to an Opal
Blitz. Oh, are you still listening? Bo,
are you still listening? I'm still here.
Yes. Okay. Yeah. So, like I really like
the Opal Blitz cuz it's actually a very
versatile truck early game. Yeah, it
gets kind of weird in the 1930s, but but
you know, we won't talk about that. Fell
with some bad people.
Yeah. Yeah. I kind of hung out with the
wrong crowd. Bad crowd in middle school.
Yeah.
I just like how I can keep my favorite
vehicles going for like a hundred years.
So like it's the year 2077 and my coal
train still being pulled by a big boy. I
love it. I know that's the name of a
train engine. I know that.
So the Union Pacific Big Boy was an
articulated steam locomotive.
It's very big.
Hey, look. There's an airplane.
That one's called a Corsair.
I'm familiar with his work.
Yeah, those were built by a few
different companies, but VA and Goodyear
are my favorites. Brewster, eh?
Goodyear.
Yeah, Goodyear built planes. Did you
know there's an AA here? I took his
gunner if you bomb is out. I'm just
going to clear it. Did you know you put
that in his turret? The uh the old
defunct model train uh company called AC
Gilbert during World War II made the
machine gun parts for the Hellcat.
Okay. Yeah. And then after the war
they're like, "Yo, I'm Listen, I'm just
being shot at. We have really good
tooling to make even better model
trains."
By the way, the entire time I was
staring at my model train shelf. So, you
know, the uh there's a conspiracy theory
with the AAC. They say they're carbon
neutral. Actually, they they have a very
very bad carbon deficit.
The war on this has gotten so deep.
I also heard the AAC uh would fire
people for taking excessive uh bathroom
breaks. Okay. Why is the AAC now turning
into like a dystopian business? From the
events of 2020 where a lot of people had
to work from home at the AAC, there was
some terrible management decisions. And
now in 2025, the A factory is a very,
very problematic workspace.
I just picture people now typing the
letter A on their keyboards and getting
paid for it.
That's pretty much what happens.
They have to write them out now. Well,
see, that's what they used to do back up
until about 199. Truck front left.
Truck. Truck. Truck. Rival truck. Truck.
Oh god. You got to handle the truck. I
got the driver in the thing. Sorry. He
was going to die. I was going to say I
don't have one. I'm not taking
deliveries. Yeah, neither am I. That was
his last package to drop off. I'm sorry.
I'll stop. That's okay. I can't help
myself. See, now now I don't trust the
the vanilla trucks on the map. Look at
that. Look at that thing just staring at
you menacingly. Uh contact there. It's
short. Maybe stout
and you shake it all about. It's down.
Thank you, Jim. I'm concerned about your
uh leadership right now. Your scouting.
My sticks in front of me. It's his
fault. It is not my fault. He's got the
battle flag on his tank. He's the
leader.
No. Uh-huh. Yeah, you do. That Yes, I
have the flag. I'm not contesting the
fact that I have the flag. Jim,
where do we go? Senpai, tell me. I
kind of glad I'm slower. Please talk
some sense into him. I don't know if I
can do that. Hey, how many people are
going to get laid off when they realize
you can copy and paste letter A? Oh,
don't multiple times. Yeah. So, like
that's another thing about the the the A
factories. They also went down the road
of NFTTS.
Special A's.
Yeah. One of a kind A's. Collector A's.
Mhm. I have a uh problem over here.
Also, they're on A. They're on A. We
lost a Jim. Oh, Jim. They've taken over
the factory. Oh, boy. Who's they? The
letter B. The B
gang. I heard the B factory is actually
quite nice.
Does the letter B have like a gang sign?
Like is it just holding like two of your
index and thumbs together? Well, there's
been some controversy because on the
lowercase B side they they install them
backwards and they become D's and there
hasn't been a D point in years. Double
dipping
there. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Counterfeit
actually. Big problem. The D tank on the
hill. Yes. Oh god. That wall. Never
mind. It's dead. Ignore that statement.
It's okay. It got me moving. I'm going
to go see what's on the A point. I'm
going to attempt to scurry up there with
you. Okay. Uh I think we're going to go
through here. Hey Jim, please pick all
the narrowest options you have. Uh just
increase my suffering, please. You know
what? Yeah. Here. Actually, let's try to
go together. Hold my hand.
What if I go through here and flank? Uh
you may get stuck on that pile of
rubble.
Might be contact to your left. Uh I
think you're right. Oh boy. I'll be
around in three business days. Hold me
now. I'm 6 ft from the edge. And he's
singing dead rock.
Maybe 6 feet isn't so far down. I really
think you should,
you know, have a discussion with him
though.
He's here. Tiger's almost there.
Uh, you might want to mark on the map
for him. T34. T34. I'm pushing. Hold on.
Let me mark the map. You got it. I'll
double mark it. Yeah, please do that.
Thank you. I was like, I'm at the ready.
I might be able to get a shot. Never
mind. He's down. All right, perfect.
We had him surrounded. We caught the
thief.
You doing okay, buddy?
I think so. Let's check in on you. You
know, the A factory released some really
interesting chemicals and uh I I have to
chemicals. I used to work at the A
factory. Um, what tank right there? I
may be entitled to a settlement. Sorry.
Got it. Thank you. Thank you.
Do you know what? Uh, tank. I missed the
shot. Good news. I ate the shot for you.
I looked back just at the right second
to catch that 152 in my face. Oh my
gosh.
I didn't finish my my lore dump yet of
the downfall of the AAC.
Jim, what was the downfall of the
Aactory?
It's very controversial.
Did they get bought out by Amazon?
It may be, but Or was it Black Rockck?
Does B stand for Black Rockck?
Actually, I think you're right. I I I
remember. If you're deep in the war, A
is Amazon, B is Black Rockck, who would
C be?
Um,
Polar Coler and uh uh uh
Polar and Goldstein there. Totally
legitimate. What is that? A financial
firm? I never heard of that. Yes. Yes,
it's a financial firm. They're out of uh
Little Rock, Arkansas. You're making
this up. Absolutely. There's no way.
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
Just because you said Little Rock
financial firm. I knew that was
complete. Well, what do you mean? Little
Rock's the investment capital of the
world. What are you talking about?
Arkansas is the venture capitalist
capital of the world. That That's what I
just said. That paid me to say because
of words and I'm okay of getting shot
down. Shout out to all my homies in our
Kansas. I'm going try to squeeze on your
right here. I'm going to try not to hit
you. Well, you know how long it's been
since I went to trigonometry.
Just watch your left and air stick. Oh,
hello. The one front still there. That's
my gunner 86.
Gunner and loader. You got time. Jim,
watch front. Oh, that's good. I'll
finish 18. Okay, go ahead. My right just
got hit. There's a swim down.
Sherman. Sherman. I'm sorry. That's two
targets front then.
I have no visual. I just saw the muzzle
flash. I'm going to push Jim. I can't
aim. I'm going to push forward too.
Swarm.
Taliho. There's the Sherman. Thank you.
I saw something else down there. He
might have gone around the flank,
though. I'm looking back. Far far.
Transmission's out on you. I'm working
on it. I'm sorry. I don't have a great
line of sight back there. There's a
Sherman in the way. Okay. Can you mark
it if you see it? Uh, it's it's
somewhere over here. He went around the
corner, right? Oh, I don't know.
Where are you? Come on. Show yourself.
Show yourself. Come on. There he is.
He's low. All right. Copy. Sorry. I
thought it went further right. He's
moving to the left.
I got stuff to my left.
Hopefully all friendlies.
I'm going to back up a few feet. I have
8 seconds before my transmission's back
in action. I'm trying to watch that gap
there.
I figured he ran into that building over
there. I'm sorry. No, it's okay. He
literally shot me, disappeared. I could
not tell where it was from. Left. Oh,
little thing. Left. M18. Left. Through
the tunnel. Through the tunnel. Copy.
Your thing is now pushing forward as
well. That M18 is so surprised.
He has another one in there with him,
too.
All right, this is becoming slightly
horrifying.
You are now alone over there for a bit,
so please be careful. There's also plane
strafing me, so the challenge just
increased. Objective survive. Getting my
gunner back.
There's one pushing from front still,
and that's going to be a big issue for
me
cuz I see him just slowly creeping up
through the trees at me.
All right, might have a shot. He's down.
Nice. Where now? Who is living in here?
That's a jumbo.
Who else wants some? No, please don't.
I am so
petrified of bombs when I play this
thing.
I just assume every bomb's going for me.
Oh, they're circling you. I would just
Yeah, I'm going to hide in here.
I just don't know which side to watch.
Well, good news. If you if you can hold
out for like 30 seconds, you can watch
one side and I can side
And if you wait 45 seconds, I'll be
there.
That's too long. Oh, okay. I'm trying.
It's the effort that matters. I hear
another plane.
I'm tigering as fast as I can. That
sounds so close. Oh, it's flying
directly over. It's trying to find me.
There's two more planes on their side
that are like swooping around and I
think Okay. Nope. Uh, this is air
traffic control to ground control. Um, I
see three enemy PL. You're getting
strafed. No, I'm inside a tunnel for
that reason.
Okay. I thought it was stick. Hello, I'm
here. I was actually going to reload
while I'm sitting here.
So, if I explode, it's a bigger boom.
So, artilleries now. They're dropping
already on me. Yeah, they they want this
thing gone. I was going to ask if you
wanted anything like uh you know, some
snacks or maybe a cold beer.
Can I have a cheeseburger? Uh,
yes. Any bombs? Asking for a friend. Oh,
I got a Zins. Sorry.
I'm going to push out over here a little
bit. Oh my gosh. Stick boy. Yak 9K. You
got Ramure.
Would you like to join me? Jim. Yeah. I
just wanted to live and be. Never mind.
They got me.
Where did that How did they Did he throw
the bomb in the tunnel? I have no idea
at this point. If he did, shout out to
that guy. But also, I'm sorry you're
dead. I'm shout out the enemy. That was
impressive. If they if they alley ooped
the bomb into the tunnel, that's kind of
impressive. Say you had like a bounty on
your head. I'm just watching teammate
after teammate disappear to airplanes
right now. I I I got killed. The 9K is
just picking people like the Toy Story
crane.
The claw. It's flying right at me.
No, my bomb.
Tragedy.
Please don't judge me. It just has to be
done.
Do your thing. You look like a ski
shooter right now.
I don't have the right shell loaded yet.
Up that one's down. Okay, that's when I
hit the head on.
Plane at 185 heading away. Let me
randomly shoot him and see if I get his
attention. Okay, that just can
absolutely nail his wing.
I still had AP loaded, too.
Let me just get his attention real
quick. Plane at 320. Totally takes his
entire left wing.
Stranger danger. Love your toaster.
Workplace. Workplace harassment.
No. Oh, Rook.
This got weird, didn't it? Wow. Yeah.
Please love your toaster. No. No.
Please. No. Cherish your toaster. No.
No. It's bath time. Toasters and baths
don't mix. Why don't you give the
toaster bread anymore? Well, I'm trying
to feed me bread. No, I'm on a keto
diet. Please. No. Keto diet. Carbs are
good for you.
Support your local wheat farmers.
Embrace gluten.
Feed bread.
I bake bread at work, but like not
edible bread.
Talking about money, cash and arrow.
It's time to go. There's a there's a
bomb. Goodbye. If you can point out the
badman hurting you, I'll hurt them back.
Um, is it a Sherman? The sky. Yes, there
there is a Sherman. There's also a T44
behind him. Understood. I'm pushing up.
Those were the main ones. I can get you
proper spots. One right there. Engine is
repaired.
I'd rather take a shot at him. There's
one pushing around this corner a second.
Just be mindful. Yep. I really want that
T44 right there. Marking again.
Actually, that's a T34.
I'm sorry.
Hey, so there's also an IS-2.
Is this an or something?
Interesting. Same spot.
Yeah, they're like next to each other.
All right, push up slowly.
I might only be able to take one. Also,
there's one low right of me charging, so
I choose you, M24.
Oh, hey, stick. Yeah, you didn't tell me
that uh there was a whole army of them
over here waiting for this opportunity.
Sherman, look out for the Sherman.
The second I pushed up, they just popped
out from behind like every rock in the
hill staring at me. I got hit with a
bomb. I only saw the two. Unfortunately,
they I guess I wasn't good enough for
all of them to pop out. The best part is
they're all like one to two battle
ratings under what I'm driving. Like the
little tank nation came out.
I hate when little tank nation comes
out. They're a really strong gang.
They're adorable though. Yeah, but like
they bite.
I took the chaffy over the is
just out of spite. No, it's fine. I Oh,
sorry. I I was given a parking ticket
actually as soon as I spawned. That was
interesting. Is that what it was? Jim,
would you like me to bomb the things up
here or a
one tank right here? I can take whatever
you need.
Uh, this guy's getting strafed. I'll
I'll take him. I'll take the silenc.
Thank you. I was trying to see if I
could see you some spots, but from my
position. No worries. I got a mark for
you. One more back here. X might be
dead.
Um here
and I'll be back in a second. A growing
list of vehicles. I don't like that. If
you see a plane, let me know cuz I'm
staring at ground. All right. One right
here. Oh, there's a plane rolling on
your six. Copy.
He's on He's on your right wing. Does
anybody have machine guns? Uh, nope. I'm
watching you from the grave.
I guess the Yeah, you tried to do the
crossover at Monaco and just hit the the
wall. Monle. Monaco. There we go. I'm
sorry. Stick. I'm going to give this guy
a fight over. He has a fun name.
Oh, that is a name. Mr. Hamster. Uh,
stick high left. Two targets. Yep.
The one that has to be right there.
Rips. Where is the thing that was? It's
tiny. Right here. That's when it killed
me. Wow. On where I crashed. I'll try
and mark him for you. Okay. Yep.
All right. I can't Oh, my breach is out.
I'm sorry, B. My breach is out. I got
shot in the back. I'm going to take this
guy on the right first. There's one down
here. Okay. I can't do anything about
it, unfortunately. You just stay
beautiful. He's right here. Yep. BFW's
got you.
It's just the little crusader.
Well, I mean, when you don't have a
breach, any tank looks terrifying. I was
going to say, did the crusader bully
you? Yeah, he did. He saw I was myself.
That's my worst nightmare. No, I'm sorry
for making fun of you. No, it's okay. Uh
there I think there's stuff behind me. I
hear things. I hear things that aren't
us. I'm attempting to run. Okay, I'm
fixed. Okay. I was panicking so much I
realized my repair ended 4 seconds ago.
Is there something behind you? We're
getting bombed.
Maybe. Please don't say that. Over here.
Uh across the valley there was something
taking shots at me. I don't know if it's
still there. So be careful if you want
to come this way. I don't trust it. I'd
like to grab a crew member if possible.
All right, get the crew member. Uh what
way do you want me to look? Which way do
you think we're going to die from?
Uh I don't know, chief. That's a big
ass. Any guesses?
Like playing Russian. How about from the
sky? Cuz I hear the bomb. No, no, no,
no, no. Oh, it was Are you okay? I'm
fine. Are you fine? I'm fine. I need
That was an odd noise you made. I need
new trousers, but I'm fine. I can't help
you with that. Okay. And I won't help
you with that. Right. Here. Do you want
to go find a good friend?
Do you hear the noise over here? Uh Jim,
your engine. The plane is so mean. Leave
him. No, he's dead.
They killed you in front of me in cold
blood. Does someone need some happy
camper repairs?
I don't know if I want to go back to you
or not. I don't want repairs with that
voice.
What was that voice, Jim? Oh, that was
Midwestern uh camp counselor.
Maybe that's why I gave flashbacks.
Gst stick. You got to be more active.
You're not a You're not a good trooper.
Okay, so there's two reasons now I don't
want to join you. One is that boy.
Second, there's artillery landing on you
and I'm in an open top vehicle. I ain't
praying no ghost.
I was reading for artillery hit you
there. Oh my god. But if it did, I would
probably just go outside and probably
have half a pack of cigarettes and then
just I don't know, maybe pull the motor
out of my Lincoln or something. Man
stuff. Man stuff.
But you wouldn't put it back in.
I can put it back in. It's a 302. It's
really easy. Out in. No, I'm saying you
just wouldn't. You take it out and just
leave it there for 6 months.
You know what? You're right.
But he did say it was his Lincoln, not
his project car. So it might get
completed. Every vehicle has this
project. He has like five project cars.
Well, yeah, but this one at least seems
like it drives. Man, I wish I had a five
project. He likes to hop in the Suburban
and drive around southern Wisconsin
looking for other projects, cars or
women. Yeah. And then in my daily
driver, my frontier, I cosplay as like I
go on vacation every week out to the
bush. And I don't I just go to work.
Thank you, sick. Something out there. I
There's something to our right.
FB40005.
Really awkward to try and use that.
There's two of them. Hey, Jim. There's a
second one with him. I know. I was Why
did I follow you? I was about to call it
out.
[Music]